The O O
Democratic B-ORG B-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
" O O
Partido O B-ORG
Democrático O I-ORG
" O O
) O O
of O O
Chile B-LOC B-LOC
was O O
a O O
Chilean O B-LOC
political O O
party O O
created O O
by O O
a O O
left O O
- O O
wing O O
faction O O
of O O
the O O
Democrat B-ORG B-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
1932 O O
. O O

Located O O
on O O
the O O
south O O
bank O O
of O O
the O O
Qiantang O B-LOC
River O I-LOC
estuary O O
, O O
it O O
borders O O
Ningbo B-LOC B-LOC
to O O
the O O
east O O
, O O
Taizhou O B-LOC
to O O
the O O
southeast O O
, O O
Jinhua B-LOC B-LOC
to O O
the O O
southwest O O
, O O
and O O
Hangzhou B-LOC B-LOC
to O O
the O O
west O O
. O O

Its O O
system O O
is O O
managed O O
by O O
Thalys O B-ORG
International O I-ORG
( O O
SNCF B-ORG B-ORG
( O O
62 O O
% O O
) O O
, O O
NMBS/SNCB O O
( O O
28 O O
% O O
) O O
, O O
and O O
Deutsche B-ORG B-ORG
Bahn I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
10 O O
% O O
) O O
) O O
and O O
operated O O
by O O
THI O B-ORG
Factory O I-ORG
( O O
SNCF B-ORG B-ORG
( O O
60 O O
% O O
) O O
, O O
NMBS/SNCB O O
( O O
40 O O
% O O
) O O
) O O
. O O

Nasser O B-PER
's O O
tenure O O
as O O
Egypt B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
leader O O
heralded O O
a O O
new O O
period O O
of O O
modernization O O
, O O
and O O
socialist O O
reform O O
in O O
Egypt B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
a O O
staunch O O
advocacy O O
of O O
pan O O
- O O
Arab O B-ORG
nationalism O O
( O O
including O O
a O O
short O O
- O O
lived O O
union O O
with O O
Syria B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
, O O
and O O
Developing O O
World O O
solidarity O O
. O O

" O O
Where B-MISC B-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Party I-MISC I-MISC
At I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
2001 O O
R O O
& O O
B O O
song O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
R O O
& O O
B O O
group O O
Jagged B-ORG B-ORG
Edge I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
with O O
guest O O
vocals O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
hip O O
- O O
hop O O
artist O O
Nelly B-PER B-PER
. O O

Karameh B-LOC B-LOC
Border I-LOC I-LOC
Crossing I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Arabic O B-MISC
: O O
مركز O B-LOC
حدود O I-LOC
الكرامة O I-LOC
) O O
is O O
the O O
only O O
border O O
crossing O O
between O O
Jordan B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Iraq B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

After O O
keyboardist O O
Rick B-PER B-PER
Wakeman I-PER I-PER
left O O
the O O
group O O
in O O
May O O
1974 O O
over O O
disagreements O O
with O O
the O O
band O O
's O O
direction O O
, O O
Yes O B-ORG
entered O O
rehearsals O O
as O O
four O O
- O O
piece O O
at O O
bassist O O
Chris B-PER B-PER
Squire I-PER I-PER
's O O
home O O
in O O
Virginia B-LOC B-LOC
Water I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Surrey O B-LOC
. O O

Yellowtail B-LOC B-LOC
Dam I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
dam O O
across O O
the O O
Bighorn B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
south O O
central O O
Montana B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
the O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Ljubljana B-LOC B-LOC
Town O I-LOC
Hall O I-LOC
( O O
Slovene O O
: O O
" O O
Ljubljanska O O
mestna O O
hiša O O
" O O
, O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
" O O
Ljubljanski O O
rotovž O O
" O O
or O O
simply O O
" O O
Rotovž O O
" O O
or O O
" O O
Magistrat O O
" O O
) O O
is O O
the O O
town O O
hall O O
in O O
Ljubljana B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
the O O
capital O O
of O O
Slovenia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
is O O
the O O
seat O O
of O O
the O O
City B-LOC B-LOC
Municipality I-LOC I-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
Ljubljana I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Vithura B-LOC B-LOC
is O O
a O O
small O O
village O O
situated O O
36 O O
km O O
from O O
Thiruvananthapuram B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
capital O O
of O O
the O O
Kerala B-LOC B-LOC
state O I-LOC
in O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

East B-LOC B-LOC
Midlands I-LOC I-LOC
Parkway I-LOC I-LOC
railway I-LOC I-LOC
station I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
located O O
north O O
of O O
Ratcliffe B-LOC B-LOC
- I-LOC I-LOC
on I-LOC I-LOC
- I-LOC I-LOC
Soar I-LOC I-LOC
on O O
the O O
Midland B-LOC B-LOC
Main I-LOC I-LOC
Line I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
the O O
East O B-LOC
Midlands O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
England B-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Air O O
Marshal O O
Sir O O
Bruce B-MISC B-PER
Reid O I-PER
Ferguson O I-PER
, O O
{ O O
" O O
1 O O
" O O
: O O
" O O
, O O
" O O
2 O O
" O O
: O O
" O O
, O O
" O O
3 O O
" O O
: O O
" O O
, O O
" O O
4 O O
" O O
: O O
" O O
} O O
( O O
born O O
14 O O
July O O
1949 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
retired O O
Royal B-ORG B-ORG
New I-ORG I-ORG
Zealand I-ORG I-ORG
Air I-ORG I-ORG
Force I-ORG I-ORG
officer O O
who O O
served O O
as O O
Chief O O
of O O
the O O
New B-ORG B-ORG
Zealand I-ORG I-ORG
Defence I-ORG I-ORG
Force I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
Director O O
of O O
the O O
Government B-ORG B-ORG
Communications I-ORG I-ORG
Security I-ORG I-ORG
Bureau I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Commonwealth B-MISC B-LOC
Park O I-LOC
is O O
in O O
Canberra B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
on O O
the O O
north O O
side O O
of O O
Lake B-LOC B-LOC
Burley I-LOC I-LOC
Griffin I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

He O O
was O O
born O O
in O O
Eston B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Saskatchewan B-MISC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
received O O
degrees O O
in O O
literature O O
from O O
the O O
University B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Saskatchewan I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
the O O
University B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Toronto I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Football O B-MISC
in O I-MISC
Australia B-LOC I-MISC
refers O O
to O O
football O O
codes O O
played O O
in O O
the O O
country O O
including O O
Australian B-MISC B-MISC
rules I-MISC I-MISC
football I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
rugby O O
league O O
, O O
rugby O O
union O O
, O O
association O O
football O O
, O O
American B-MISC B-MISC
football I-MISC I-MISC
and O O
Gaelic B-MISC B-MISC
football I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

Wendy B-PER B-PER
Boase I-PER I-PER
helped O O
Henrietta B-PER B-PER
Branford I-PER I-PER
to O O
write O O
the O O
novel O O
Fire B-MISC B-MISC
, I-MISC I-MISC
Bed I-MISC I-MISC
, I-MISC I-MISC
and I-MISC I-MISC
Bone I-MISC I-MISC
which O O
won O O
the O O
Guardian O B-MISC
Children O I-MISC
's O I-MISC
Fiction O I-MISC
Prize B-MISC I-MISC
. O O

Senieji B-LOC B-LOC
Trakai I-LOC I-LOC
Castle O I-LOC
was O O
a O O
castle O O
in O O
Senieji B-LOC B-LOC
Trakai I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
literally O O
: O O
" O O
Old O O
" O O
Trakai B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
, O O
Lithuania B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Webbs B-LOC B-MISC
Creek I-LOC I-MISC
Ferry O I-MISC
is O O
a O O
cable O O
ferry O O
across O O
the O O
Hawkesbury B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
South I-LOC I-LOC
Wales I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Its O O
height O O
above O O
nearby O O
cities O O
varies O O
from O O
1908 O O
m O O
above O O
Huamantla B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
2461 O O
m O O
above O O
Villa O B-LOC
Vicente B-PER I-LOC
Guerrero I-PER I-LOC
, O O
2221 O O
m O O
above O O
Tlaxcala B-LOC B-LOC
to O O
2299 O O
m O O
above O O
Puebla B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

" O O
France B-LOC B-LOC
" O O
, O O
accompanied O O
by O O
her O O
sister O O
ship O O
" O O
Jean B-PER O
Bart I-PER O
" O O
, O O
was O O
sent O O
to O O
the O O
Black B-LOC B-LOC
Sea I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
1919 O O
to O O
oppose O O
the O O
Bolsheviks O B-ORG
during O O
the O O
Russian B-MISC B-MISC
Civil I-MISC I-MISC
War I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

The O O
Qu O B-LOC
rises O O
in O O
southwestern O O
Jiangchuan B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
flows O O
through O O
the O O
Yuxi B-LOC B-LOC
City O I-LOC
, O O
Eshan B-LOC B-LOC
Yi I-LOC I-LOC
Autonomous I-LOC I-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Tonghai B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Jianshui B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Huaning B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
to O O
reach O O
its O O
mouth O O
at O O
the O O
Panxi O B-LOC
Town O I-LOC
of O O
the O O
Huaning B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Gohar B-PER B-PER
Ayub I-PER I-PER
Khan I-PER I-PER
( O O
Urdu B-MISC O
: O O
گوہر O O
ایوب O O
خان‎ O O
; O O
born O O
15 O O
January O O
1937 O O
) O O
, O O
is O O
a O O
Pakistani O B-LOC
veteran O O
politician O O
, O O
business O O
oligarch O O
, O O
retired O O
army O O
officer O O
, O O
and O O
conservative O O
figure O O
of O O
the O O
Pakistan B-ORG B-ORG
Muslim I-ORG I-ORG
League I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
who O O
held O O
ministerial O O
positions O O
during O O
the O O
administration O O
of O O
Prime O O
Minister O O
Nawaz B-PER B-PER
Sharif I-PER I-PER
. O O

Fatehpur B-LOC B-LOC
Sikri I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
town O O
in O O
the O O
Agra B-LOC B-LOC
District O I-LOC
of O O
Uttar B-LOC B-LOC
Pradesh I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
history O O
of O O
jazz O B-MISC
in O I-MISC
Belgium B-LOC I-MISC
starts O O
with O O
the O O
Dinant B-LOC B-LOC
instrument O O
maker O O
Adolphe B-PER B-PER
Sax I-PER I-PER
, O O
whose O O
saxophone O O
became O O
part O O
of O O
military O O
bands O O
in O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
Orleans I-LOC I-LOC
around O O
1900 O O
and O O
would O O
develop O O
into O O
the O O
jazz O O
instrument O O
par O O
excellence O O
. O O

It O O
is O O
written O O
by O O
Don O B-PER
Black B-MISC I-PER
, O O
Christopher B-PER B-PER
Hampton I-PER I-PER
( O O
with O O
additional O O
lyrics O O
by O O
Amy B-PER B-PER
Powers I-PER I-PER
) O O
, O O
and O O
Andrew B-PER B-PER
Lloyd I-PER I-PER
Webber I-PER I-PER
. O O

The O O
film O O
's O O
cast O O
included O O
Francis B-PER B-PER
Ford I-PER I-PER
, O O
Edith B-PER B-PER
Storey I-PER I-PER
, O O
William B-PER B-PER
A. I-PER I-PER
Carroll I-PER I-PER
and O O
one O O
hundred O O
cadets O O
from O O
the O O
Peacock O B-ORG
Military B-ORG I-ORG
Academy I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

The O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
firm O O
was O O
based O O
out O O
of O O
the O O
Tin B-MISC B-LOC
Pan I-MISC I-LOC
Alley I-MISC I-LOC
district O O
of O O
Manhattan B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Police B-MISC B-MISC
Review I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
Jane O B-MISC
's O I-MISC
Police B-MISC I-MISC
Review I-MISC I-MISC
) O O
was O O
a O O
weekly O O
magazine O O
for O O
police O O
officers O O
in O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
Kingdom I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
latterly O O
published O O
by O O
Jane B-ORG B-ORG
's I-ORG I-ORG
Information I-ORG I-ORG
Group I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

The O O
film O O
stars O O
Vineeth B-PER B-LOC
and O O
Lakshmi B-PER B-PER
Gopalaswamy I-PER I-PER
in O O
the O O
lead O O
roles O O
along O O
with O O
Sona B-PER B-PER
Nair I-PER I-PER
and O O
Rachana B-PER B-PER
Narayanankutty I-PER I-PER
in O O
key O O
supporting O O
roles O O
. O O

He O O
won O O
the O O
gold O O
medal O O
at O O
the O O
men O O
's O O
doubles O O
( O O
together O O
with O O
Dainis B-PER B-PER
Bremze I-PER I-PER
) O O
event O O
at O O
the O O
1978 O O
FIL O B-MISC
World O I-MISC
Luge B-MISC I-MISC
Championships O I-MISC
in O O
Imst B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Austria B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

A B-MISC B-MISC
Christmas I-MISC I-MISC
to I-MISC I-MISC
Remember I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
1999 O O
Christmas B-MISC B-MISC
album O O
by O O
Amy B-PER B-PER
Grant I-PER I-PER
with O O
the O O
Patrick B-PER B-ORG
Williams I-PER I-ORG
Orchestra O I-ORG
, O O
which O O
became O O
certified O O
gold O O
. O O

Meanwhile O O
, O O
Michonne B-PER B-PER
( O O
Danai B-PER B-PER
Gurira I-PER I-PER
) O O
cares O O
for O O
an O O
ailing O O
Andrea B-MISC B-PER
( O O
Laurie B-PER B-PER
Holden I-PER I-PER
) O O
. O O

Professional O O
football O O
is O O
played O O
in O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
for O O
four O O
of O O
these O O
codes O O
, O O
with O O
the O O
leagues O O
involved O O
including O O
the O O
Australian B-ORG B-ORG
Football I-ORG I-ORG
League I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
Aussie O B-MISC
rules O I-MISC
) O O
, O O
the O O
National B-ORG B-ORG
Rugby I-ORG I-ORG
League I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
Rugby B-MISC B-ORG
League I-MISC I-ORG
) O O
, O O
Super B-ORG B-ORG
Rugby I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
rugby O O
union O O
) O O
, O O
and O O
the O O
A B-ORG B-ORG
- I-ORG I-ORG
League I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
soccer O O
) O O
. O O

Alton O B-LOC
is O O
a O O
city O O
on O O
the O O
Mississippi B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
Madison B-MISC B-LOC
County I-MISC I-LOC
, O O
Illinois B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
about O O
15 O O
mi O O
north O O
of O O
St. B-LOC B-LOC
Louis I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Missouri B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

As O O
a O O
film O O
editor O O
, O O
he O O
is O O
best O O
known O O
for O O
collaborations O O
with O O
film O O
director O O
Spike B-PER B-PER
Lee I-PER I-PER
, O O
editing O O
some O O
of O O
Lee O B-PER
's O O
best O O
known O O
films O O
including O O
" O O
Do B-MISC B-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Right I-MISC I-MISC
Thing I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1989 O O
) O O
, O O
" O O
Malcolm B-PER B-MISC
X I-PER I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1992 O O
) O O
, O O
" O O
He B-MISC B-MISC
Got I-MISC I-MISC
Game I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1998 O O
) O O
, O O
" O O
25th B-MISC B-MISC
Hour I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
2002 O O
) O O
and O O
" O O
Inside B-MISC B-MISC
Man I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
2006 O O
) O O
. O O

The B-MISC O
Rocket I-MISC B-MISC
Post I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
2004 O O
British O B-LOC
drama O O
film O O
directed O O
by O O
Stephen B-PER B-PER
Whittaker I-PER I-PER
and O O
starring O O
Ulrich B-PER B-PER
Thomsen I-PER I-PER
, O O
Shauna B-PER B-PER
Macdonald I-PER I-PER
, O O
Kevin B-PER B-PER
McKidd I-PER I-PER
and O O
Patrick B-PER B-PER
Malahide I-PER I-PER
. O O

Vaishampayana O B-PER
( O O
Sanskrit B-MISC B-MISC
: O O
वैशंपायन O O
, O O
Vaiśampāyana O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
traditional O O
narrator O O
of O O
the O O
Mahabharata B-MISC B-MISC
, O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
two O O
major O O
Sanskrit B-MISC B-MISC
epics O O
of O O
ancient O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
" O O
Takshashila O B-LOC
" O O
, O O
modern O O
- O O
day O O
Taxila O B-LOC
, O O
Pakistan B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
where O O
he O O
narrated O O
the O O
epic O O
poem O O
for O O
the O O
first O O
time O O
. O O

Complete O O
or O O
partial O O
oxhide O O
ingots O O
have O O
been O O
discovered O O
in O O
Sardinia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Crete B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Peloponnese B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Cyprus B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Cannatello O B-LOC
in O O
Sicily B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Boğazköy O B-LOC
in O O
Turkey B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
ancient O O
Hattusa O B-LOC
, O O
the O O
Hittite O B-LOC
capital O O
) O O
, O O
Qantir O B-LOC
- O O
Piramesse O O
in O O
Egypt B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
Sozopol B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
Bulgaria B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

His O O
compositions O O
and O O
arrangements O O
have O O
been O O
performed O O
at O O
Carnegie B-LOC B-LOC
Hall I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Lincoln B-LOC B-LOC
Center I-LOC I-LOC
for I-LOC I-LOC
the I-LOC I-LOC
Performing I-LOC I-LOC
Arts I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-ORG
Nations I-LOC I-ORG
and O O
by O O
orchestras O O
in O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Asia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Israel B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
America I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Europe O B-LOC
. O O

She O O
is O O
both O O
based O O
on O O
the O O
character O O
from O O
" O O
Beauty B-MISC B-MISC
and I-MISC I-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Beast I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
by O O
Jeanne B-PER B-PER
- I-PER I-PER
Marie I-PER I-PER
Leprince I-PER I-PER
de I-PER I-PER
Beaumont I-PER I-PER
, O O
and O O
the O O
Disney O B-ORG
princess O O
of O O
the O O
1991 O O
film O O
of O O
the O O
same O O
name O O
. O O

Released O O
after O O
a O O
few O O
months O O
, O O
he O O
led O O
the O O
unexpected O O
reconquest O O
of O O
Constantinople O B-LOC
from O O
the O O
Latin B-LOC B-LOC
Empire I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
July O O
1261 O O
, O O
restoring O O
the O O
Byzantine B-LOC B-LOC
Empire I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
Slovak O B-ORG
Radio O I-ORG
Symphony O I-ORG
Orchestra O I-ORG
( O O
previously O O
Czechoslovak O O
Radio O O
Symphony O O
Orchestra O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
symphony O O
orchestra O O
based O O
in O O
Bratislava B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Slovakia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

" O O
Do B-MISC B-MISC
n't I-MISC I-MISC
Let I-MISC I-MISC
It I-MISC I-MISC
End I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
is O O
the O O
third O O
track O O
and O O
the O O
second O O
top O O
10 O O
single O O
on O O
the O O
1983 O O
album O O
" O O
Kilroy B-MISC B-MISC
Was I-MISC I-MISC
Here I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
by O O
Styx O B-ORG
. O O

" O O
We O O
’ O O
re O O
looking O O
forward O O
to O O
getting O O
out O O
there O O
with O O
the O O
Blackberry B-ORG B-ORG
Smoke I-ORG I-ORG
guys O O
, O O
" O O
says O O
ZZ B-ORG B-ORG
Top I-ORG I-ORG
frontman O O
Billy O B-PER
Gibbons O I-PER
. O O

The B-MISC B-MISC
Kaiser I-MISC I-MISC
Aluminum I-MISC I-MISC
Hour I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
dramatic O O
anthology O O
television O O
series O O
which O O
was O O
broadcast O O
in O O
prime O O
time O O
in O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
during O O
the O O
1956 O O
- O O
57 O O
season O O
by O O
NBC B-ORG B-ORG
. O O

His O O
influences O O
are O O
: O O
René O B-PER
Magritte O I-PER
, O O
Balthus B-PER B-PER
and O O
Pierre B-PER B-PER
Roy I-PER I-PER
. O O

The B-MISC B-MISC
Red I-MISC I-MISC
Rover I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
novel O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
writer O O
James B-PER B-PER
Fenimore I-PER I-PER
Cooper I-PER I-PER
. O O

He O O
was O O
the O O
third O O
Brazilian O B-LOC
tennis O O
player O O
to O O
achieve O O
this O O
, O O
after O O
Maria B-PER B-PER
Bueno I-PER I-PER
and O O
Thomaz B-PER B-PER
Koch I-PER I-PER
. O O

The O O
Second B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
or O O
Watsessing O B-LOC
River O I-LOC
, O O
in O O
the O O
state O O
of O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
Jersey I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
is O O
the O O
second O O
main O O
tributary O O
of O O
the O O
Passaic B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
encountered O O
while O O
travelling O O
upstream O O
from O O
its O O
mouth O O
at O O
Newark O B-LOC
Bay O I-LOC
. O O

Bubba B-MISC B-MISC
Ho I-MISC I-MISC
- I-MISC I-MISC
Tep I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
2002 O O
American O B-LOC
comedy O O
horror O O
film O O
written O O
, O O
co O O
- O O
produced O O
and O O
directed O O
by O O
Don B-PER B-PER
Coscarelli I-PER I-PER
. O O

The O O
film O O
also O O
stars O O
Ossie B-PER B-PER
Davis I-PER I-PER
as O O
Jack O B-PER
, O O
a O O
black O O
man O O
who O O
claims O O
to O O
be O O
John B-PER B-PER
F. I-PER I-PER
Kennedy I-PER I-PER
, O O
explaining O O
that O O
he O O
was O O
patched O O
up O O
after O O
the O O
assassination O O
, O O
dyed O O
black O O
, O O
and O O
abandoned O O
. O O

The O O
song O O
was O O
not O O
featured O O
on O O
one O O
of O O
Morrissey B-PER B-PER
's O O
main O O
studio O O
albums O O
, O O
but O O
can O O
be O O
found O O
on O O
the O O
compilation O O
album O O
" O O
Bona B-MISC B-MISC
Drag I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
along O O
with O O
the O O
B O O
- O O
side O O
" O O
Lucky O B-MISC
Lisp O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Noordeloos B-LOC B-LOC
is O O
a O O
town O O
in O O
the O O
Dutch O B-LOC
province O O
of O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Holland I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
Seventh O O
Five O O
- O O
Year O O
Plans O O
for O O
National O O
Economy O O
of O O
Pakistan B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
otherwise O O
known O O
as O O
Seventh O B-MISC
Plan O I-MISC
, O O
were O O
a O O
set O O
of O O
a O O
highly O O
centralized O O
and O O
planned O O
economic O O
development O O
targets O O
designed O O
for O O
the O O
improvement O O
of O O
the O O
standard O O
of O O
living O O
, O O
and O O
overall O O
strengthening O O
of O O
gross O O
domestic O O
product O O
( O O
GDP O O
) O O
growth O O
in O O
Pakistan B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
between O O
the O O
period O O
of O O
1988 O O
until O O
its O O
termination O O
in O O
1993 O O
. O O

The O O
Ibergeregg B-LOC B-LOC
Pass I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
mountain O O
pass O O
at O O
an O O
elevation O O
1406 O O
m O O
in O O
the O O
Swiss O B-LOC
canton O O
of O O
Schwyz B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
award O O
was O O
founded O O
in O O
1970 O O
by O O
Roland B-PER B-PER
Michener I-PER I-PER
, O O
who O O
was O O
Governor O O
General O O
of O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
at O O
the O O
time O O
, O O
and O O
his O O
wife O O
Norah O B-PER
. O O

Surrounded O O
by O O
the O O
Western B-LOC B-LOC
Ghats I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Sahyadri O B-LOC
) O O
, O O
Vithura B-LOC B-LOC
is O O
a O O
prime O O
tourist O O
spot O O
. O O

He O O
was O O
born O O
in O O
Mexico B-LOC B-LOC
City I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
from O O
a O O
family O O
associated O O
with O O
the O O
Porfirio O B-PER
Díaz O I-PER
regime O O
and O O
who O O
had O O
to O O
hide O O
during O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
Mexican B-MISC B-MISC
Revolution I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

Aside O O
from O O
wrestling O O
, O O
he O O
is O O
the O O
lead O O
singer O O
of O O
a O O
rock O O
band O O
called O O
The O B-ORG
High O I-ORG
Crusade O I-ORG
, O O
which O O
includes O O
his O O
friends O O
and O O
fellow O O
wrestlers O O
Chris B-PER B-PER
Sabin I-PER I-PER
and O O
Petey B-PER B-PER
Williams I-PER I-PER
. O O

Berthe O B-PER
Marie O I-PER
Pauline O I-PER
Morisot O I-PER
( O O
] O O
; O O
January O O
14 O O
, O O
1841 O O
– O O
March O O
2 O O
, O O
1895 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
painter O O
and O O
a O O
member O O
of O O
the O O
circle O O
of O O
painters O O
in O O
Paris B-LOC B-LOC
who O O
became O O
known O O
as O O
the O O
Impressionists B-MISC B-MISC
. O O

FK B-ORG B-ORG
Sarajevo I-ORG I-ORG
was O O
the O O
only O O
major O O
football O O
club O O
founded O O
by O O
the O O
post O O
- O O
war O O
Yugoslav O B-LOC
authorities O O
in O O
the O O
city O O
of O O
Sarajevo B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

He O O
is O O
General O O
Secretary O O
and O O
co O O
- O O
founder O O
of O O
the O O
Institute B-ORG B-ORG
for I-ORG I-ORG
Palestine I-ORG I-ORG
Studies I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
established O O
in O O
Beirut B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
December O O
1963 O O
as O O
an O O
independent O O
research O O
and O O
publishing O O
center O O
focusing O O
on O O
the O O
Palestine O B-LOC
problem O O
and O O
the O O
Arab–Israeli O O
conflict O O
. O O

Greatest B-MISC B-MISC
Hats I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
first O O
compilation O O
album O O
by O O
the O O
Canadian O B-LOC
new O O
wave/synthpop O O
group O O
Men B-ORG B-ORG
Without I-ORG I-ORG
Hats I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
released O O
in O O
1996 O O
. O O

The B-ORG B-ORG
Guess I-ORG I-ORG
Who I-ORG I-ORG
is O O
a O O
Canadian O B-LOC
rock O O
band O O
, O O
formed O O
in O O
Winnipeg B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
1965 O O
. O O

The O O
longest O O
river O O
in O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
England I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
the O O
Connecticut B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
the O O
Knowledge O B-MISC
Corridor O I-MISC
's O O
most O O
prominent O O
natural O O
asset O O
. O O

Antonio B-PER B-PER
Maria I-PER I-PER
Bononcini I-PER I-PER
( O O
18 O O
June O O
1677 O O
– O O
8 O O
July O O
1726 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
Italian O B-LOC
cellist O O
and O O
composer O O
, O O
the O O
younger O O
brother O O
of O O
the O O
better O O
- O O
known O O
Giovanni B-PER B-PER
Bononcini I-PER I-PER
. O O

He O O
was O O
affectionately O O
christened O O
" O O
the O O
fifth O O
Beatle O O
" O O
as O O
he O O
is O O
best O O
known O O
for O O
replacing O O
Ringo B-PER B-PER
Starr I-PER I-PER
on O O
drums O O
on O O
the O O
Beatles O B-ORG
" O O
first O O
single O O
, O O
" O O
Love B-MISC B-MISC
Me I-MISC I-MISC
Do I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Introduced O O
in O O
September O O
1975 O O
, O O
the O O
Chevette O B-ORG
superseded O O
the O O
Vega B-MISC B-MISC
as O O
Chevrolet B-ORG B-ORG
's O O
entry O O
- O O
level O O
subcompact O O
and O O
sold O O
2.8 O O
million O O
units O O
over O O
twelve O O
years O O
. O O

Prem B-MISC B-MISC
Bandhan I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
Hindi B-MISC B-MISC
: O O
प्रेम O O
बंधन O O
; O O
translation O O
: O O
bond O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
love O I-MISC
) O O
is O O
a O O
1979 O O
is O O
an O O
Indian O B-LOC
Hindi B-MISC B-MISC
film O O
directed O O
by O O
Ramanand B-PER B-PER
Sagar I-PER I-PER
. O O

This O O
film O O
, O O
along O O
with O O
" O O
Amar O B-MISC
Deep O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
marked O O
the O O
comeback O O
of O O
Rajesh B-PER B-PER
Khanna I-PER I-PER
, O O
as O O
these O O
were O O
his O O
commercially O O
successful O O
films O O
after O O
period O O
of O O
one O O
full O O
year O O
as O O
in O O
the O O
year O O
1978 O O
none O O
of O O
his O O
films O O
became O O
huge O O
hits O O
at O O
the O O
box O O
office O O
with O O
exception O O
of O O
Bhola B-MISC B-MISC
Bhala I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

Mohamed B-PER B-PER
Abu I-PER I-PER
Samra I-PER I-PER
is O O
the O O
current O O
secretary O O
- O O
general O O
of O O
the O O
Islamic B-ORG B-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
which O O
is O O
the O O
political O O
arm O O
of O O
Egyptian O B-ORG
Islamic O I-ORG
Jihad O I-ORG
. O O

Team B-ORG B-ORG
Taranaki I-ORG I-ORG
is O O
an O O
amateur O O
association O O
football O O
composite O O
club O O
based O O
in O O
the O O
Taranaki O B-LOC
region O O
of O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC I-LOC
which O O
draws O O
its O O
players O O
from O O
the O O
13 O O
local O O
football O O
clubs O O
. O O

" O O
Pass O B-MISC
It O I-MISC
On O I-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
song O O
by O O
The B-ORG B-ORG
Coral I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
which O O
was O O
taken O O
as O O
the O O
second O O
single O O
taken O O
from O O
their O O
2003 O O
album O O
, O O
" O O
Magic B-MISC B-MISC
and I-MISC I-MISC
Medicine I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

" O O
Crestfallen B-MISC B-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
track O O
on O O
The B-ORG B-ORG
Smashing I-ORG I-ORG
Pumpkins I-ORG I-ORG
" O O
1998 O O
album O O
, O O
" O O
Adore O B-MISC
" O O
. O O

Slivo B-LOC B-LOC
Pole I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Bulgarian O O
: O O
Сливо O O
поле O O
, O O
] O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
town O O
in O O
northeastern O O
Bulgaria B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
part O O
of O O
Rousse O B-LOC
Province O I-LOC
. O O

The O O
town O O
is O O
located O O
five O O
kilometres O O
from O O
the O O
Danube B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
along O O
the O O
main O O
road O O
from O O
Rousse O B-LOC
to O O
Silistra B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Taedong B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Chosŏn'gŭl O B-LOC
: O O
대동강 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
large O O
river O O
in O O
North B-LOC B-LOC
Korea I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Viktor B-PER B-PER
von I-PER I-PER
Hacker I-PER I-PER
( O O
October O O
21 O O
, O O
1852 O O
 O O
- O O
 O O
May O O
20 O O
, O O
1933 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
Austrian O B-LOC
surgeon O O
born O O
in O O
Vienna B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Montazeri O B-PER
spent O O
his O O
later O O
years O O
in O O
Qom B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
remained O O
politically O O
influential O O
in O O
Iran B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
especially O O
to O O
the O O
reformist O O
movement O O
. O O

He O O
is O O
also O O
currently O O
a O O
Senior O O
Advisor O O
at O O
the O O
Albright B-ORG B-ORG
Stonebridge I-ORG I-ORG
Group I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
a O O
global O O
strategy O O
firm O O
, O O
where O O
he O O
assists O O
clients O O
with O O
issues O O
involving O O
Russia B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
countries O O
in O O
the O O
former O O
Soviet O B-LOC
Union O I-LOC
. O O

Sagdeev O B-PER
was O O
married O O
to O O
, O O
and O O
divorced O O
from O O
, O O
Susan B-PER B-PER
Eisenhower I-PER I-PER
, O O
granddaughter O O
of O O
Dwight B-PER B-PER
D. I-PER I-PER
Eisenhower I-PER I-PER
. O O

Sagdeev O B-PER
was O O
the O O
recipient O O
of O O
the O O
2003 O O
Carl B-MISC B-MISC
Sagan I-MISC I-MISC
Memorial I-MISC I-MISC
Award I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
and O O
the O O
James B-MISC B-MISC
Clerk I-MISC I-MISC
Maxwell I-MISC I-MISC
Prize I-MISC I-MISC
in I-MISC I-MISC
Plasma I-MISC I-MISC
Physics I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
2001 O O
) O O
. O O

Helm O B-PER
currently O O
teaches O O
in O O
the O O
Department O O
of O O
English O O
at O O
York B-ORG B-ORG
University I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
Toronto B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Us B-MISC B-MISC
and I-MISC I-MISC
Them I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
fifth O O
studio O O
album O O
by O O
English O B-LOC
band O O
Godflesh B-ORG B-ORG
. O O

The O O
next O O
Compiler O B-MISC
Construction O I-MISC
conference O I-MISC
took O O
place O O
in O O
1982 O O
in O O
Boston B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Massachusetts B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

This O O
would O O
be O O
the O O
final O O
Meat B-PER B-PER
Loaf I-PER I-PER
release O O
under O O
Epic O B-ORG
Records O I-ORG
until O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Very I-MISC I-MISC
Best I-MISC I-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Meat I-MISC I-MISC
Loaf I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1998 O O
) O O
. O O

Because O O
of O O
controversy O O
surrounding O O
a O O
scene O O
in O O
which O O
Cosmo B-PER B-PER
Kramer I-PER I-PER
accidentally O O
burns O O
and O O
then O O
stomps O O
on O O
the O O
Puerto O B-LOC
Rican O I-LOC
flag O O
, O O
NBC B-ORG B-ORG
was O O
forced O O
to O O
apologize O O
and O O
had O O
it O O
banned O O
from O O
airing O O
on O O
the O O
network O O
again O O
. O O

IE O B-MISC
Mobile O I-MISC
comes O O
loaded O O
by O O
default O O
with O O
Windows B-MISC B-MISC
Phone I-MISC I-MISC
and O O
Windows B-MISC B-MISC
CE I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

A O O
large O O
number O O
also O O
settled O O
in O O
Rawalpindi B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Tarnol O B-LOC
, O O
Lahore B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

They O O
are O O
also O O
present O O
in O O
large O O
number O O
in O O
Mohmand O B-LOC
, O O
Bajaur B-LOC B-LOC
Agency I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Federally B-LOC B-LOC
Administered I-LOC I-LOC
Tribal I-LOC I-LOC
Areas I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
in O O
Zhob B-LOC B-LOC
District I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Balochistan O B-LOC
, O O
Pakistan B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
district O O
is O O
bounded O O
by O O
the O O
districts O O
of O O
Monaragala O B-LOC
and O O
Rathnapura O B-LOC
on O O
the O O
East O O
& O O
South O O
, O O
by O O
Ampara B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Kandy B-LOC B-LOC
districts O O
on O O
the O O
North O O
and O O
by O O
Nuwara B-LOC B-LOC
Eliya I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Matale B-LOC B-LOC
on O O
the O O
West O O
. O O

Christina B-PER B-PER
Surer I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
26 O O
March O O
1974 O O
in O O
Basel B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
Swiss O B-LOC
race O O
car O O
driver O O
. O O

Qiu B-PER B-PER
Xiaolong I-PER I-PER
( O O
, O O
; O O
born O O
Shanghai B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
China O B-LOC
, O O
1953 O O
) O O

The O O
Valley O B-LOC
is O O
bordered O O
by O O
the O O
Colorado B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
to O O
the O O
east O O
and O O
, O O
in O O
part O O
, O O
the O O
Salton B-LOC B-LOC
Sea I-LOC I-LOC
to O O
the O O
west O O
. O O

The B-MISC B-MISC
Hitch I-MISC I-MISC
- I-MISC I-MISC
Hiker I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
1953 O O
film O O
noir O O
directed O O
by O O
Ida B-PER B-PER
Lupino I-PER I-PER
, O O
about O O
two O O
fishing O O
buddies O O
who O O
pick O O
up O O
a O O
mysterious O O
hitchhiker O O
during O O
a O O
trip O O
to O O
Mexico O B-LOC
. O O

Inspired O O
by O O
the O O
crime O O
spree O O
of O O
the O O
psychopathic O O
murderer O O
Billy O B-PER
Cook O I-PER
( O O
1928–1952 O O
) O O
, O O
the O O
screenplay O O
was O O
written O O
by O O
Robert B-PER B-PER
L. I-PER I-PER
Joseph I-PER I-PER
, O O
Lupino O B-PER
, O O
and O O
her O O
husband O O
Collier B-PER B-PER
Young I-PER I-PER
, O O
based O O
on O O
a O O
story O O
by O O
blacklisted O O
" O O
Out B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Past I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
screenwriter O O
Daniel B-PER B-PER
Mainwaring I-PER I-PER
( O O
who O O
did O O
not O O
receive O O
screen O O
credit O O
) O O
. O O

Full O O
details O O
have O O
never O O
been O O
released O O
, O O
but O O
it O O
is O O
known O O
that O O
" O O
Ratweek O B-ORG
" O O
achieved O O
successes O O
against O O
Nazi O B-ORG
personnel O O
and O O
collaborators O O
in O O
Norway B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
France B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Denmark B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
the O O
Netherlands B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Antennaria B-MISC B-MISC
media I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
North O B-LOC
American O I-LOC
species O O
of O O
flowering O O
plants O O
in O O
the O O
daisy O O
family O O
known O O
by O O
the O O
common O O
name O O
Rocky B-LOC B-LOC
Mountain I-LOC I-LOC
pussytoes O O
. O O

The O O
film O O
is O O
directed O O
by O O
Wayne B-PER B-PER
Blair I-PER I-PER
and O O
written O O
by O O
Keith O B-PER
Thompson O I-PER
and O O
Tony B-PER B-PER
Briggs I-PER I-PER
, O O
the O O
latter O O
of O O
whom O O
wrote O O
the O O
play O O
. O O

He O O
is O O
also O O
Chairman O O
of O O
the O O
Monetary B-ORG B-ORG
Authority I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Singapore I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
MAS O B-ORG
) O O
, O O
Singapore B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
central O O
bank O O
and O O
financial O O
regulator O O
. O O

It O O
was O O
released O O
on O O
April O O
21 O O
, O O
2015 O O
, O O
by O O
Slumerican O B-ORG
, O O
Shady B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
Interscope B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

The O O
Scheme O B-MISC
was O O
completed O O
under O O
the O O
supervision O O
of O O
Chief O O
Engineer O O
, O O
Sir O O
William B-PER B-PER
Hudson I-PER I-PER
and O O
is O O
the O O
largest O O
engineering O O
project O O
undertaken O O
in O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

During O O
the O O
decades O O
of O O
the O O
1950s O O
and O O
1960s O O
, O O
Healey O B-PER
was O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
leading O O
public O O
figures O O
of O O
the O O
Communist B-ORG B-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
the O O
state O O
of O O
California B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

CBS B-ORG B-ORG
Sports I-ORG I-ORG
Network I-ORG I-ORG
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
digital O O
cable O O
and O O
satellite O O
television O O
network O O
that O O
is O O
owned O O
by O O
the O O
CBS B-ORG B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Noah B-PER B-PER
Noble I-PER I-PER
( O O
January O O
15 O O
, O O
1794 O O
– O O
February O O
8 O O
, O O
1844 O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
fifth O O
Governor O O
of O O
the O O
U.S. O B-LOC
state O O
of O O
Indiana B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
1831 O O
to O O
1837 O O
. O O

It O O
is O O
the O O
site O O
of O O
the O O
Yaquina B-LOC B-LOC
Head I-LOC I-LOC
Light I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
and O O
is O O
managed O O
as O O
Yaquina O B-LOC
Head O I-LOC
Outstanding O I-LOC
Natural O I-LOC
Area O I-LOC
by O O
the O O
Bureau B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Land I-ORG I-ORG
Management I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Civil B-ORG B-ORG
Revolution I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
Italian O O
: O O
" O O
Rivoluzione O O
Civile O O
" O O
, O O
RC O B-ORG
) O O
was O O
a O O
left O O
- O O
wing O O
coalition O O
of O O
political O O
parties O O
in O O
Italy B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Como B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
] O O
, O O
] O O
; O O
Lombard O O
: O O
" O O
Còmm O O
" O O
] O O
, O O
" O O
Cómm O O
" O O
] O O
or O O
" O O
Cùmm O O
" O O
] O O
; O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
city O O
and O O
" O O
comune O O
" O O
in O O
Lombardy B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Italy O B-LOC
. O O

The B-MISC B-MISC
Beverly I-MISC I-MISC
Hillbillies I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
sitcom O O
originally O O
broadcast O O
on O O
CBS B-ORG B-ORG
for O O
nine O O
seasons O O
, O O
from O O
September O O
26 O O
, O O
1962 O O
, O O
to O O
March O O
23 O O
, O O
1971 O O
. O O

Inspired O O
by O O
the O O
Fabian B-ORG B-ORG
Society I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
Kingdom I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
it O O
is O O
dedicated O O
to O O
Fabianism O B-MISC
, O O
the O O
focus O O
on O O
the O O
advancement O O
of O O
socialist O O
ideas O O
through O O
gradual O O
influence O O
and O O
patiently O O
promoting O O
socialist O O
ideals O O
to O O
intellectual O O
circles O O
and O O
groups O O
with O O
power O O
. O O

Antwerp B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
, O O
Dutch O B-LOC
: O O
Antwerpen O O
] O O
, O O
French O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
Anvers O O
" O O
] O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
Flemish O O
city O O
in O O
Belgium B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
the O O
capital O O
of O O
Antwerp B-LOC B-LOC
province O O
in O O
the O O
community O O
of O O
Flanders B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The B-MISC B-MISC
Young I-MISC I-MISC
Ones I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
video O O
game O O
based O O
on O O
the O O
British O B-LOC
comedy O O
television O O
series O O
, O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Young I-MISC I-MISC
Ones I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

The O O
son O O
of O O
financier O O
James B-PER B-PER
Goldsmith I-PER I-PER
and O O
Lady B-PER B-PER
Annabel I-PER I-PER
Goldsmith I-PER I-PER
he O O
is O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
managers O O
of O O
the O O
sustainability O O
- O O
focused O O
investment O O
firm O O
WHEB O B-ORG
Group O O
. O O

The O O
joke O O
, O O
based O O
upon O O
a O O
mistranslation O O
that O O
suggested O O
the O O
existence O O
of O O
a O O
character O O
named O O
Sheng O B-PER
Long O I-PER
in O O
the O O
Capcom B-ORG B-ORG
fighting O O
game O O
" O O
Street B-MISC B-MISC
Fighter I-MISC I-MISC
II I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
described O O
a O O
method O O
to O O
fight O O
the O O
character O O
in O O
the O O
game O O
. O O

Saints B-MISC B-MISC
and I-MISC I-MISC
Sinners I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
an O O
album O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
rock O O
band O O
Young B-ORG B-ORG
Dubliners I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

It O O
features O O
guest O O
appearances O O
by O O
Kenny B-PER B-PER
Wayne I-PER I-PER
Shepherd I-PER I-PER
, O O
Eric B-PER B-PER
Rigler I-PER I-PER
and O O
Cindy O B-PER
Wasserman O I-PER
. O O

It O O
was O O
composed O O
by O O
Holly B-PER B-PER
Knight I-PER I-PER
and O O
Heart O B-ORG
band O O
member O O
Nancy B-PER B-PER
Wilson I-PER I-PER
. O O

Further B-MISC B-MISC
Down I-MISC I-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Spiral I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
first O O
remix O O
album O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
industrial O O
rock O O
band O O
Nine B-ORG B-ORG
Inch I-ORG I-ORG
Nails I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
released O O
on O O
June O O
1 O O
, O O
1995 O O
. O O

Al B-LOC B-LOC
Majma'ah I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Arabic O O
: O O
المجمعة‎ O O
‎ O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
city O O
and O O
a O O
governorate O O
in O O
Ar O B-LOC
Riyad O I-LOC
Province O I-LOC
, O O
Saudi B-LOC B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Public O B-MISC
holidays O I-MISC
in O I-MISC
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
known O O
as O O
" O O
statutory O O
holidays O O
" O O
, O O
" O O
stat O O
holidays O O
" O O
, O O
or O O
simply O O
" O O
stats O O
" O O
, O O
consist O O
of O O
a O O
variety O O
of O O
cultural O O
, O O
nationalistic O O
, O O
and O O
religious O O
holidays O O
that O O
are O O
legislated O O
in O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
at O O
the O O
federal O O
or O O
provincial O O
and O O
territorial O O
levels O O
. O O

He O O
was O O
son O O
of O O
the O O
philosopher O O
Friedrich B-PER B-PER
Adolf I-PER I-PER
Trendelenburg I-PER I-PER
, O O
father O O
of O O
the O O
pharmacologist O O
Paul O B-PER
Trendelenburg O I-PER
and O O
grandfather O O
of O O
the O O
pharmacologist O O
Ullrich B-PER B-PER
Georg I-PER I-PER
Trendelenburg I-PER I-PER
. O O

Men B-MISC B-MISC
at I-MISC I-MISC
Arms I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
15th O O
" O O
Discworld O B-MISC
" O O
novel O O
by O O
Terry B-PER B-PER
Pratchett I-PER I-PER
, O O
first O O
published O O
in O O
1993 O O
. O O

Babik B-PER B-PER
Reinhardt I-PER I-PER
( O O
8 O O
June O O
1944 O O
, O O
Paris B-LOC B-LOC
– O O
13 O O
November O O
2001 O O
, O O
Cannes B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
guitarist O O
and O O
the O O
younger O O
son O O
of O O
gypsy O O
jazz O O
guitarist O O
Django B-PER B-PER
Reinhardt I-PER I-PER
by O O
Django O B-PER
's O O
second O O
wife O O
, O O
Naguine O B-PER
. O O

Among O O
the O O
longest O O
bridges O O
in O O
existence O O
when O O
it O O
was O O
built O O
, O O
it O O
is O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
Overseas B-LOC B-LOC
Highway I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
the O O
Keys O B-LOC
, O O
which O O
is O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
2,369 O O
- O O
mile O O
U.S. B-LOC B-LOC
Route I-LOC I-LOC
1 I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
great O O
Storfjorden B-LOC B-LOC
flows O O
out O O
into O O
the O O
Sulafjorden B-LOC B-LOC
which O O
then O O
flows O O
out O O
into O O
the O O
Breidsundet O B-LOC
sound O O
, O O
and O O
on O O
into O O
the O O
ocean O O
. O O

You B-MISC B-MISC
Do I-MISC I-MISC
Your I-MISC I-MISC
Thing I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
fourth O O
studio O O
album O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
country O O
music O O
duo O O
Montgomery B-ORG B-ORG
Gentry I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

It B-MISC B-MISC
Wo I-MISC I-MISC
n't I-MISC I-MISC
Be I-MISC I-MISC
Soon I-MISC I-MISC
Before I-MISC I-MISC
Long I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
second O O
studio O O
album O O
by O O
the O O
American O B-LOC
rock O O
band O O
Maroon B-ORG B-ORG
5 I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

is O O
the O O
second O O
studio O O
album O O
and O O
major O O
label O O
debut O O
by O O
the O O
American O B-LOC
thrash O O
metal O O
band O O
Megadeth B-ORG B-ORG
, O O
released O O
on O O
September O O
19 O O
, O O
1986 O O
by O O
Capitol B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Alfred B-PER B-PER
Jarry I-PER I-PER
( O O
] O O
; O O
8 O O
September O O
1873 O O
– O O
1 O O
November O O
1907 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
French O B-LOC
symbolist O O
writer O O
who O O
is O O
best O O
known O O
for O O
his O O
play O O
" O O
Ubu B-MISC B-MISC
Roi I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1896 O O
) O O
. O O

The O O
town O O
has O O
its O O
own O O
railway O O
station O O
on O O
the O O
Portsmouth B-LOC B-LOC
Direct I-LOC I-LOC
Line I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
the O O
mainline O O
rail O O
link O O
connecting O O
Portsmouth B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
London O B-LOC
. O O

Mechelen B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
] O O
, O O
French O O
: O O
" O O
Malines O O
" O O
, O O
traditional O O
English O B-MISC
name O O
: O O
Mechlin O B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
city O O
and O O
municipality O O
in O O
the O O
province O O
of O O
Antwerp B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Flanders B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Belgium B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Groningen B-LOC B-LOC
was O O
also O O
the O O
site O O
of O O
the O O
headquarters O O
for O O
the O O
Sicherheitsdienst B-ORG B-ORG
in O O
the O O
North O O
of O O
the O O
Netherlands O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
railway O O
would O O
improve O O
journey O O
times O O
for O O
trains O O
travelling O O
from O O
Frankfurt O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
am O I-LOC
- O I-LOC
Main O I-LOC
to O O
both O O
Berlin B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Munich B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Theóphile O B-PER
Auguste O I-PER
Stahl O I-PER
( O O
Bergamo B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
May O O
23 O O
, O O
1828 O O
– O O
Alsace B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
October O O
30 O O
, O O
1877 O O
) O O
or O O
simply O O
Augusto B-PER B-PER
Stahl I-PER I-PER
, O O
as O O
he O O
was O O
known O O
in O O
Brazil B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
was O O
a O O
German O O
- O O
Brazilian O B-LOC
photographer O O
that O O
lived O O
during O O
the O O
19th O O
century O O
. O O

After O O
several O O
controversies O O
, O O
the O O
school O O
's O O
Honorary O O
Dean O O
Arindam O B-PER
Chaudhuri O I-PER
decided O O
to O O
shut O O
down O O
all O O
campuses O O
across O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
except O O
the O O
one O O
in O O
Delhi B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Daniel B-PER B-PER
Ellison I-PER I-PER
( O O
February O O
14 O O
, O O
1886 O O
– O O
August O O
20 O O
, O O
1960 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
U.S. O B-LOC
Representative O O
from O O
Maryland B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Active O O
since O O
2000 O O
, O O
she O O
is O O
currently O O
signed O O
to O O
Sacred B-ORG B-ORG
Bones I-ORG I-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
Bella B-ORG B-ORG
Union I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
and O O
released O O
her O O
seventh O O
full O O
- O O
length O O
studio O O
album O O
, O O
" O O
Strangers O B-MISC
" O O
, O O
in O O
May O O
2016 O O
. O O

In O O
1972 O O
, O O
Memorial O B-LOC
Stadium O I-LOC
's O O
playing O O
surface O O
was O O
named O O
Faurot B-LOC B-LOC
Field I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
honor O O
of O O
longtime O O
coach O O
Don B-PER B-PER
Faurot I-PER I-PER
. O O

It O O
is O O
the O O
second O O
- O O
largest O O
sports O O
facility O O
by O O
seating O O
capacity O O
in O O
the O O
state O O
of O O
Missouri B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
to O O
Arrowhead B-LOC B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
Kansas O B-LOC
City O I-LOC
. O O

Prior O O
to O O
2012 O O
, O O
the O O
work O O
was O O
a O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
permanent O O
exhibition O O
at O O
the O O
chateau O O
in O O
the O O
town O O
of O O
Moravský O B-LOC
Krumlov O I-LOC
in O O
the O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Moravian I-LOC I-LOC
Region I-LOC I-LOC
of O O
the O O
Czech B-LOC B-LOC
Republic I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

This O O
agreement O O
, O O
which O O
was O O
later O O
revoked O O
by O O
Prime O O
Minister O O
Rainilaiarivony B-PER B-PER
, O O
was O O
key O O
to O O
establishing O O
France O B-LOC
's O O
claim O O
over O O
Madagascar B-LOC B-LOC
as O O
a O O
protectorate O O
and O O
, O O
in O O
1896 O O
, O O
as O O
a O O
colony O O
. O O

She O O
has O O
BFA O O
( O O
2000 O O
) O O
and O O
BEd O O
( O O
2004 O O
) O O
degrees O O
from O O
York B-ORG B-ORG
University I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
Toronto B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Ontario O B-LOC
. O O

Instrument O B-MISC
is O O
a O O
documentary O O
film O O
directed O O
by O O
Jem B-PER B-PER
Cohen I-PER I-PER
about O O
the O O
band O O
Fugazi B-ORG B-ORG
. O O

Lieven B-PER B-PER
Bauwens I-PER I-PER
( O O
14 O O
June O O
1769 O O
, O O
in O O
Ghent B-LOC B-LOC
– O O
17 O O
March O O
1822 O O
, O O
in O O
Paris B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
Belgian O B-LOC
entrepreneur O O
and O O
industrial O O
spy O O
who O O
was O O
sent O O
to O O
Great B-LOC B-LOC
Britain I-LOC I-LOC
at O O
a O O
young O O
age O O
and O O
brought O O
a O O
spinning O O
mule O O
and O O
skilled O O
workers O O
to O O
the O O
European O B-LOC
continent O O
. O O

He O O
then O O
took O O
over O O
the O O
roles O O
of O O
Herry B-PER B-PER
Monster I-PER I-PER
and O O
Ernie O B-PER
from O O
Sesame B-MISC B-MISC
Street I-MISC I-MISC
in O O
2017 O O
. O O

The O O
second O O
campus O O
established O O
under O O
the O O
University B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Illinois I-ORG I-ORG
system I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
UIC O B-ORG
is O O
also O O
the O O
largest O O
university O O
in O O
the O O
Chicago B-LOC B-LOC
area O O
, O O
having O O
approximately O O
29,000 O O
students O O
enrolled O O
in O O
15 O O
colleges O O
. O O

Shaji B-PER B-PER
Kailas I-PER I-PER
is O O
an O O
Indian O B-LOC
film O O
director O O
best O O
known O O
for O O
his O O
hard O O
- O O
hitting O O
Malayalam B-MISC B-MISC
commercial O O
films O O
of O O
the O O
1990s O O
. O O

Packer O B-LOC
Park O I-LOC
is O O
a O O
neighborhood O O
in O O
the O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Philadelphia I-LOC I-LOC
section O O
of O O
Philadelphia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Pennsylvania B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
that O O
originally O O
included O O
1,200 O O
homes O O
built O O
in O O
two O O
unique O O
builder O O
developments O O
of O O
Packer O B-LOC
Park O I-LOC
1950s O O
and O O
Brinton O O
Estates O O
1990s O O
. O O

Fusion O B-ORG
featured O O
new O O
gameplay O O
features O O
such O O
as O O
EyeToy B-MISC B-MISC
support O O
for O O
the O O
PlayStation B-MISC B-MISC
2 I-MISC I-MISC
release O O
as O O
well O O
as O O
new O O
music O O
from O O
hit O O
pop O O
artists O O
. O O

The O O
village O O
is O O
on O O
the O O
border O O
of O O
France B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
first O O
National B-ORG O
Park I-ORG O
, O O
the O O
Vanoise B-LOC B-LOC
National I-LOC I-LOC
Park I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Logical I-MISC I-MISC
Song I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
song O O
by O O
the O O
English O B-LOC
rock O O
band O O
Supertramp B-ORG B-ORG
. O O

Uchylsko B-LOC B-LOC
is O O
a O O
village O O
in O O
Gmina O B-LOC
Gorzyce O I-LOC
, O O
Wodzisław O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
Silesian B-LOC B-LOC
Voivodeship I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Poland B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
near O O
the O O
border O O
with O O
the O O
Czech B-LOC B-LOC
Republic I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Dixon B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Dock I-MISC I-MISC
Green I-MISC I-MISC
was O O
a O O
BBC B-ORG B-ORG
television O O
series O O
about O O
daily O O
life O O
at O O
a O O
London O B-LOC
police O O
station O O
, O O
with O O
the O O
emphasis O O
on O O
petty O O
crime O O
, O O
successfully O O
controlled O O
through O O
common O O
sense O O
and O O
human O O
understanding O O
. O O

For O O
his O O
first O O
twelve O O
years O O
, O O
until O O
2004 O O
, O O
he O O
served O O
on O O
the O O
court O O
alongside O O
his O O
older O O
brother O O
, O O
Richard B-PER B-PER
S. I-PER I-PER
Arnold I-PER I-PER
, O O
a O O
Democrat O B-ORG
appointed O O
by O O
President O O
Jimmy B-PER B-PER
Carter I-PER I-PER
. O O

The B-MISC B-MISC
Saint I-MISC I-MISC
in I-MISC I-MISC
Europe I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
collection O O
of O O
short O O
stories O O
by O O
Leslie B-PER B-PER
Charteris I-PER I-PER
, O O
first O O
published O O
in O O
1953 O O
by O O
The O B-ORG
Crime O I-ORG
Club O I-ORG
in O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
in O O
1954 O O
by O O
Hodder O B-ORG
and O I-ORG
Stoughton O I-ORG
in O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
Kingdom I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Jan B-PER B-PER
Joost I-PER I-PER
van I-PER I-PER
Cossiau I-PER I-PER
( O O
c.1660–1732 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Flemish O B-LOC
landscape O O
painter O O
and O O
engraver O O
who O O
was O O
born O O
near O O
Breda B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Adele B-PER B-PER
wrote O O
the O O
song O O
in O O
10 O O
minutes O O
after O O
her O O
mother O O
tried O O
to O O
persuade O O
her O O
to O O
leave O O
her O O
home O O
suburb O O
of O O
West B-LOC B-LOC
Norwood I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
London O B-LOC
for O O
university O O
. O O

His O O
song O O
" O O
Take B-MISC B-MISC
Over I-MISC I-MISC
Control I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
which O O
features O O
Dutch O B-LOC
singer O O
Eva B-PER B-PER
Simons I-PER I-PER
, O O
charted O O
in O O
10 O O
different O O
countries O O
. O O

I B-MISC B-MISC
Am I-MISC I-MISC
Ready I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
American O B-LOC
country O O
music O O
artist O O
Steve B-PER B-PER
Wariner I-PER I-PER
's O O
tenth O O
full O O
- O O
length O O
album O O
. O O

The O O
Central B-LOC B-LOC
Line I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Swedish O O
: O O
" O O
Mittbanan O O
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
358 O O
km O O
long O O
railway O O
line O O
between O O
Sundsvall B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Storlien B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
central O O
Sweden B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
Västernorrland O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
and O O
Jämtland O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
) O O
. O O

Helldivers B-MISC B-MISC
is O O
a O O
top O O
- O O
down O O
shooter O O
game O O
developed O O
by O O
Arrowhead O B-ORG
Game O I-ORG
Studios O I-ORG
and O O
published O O
by O O
Sony B-ORG B-ORG
Computer I-ORG I-ORG
Entertainment I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

" O O
Helldivers B-MISC B-MISC
" O O
takes O O
inspiration O O
from O O
military O O
science O O
fiction O O
such O O
as O O
" O O
Aliens O B-MISC
" O O
and O O
" O O
Starship B-MISC B-MISC
Troopers I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Gaetano B-PER B-PER
Cecere I-PER I-PER
, O O
( O O
November O O
26 O O
, O O
1894 O O
– O O
1985 O O
) O O
American O B-LOC
sculptor O O
, O O
born O O
, O O
educated O O
and O O
worked O O
in O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
City I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Charles B-PER B-PER
Abraham I-PER I-PER
Chasselat I-PER I-PER
, O O
a O O
French O B-MISC
historical O O
painter O O
, O O
was O O
the O O
son O O
of O O
Pierre B-PER B-PER
Chasselat I-PER I-PER
. O O

Greatest B-MISC B-MISC
Hits I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
first O O
and O O
only O O
compilation O O
album O O
released O O
by O O
Haitian O B-LOC
singer O O
Wyclef B-PER B-PER
Jean I-PER I-PER
. O O

) O O
, O O
Heidelberg B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Zamdela O O
, O O
and O O
Potchefstroom B-LOC B-LOC
also O O
generally O O
tend O O
to O O
consider O O
themselves O O
to O O
live O O
in O O
the O O
Vaal O B-LOC
Triangle O I-LOC
. O O

The O O
club O O
was O O
formed O O
in O O
1892 O O
following O O
a O O
disagreement O O
between O O
the O O
board O O
of O O
Everton O B-ORG
and O O
club O O
president O O
John B-PER B-PER
Houlding I-PER I-PER
, O O
who O O
owned O O
the O O
club O O
's O O
ground O O
, O O
Anfield B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Princessa B-PER B-PER
recorded O O
a O O
cover O O
version O O
of O O
Valerie B-PER B-PER
Dore I-PER I-PER
's O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
Night O I-MISC
" O O
on O O
her O O
self O O
- O O
titled O O
debut O O
. O O

The O O
first O O
modern O O
Olympian O O
from O O
Cyprus B-LOC B-LOC
was O O
actually O O
Anastasios B-PER B-PER
Andreou I-PER I-PER
in O O
1896 O O
, O O
who O O
competed O O
under O O
the O O
Greek O B-LOC
flag O O
. O O

It O O
is O O
a O O
part O O
of O O
, O O
and O O
should O O
not O O
be O O
confused O O
with O O
, O O
Old B-LOC B-LOC
Strathcona I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
although O O
much O O
of O O
the O O
Strathcona O B-LOC
neighbourhood O O
is O O
in O O
Old B-LOC B-LOC
Strathcona I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

In O O
interviews O O
, O O
Lodge O B-PER
has O O
stated O O
that O O
he O O
was O O
listening O O
to O O
" O O
Running B-MISC B-MISC
on I-MISC I-MISC
Empty I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
by O O
Jackson B-PER B-PER
Browne I-PER I-PER
when O O
he O O
wrote O O
" O O
Sitting O O
At O O
The O O
Wheel O O
" O O
. O O

Peter B-PER B-PER
Iwers I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
on O O
15 O O
May O O
1975 O O
) O O
is O O
the O O
former O O
bass O O
player O O
of O O
the O O
Swedish O B-LOC
band O O
In B-ORG B-ORG
Flames I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

The O O
short O O
's O O
centerpiece O O
is O O
a O O
fantasy O O
sequence O O
derived O O
from O O
Clampett O B-PER
's O O
black O O
and O O
white O O
" O O
Looney B-MISC B-MISC
Tunes I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
short O O
" O O
Porky B-MISC B-MISC
in I-MISC I-MISC
Wackyland I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1938 O O
) O O
. O O

It O O
is O O
set O O
in O O
Carthage B-LOC B-LOC
during O O
the O O
3rd O O
century O O
BC O O
, O O
immediately O O
before O O
and O O
during O O
the O O
Mercenary O B-MISC
Revolt O I-MISC
which O O
took O O
place O O
shortly O O
after O O
the O O
First B-MISC B-MISC
Punic I-MISC I-MISC
War I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

Harold B-PER B-PER
John I-PER I-PER
Pye I-PER I-PER
( O O
27 O O
November O O
1901 O O
 O O
- O O
 O O
20 O O
January O O
1986 O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
son O O
of O O
William B-PER B-PER
George I-PER I-PER
Pye I-PER I-PER
who O O
, O O
in O O
1896 O O
, O O
started O O
a O O
company O O
called O O
W O B-ORG
G O I-ORG
Pye O I-ORG
which O O
manufactured O O
scientific O O
and O O
optical O O
equipment O O
. O O

" O O
The O B-MISC
Harvest O I-MISC
Of O I-MISC
Love O I-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
short O O
comedy O O
song O O
, O O
co O O
- O O
written O O
and O O
originally O O
performed O O
by O O
Benny B-PER B-PER
Hill I-PER I-PER
, O O
released O O
on O O
Pye B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
7N.15520 O O
) O O
. O O

After O O
starting O O
her O O
music O O
career O O
as O O
a O O
member O O
of O O
the O O
Space O B-ORG
Ballerinas O I-ORG
, O O
a O O
synthpop O O
group O O
then O O
based O O
in O O
Olympia O B-LOC
, O O
she O O
recorded O O
her O O
debut O O
solo O O
album O O
" O O
All B-MISC B-MISC
Your I-MISC I-MISC
Faded I-MISC I-MISC
Things I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
2003 O O
) O O
with O O
producer O O
Justin B-PER B-PER
Trosper I-PER I-PER
, O O
before O O
releasing O O
her O O
second O O
album O O
" O O
This B-MISC B-MISC
Is I-MISC I-MISC
an I-MISC I-MISC
Exercise I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
2006 O O
) O O
on O O
the O O
Kill B-ORG B-ORG
Rock I-ORG I-ORG
Stars I-ORG I-ORG
label O O
. O O

The O O
Committee B-ORG B-ORG
on I-ORG I-ORG
Judicial I-ORG I-ORG
Accountability I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
CJA O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
group O O
of O O
lawyers O O
in O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
who O O
work O O
to O O
improve O O
the O O
accountability O O
of O O
judges O O
. O O

The O O
track O O
was O O
written O O
by O O
German O O
musician O O
, O O
composer O O
and O O
producer O O
Harold B-PER B-PER
Faltermeyer I-PER I-PER
and O O
American O B-LOC
songwriter/producer O O
Mark B-PER B-PER
Spiro I-PER I-PER
. O O

It O O
is O O
the O O
seat O O
of O O
the O O
Nkandla O B-LOC
Local O I-LOC
Municipality O I-LOC
, O O
and O O
the O O
district O O
in O O
which O O
the O O
residence O O
of O O
the O O
current O O
President O O
of O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Africa I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Jacob B-PER B-PER
Zuma I-PER I-PER
is O O
located O O
. O O

The O O
city O O
is O O
near O O
the O O
Kaesong B-LOC B-LOC
Industrial I-LOC I-LOC
Region I-LOC I-LOC
close O O
to O O
the O O
border O O
with O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Korea I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
contains O O
the O O
remains O O
of O O
the O O
Manwoldae O B-LOC
palace O I-LOC
. O O

The O O
first O O
concentration O O
camp O O
was O O
created O O
by O O
Francisco B-PER B-PER
Franco I-PER I-PER
on O O
July O O
20 O O
1936 O O
and O O
was O O
located O O
in O O
the O O
castle O O
of O O
" O O
El O B-LOC
Hecho O I-LOC
" O O
in O O
Ceuta B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Chalmette O B-ORG
High O I-ORG
hosted O O
the O O
St. B-ORG B-ORG
Bernard I-ORG I-ORG
Unified I-ORG I-ORG
School I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
before O O
reopening O O
as O O
Chalmette B-ORG B-ORG
High I-ORG I-ORG
School I-ORG I-ORG
for O O
the O O
2006 O O
- O O
2007 O O
school O O
year O O
. O O

After O O
the O O
Revolution O B-MISC
it O O
was O O
refashioned O O
( O O
1799–1805 O O
) O O
by O O
Jean B-PER B-PER
Chalgrin I-PER I-PER
into O O
a O O
legislative O O
building O O
and O O
subsequently O O
greatly O O
enlarged O O
and O O
remodeled O O
( O O
1835–1856 O O
) O O
by O O
Alphonse B-PER B-PER
de I-PER I-PER
Gisors I-PER I-PER
. O O

After O O
his O O
military O O
victories O O
over O O
Chittor O O
and O O
Ranthambore O O
, O O
Akbar B-PER B-PER
decided O O
to O O
shift O O
his O O
capital O O
from O O
Agra B-LOC B-LOC
to O O
a O O
new O O
location O O
23 O O
mi O O
west O O
south O O
- O O
west O O
, O O
to O O
honour O O
the O O
Sufi O O
saint O O
Salim B-PER O
Chishti I-PER O
. O O

Unlike O O
the O O
Mason B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
Courthouse I-LOC I-LOC
also O O
designed O O
by O O
Hosford O B-PER
and O O
built O O
at O O
the O O
same O O
time O O
for O O
$ O O
39,786 O O
, O O
the O O
Glasscock B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
Courthouse I-LOC I-LOC
has O O
no O O
clock O O
tower O O
cupola O O
in O O
the O O
center O O
of O O
its O O
roof O O
and O O
its O O
side O O
porticoes O O
are O O
smaller O O
than O O
the O O
other O O
two O O
. O O

Abrakurrie B-LOC B-LOC
Cave I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
wild O O
cave O O
on O O
the O O
Nullarbor O B-LOC
Plain O I-LOC
in O O
Western B-LOC B-LOC
Australia I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

It O O
is O O
a O O
theme O O
restaurant O O
named O O
for O O
the O O
song O O
" O O
Cheeseburger B-ORG B-ORG
in I-ORG I-ORG
Paradise I-ORG I-ORG
" O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
pop O O
music O O
singer O O
Jimmy B-PER B-PER
Buffett I-PER I-PER
. O O

Albert B-PER B-PER
Tatlock I-PER I-PER
was O O
a O O
fictional O O
character O O
on O O
the O O
British O B-LOC
television O O
soap O O
opera O O
" O O
Coronation B-MISC B-MISC
Street I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

David B-PER B-PER
Tod I-PER I-PER
( O O
February O O
21 O O
, O O
1805 O O
– O O
November O O
13 O O
, O O
1868 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
politician O O
and O O
industrialist O O
from O O
the O O
U.S. O B-LOC
state O O
of O O
Ohio B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

As O O
the O O
25th O O
Governor O O
of O O
Ohio B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Tod O B-PER
gained O O
recognition O O
for O O
his O O
forceful O O
and O O
energetic O O
leadership O O
during O O
the O O
American B-MISC B-MISC
Civil I-MISC I-MISC
War I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

Jonah B-PER B-PER
Fisher I-PER I-PER
is O O
a O O
correspondent O O
for O O
BBC B-ORG B-ORG
News I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
its O O
first O O
resident O O
correspondent O O
for O O
Myanmar O B-LOC
. O O

From O O
2012 O O
to O O
2014 O O
, O O
Fisher O B-PER
was O O
the O O
BBC B-ORG B-ORG
's O O
correspondent O O
in O O
Bangkok B-LOC B-LOC
where O O
he O O
covered O O
anti O O
- O O
government O O
protesters O O
in O O
Bangkok B-LOC B-LOC
as O O
demonstrators O O
try O O
to O O
unseat O O
the O O
Thai O B-LOC
Prime O O
Minister O O
Yingluck B-PER B-PER
Shinawatra I-PER I-PER
. O O

It O O
is O O
based O O
upon O O
David B-PER B-PER
Lynch I-PER I-PER
's O O
1984 O O
movie O O
" O O
Dune O B-MISC
" O O
, O O
an O O
adaptation O O
of O O
Frank B-PER B-PER
Herbert I-PER I-PER
's O O
science O O
fiction O O
novel O O
of O O
the O O
same O O
name O O
. O O

It O O
addresses O O
the O O
subject O O
of O O
female O O
genital O O
mutilation O O
, O O
a O O
common O O
practice O O
in O O
a O O
number O O
of O O
African O B-LOC
countries O O
, O O
from O O
Egypt B-LOC B-LOC
to O O
Nigeria B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Many O O
Korn B-ORG B-ORG
fans O O
interpret O O
the O O
lyrics O O
to O O
be O O
about O O
frontman O O
Jonathan B-PER B-PER
Davis I-PER I-PER
" O O
getting O O
tired O O
of O O
drinking O O
and O O
drug O O
abuse O O
and O O
his O O
decision O O
to O O
get O O
sober O O
a O O
year O O
prior O O
to O O
" O O
Issues O B-MISC
" O O
coming O O
out O O
. O O

" O O
Guilty O B-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
vocal O O
duet O O
between O O
Barbra B-PER B-PER
Streisand I-PER I-PER
and O O
Barry B-PER B-PER
Gibb I-PER I-PER
. O O

Though O O
Rhodesia B-LOC B-LOC
declared O O
independence O O
in O O
1965 O O
, O O
succeeding O O
political O O
developments O O
and O O
wars O O
changed O O
the O O
status O O
of O O
the O O
country O O
and O O
the O O
National O B-ORG
Assembly O I-ORG
was O O
reformed O O
and O O
has O O
continued O O
since O O
1970 O O
while O O
Zimbabwe B-LOC B-LOC
regained O O
independence O O
in O O
1980 O O
. O O

" O O
Bootie B-MISC B-MISC
Call I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
was O O
first O O
released O O
on O O
31 O O
August O O
1998 O O
by O O
London B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
as O O
All O B-ORG
Saints O I-ORG
" O O
fourth O O
official O O
single O O
. O O

Sugarplum B-ORG B-ORG
Fairy I-ORG I-ORG
is O O
a O O
pop O O
- O O
rock O O
band O O
from O O
Borlänge O B-LOC
, O O
Sweden B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Syrets O B-LOC
( O O
Ukrainian O O
: O O
Сирець O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
Kiev B-ORG B-ORG
Metro I-ORG I-ORG
station O O
on O O
the O O
Syretsko B-LOC B-LOC
- I-LOC I-LOC
Pecherska I-LOC I-LOC
Line I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Jonatan B-PER B-PER
Berg I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
9 O O
May O O
1985 O O
in O O
Torsby B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
former O O
Swedish O B-LOC
footballer O O
. O O

The O O
Social B-ORG B-ORG
Democratic I-ORG I-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
French O O
: O O
" O O
Parti O O
social O O
- O O
démocrate O O
" O O
, O O
PSD O B-ORG
) O O
was O O
a O O
centrist O O
political O O
party O O
in O O
France B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Ter B-LOC B-LOC
Heijde I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
village O O
in O O
the O O
Dutch O B-LOC
province O O
of O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Holland I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Surpassed O O
only O O
by O O
the O O
Phil O B-LOC
G. O I-LOC
McDonald O I-LOC
Bridge O I-LOC
in O O
West B-LOC B-LOC
Virginia I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
the O O
Emlenton B-LOC B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
Pennsylvania B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
it O O
is O O
the O O
third O O
- O O
highest O O
bridge O O
carrying O O
an O O
Interstate O B-LOC
Highway O I-LOC
in O O
the O O
eastern O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
at O O
225 O O
ft O O
tall O O
. O O

Kid B-MISC B-MISC
Galahad I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
1962 O O
American O B-LOC
musical O O
film O O
starring O O
Elvis B-PER B-PER
Presley I-PER I-PER
as O O
a O O
boxer O O
. O O

El B-MISC B-MISC
Lado I-MISC I-MISC
Oscuro I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
en O O
: O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
Dark O I-MISC
Side O I-MISC
" O O
) O O
is O O
the O O
second O O
studio O O
album O O
by O O
power O O
metal O O
band O O
DarkSun B-ORG B-ORG
, O O
released O O
in O O
2004 O O
. O O

Alfred B-PER B-PER
Mechtersheimer I-PER I-PER
is O O
a O O
former O O
Bundestag B-ORG B-ORG
member O O
and O O
Neue O B-ORG
Rechte O I-ORG
politician O O
and O O
author O O
. O O

The O O
film O O
chronicles O O
Trump O B-PER
's O O
life O O
, O O
including O O
his O O
career O O
and O O
his O O
marriages O O
to O O
Ivana B-PER B-PER
Trump I-PER I-PER
and O O
Marla B-PER B-PER
Maples I-PER I-PER
. O O

" O O
Ashtray B-MISC B-MISC
Heart I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
is O O
the O O
third O O
official O O
single O O
from O O
Placebo O B-ORG
's O O
sixth O O
studio O O
album O O
, O O
" O O
Battle B-MISC B-MISC
for I-MISC I-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Sun I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Panther B-LOC B-LOC
Peak I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
mountain O O
located O O
in O O
Essex O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Slow B-MISC B-MISC
Life I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
an O O
EP O O
by O O
the O O
Welsh O B-LOC
alternative O O
rock O O
band O O
Super B-ORG B-ORG
Furry I-ORG I-ORG
Animals I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
released O O
in O O
2004 O O
. O O

The O O
track O O
" O O
Motherfokker O B-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
collaboration O O
between O O
the O O
Super B-ORG B-ORG
Furry I-ORG I-ORG
Animals I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
rap O O
group O O
Goldie B-ORG B-ORG
Lookin I-ORG I-ORG
Chain I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

He O O
is O O
best O O
known O O
for O O
having O O
been O O
stabbed O O
to O O
death O O
by O O
Robert B-PER B-PER
the I-PER I-PER
Bruce I-PER I-PER
before O O
the O O
altar O O
at O O
the O O
church O O
of O O
the O O
Greyfriars O B-LOC
at O O
Dumfries B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Major O O
- O O
General O O
Aye B-PER B-PER
Kyaw I-PER I-PER
was O O
Minister O O
of O O
Information B-MISC O
in O O
Burma B-LOC B-LOC
between O O
June O O
1995 O O
and O O
November O O
1997 O O
. O O

Ladd O B-PER
is O O
the O O
mother O O
of O O
actress O O
Laura B-PER B-PER
Dern I-PER I-PER
, O O
with O O
her O O
ex O O
- O O
husband O O
, O O
actor O O
Bruce B-PER B-PER
Dern I-PER I-PER
. O O

Humber B-LOC B-LOC
was O O
a O O
provincial O O
electoral O O
district O O
( O O
riding O O
) O O
in O O
Ontario O B-LOC
, O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O B-MISC
Evening O I-MISC
Post O I-MISC
was O O
an O O
afternoon O O
metropolitan O O
daily O O
newspaper O O
based O O
in O O
Wellington B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

It O O
was O O
founded O O
in O O
1865 O O
by O O
Dublin O B-LOC
- O O
born O O
printer O O
, O O
newspaper O O
manager O O
and O O
leader O O
- O O
writer O O
Henry B-PER B-PER
Blundell I-PER I-PER
, O O
who O O
brought O O
his O O
large O O
family O O
to O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
1863 O O
. O O

In O O
the O O
W. B-PER B-PER
B. I-PER I-PER
Yeats I-PER I-PER
version O O
, O O
it O O
is O O
subtly O O
suggested O O
that O O
Clytemnestra O B-PER
, O O
although O O
being O O
the O O
daughter O O
of O O
Tyndareus B-PER B-PER
, O O
has O O
somehow O O
been O O
traumatized O O
by O O
what O O
the O O
swan O O
has O O
done O O
to O O
her O O
mother O O
( O O
see O O
below O O
) O O
. O O

Mukherjee O B-PER
was O O
opposed O O
to O O
Rajiv B-PER B-PER
Gandhi I-PER I-PER
being O O
appointed O O
the O O
prime O O
minister O O
of O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

He O O
was O O
the O O
younger O O
brother O O
of O O
Titus B-PER B-PER
and O O
son O O
of O O
Vespasian B-PER B-PER
, O O
his O O
two O O
predecessors O O
on O O
the O O
throne O O
, O O
and O O
the O O
last O O
member O O
of O O
the O O
Flavian O B-ORG
dynasty O I-ORG
. O O

The O O
park O O
consists O O
of O O
70 O O
acre O O
situated O O
along O O
the O O
Sycamore B-LOC B-LOC
Shoals I-LOC I-LOC
of O O
the O O
Watauga B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
a O O
National O B-MISC
Historic O I-MISC
Landmark O I-MISC
where O O
a O O
series O O
of O O
events O O
critical O O
to O O
the O O
establishment O O
of O O
the O O
states O O
of O O
Tennessee B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Kentucky B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
the O O
settlement O O
of O O
the O O
Trans O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
Appalachian O I-LOC
frontier O O
in O O
general O O
, O O
took O O
place O O
. O O

It O O
is O O
directed O O
by O O
Shahzad O B-PER
Kashmiri O I-PER
and O O
Haissam B-PER B-PER
Hussain I-PER I-PER
( O O
directed O O
initial O O
parts O O
) O O
, O O
written O O
by O O
Farhat B-PER B-PER
Ishtiaq I-PER I-PER
and O O
screenplay O O
by O O
Muhammad O O
Wasi O O
- O O
ud O O
- O O
din O O
. O O

Samuel B-PER B-PER
Bigger I-PER I-PER
( O O
March O O
20 O O
, O O
1802 O O
– O O
September O O
9 O O
, O O
1846 O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
seventh O O
Governor O O
of O O
the O O
U.S. O B-LOC
state O O
of O O
Indiana B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
December O O
9 O O
, O O
1840 O O
to O O
December O O
6 O O
, O O
1843 O O
. O O

The O O
Small B-ORG B-ORG
Business I-ORG I-ORG
Administration I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
SBA O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
government O O
agency O O
that O O
provides O O
support O O
to O O
entrepreneurs O O
and O O
small O O
businesses O O
. O O

Family B-MISC B-MISC
Affair I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
sitcom O O
that O O
aired O O
on O O
CBS B-ORG B-ORG
from O O
September O O
12 O O
, O O
1966 O O
to O O
March O O
4 O O
, O O
1971 O O
. O O

Frank B-PER B-PER
Duval I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
November O O
22 O O
, O O
1940 O O
, O O
Berlin B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
German O B-LOC
composer O O
, O O
conductor O O
, O O
record O O
producer O O
, O O
songwriter O O
and O O
singer O O
. O O

As O O
of O O
April O O
2012 O O
, O O
Hashimi O B-PER
is O O
living O O
in O O
Ankara B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Turkey B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
with O O
the O O
assurance O O
that O O
he O O
will O O
not O O
be O O
extradited O O
. O O

The O O
film O O
was O O
an O O
unauthorized O O
adaptation O O
of O O
Robert B-PER B-PER
Louis I-PER I-PER
Stevenson I-PER I-PER
's O O
novel O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Strange I-MISC I-MISC
Case I-MISC I-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Dr. I-MISC I-MISC
Jekyll I-MISC I-MISC
and I-MISC I-MISC
Mr. I-MISC I-MISC
Hyde I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
but O O
the O O
source O O
material O O
went O O
unrecognized O O
by O O
some O O
of O O
the O O
German O B-LOC
media O O
due O O
to O O
changes O O
in O O
the O O
characters O O
" O O
names O O
. O O

McLaughlin O B-PER
served O O
as O O
a O O
director O O
of O O
CBS B-ORG B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG I-ORG
from O O
1979 O O
, O O
becoming O O
chairman O O
of O O
the O O
board O O
in O O
January O O
1999 O O
until O O
the O O
CBS B-ORG B-ORG
merger O O
. O O

Norman B-PER B-PER
Boyd I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
16 O O
October O O
1961 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
former O O
Unionist O B-ORG
politician O O
in O O
Northern B-LOC B-LOC
Ireland I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

In O O
1998 O O
, O O
the O O
Modern B-ORG B-ORG
Library I-ORG I-ORG
ranked O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Moviegoer I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
sixtieth O O
on O O
its O O
list O O
of O O
the O O
hundred O O
best O O
English O B-MISC
- O O
language O O
novels O O
of O O
the O O
twentieth O O
century O O
. O O

There O O
is O O
a O O
border O O
with O O
Dartford B-LOC B-LOC
borough O O
to O O
the O O
east O O
and O O
Sevenoaks B-LOC B-LOC
district O O
to O O
the O O
south O O
- O O
east O O
, O O
both O O
being O O
in O O
the O O
ceremonial O O
county O O
of O O
Kent O B-LOC
. O O

Live B-MISC B-MISC
in I-MISC I-MISC
Berlin I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
title O O
or O O
subtitle O O
of O O
several O O
albums O O
and O O
videos O O
recorded O O
in O O
Berlin B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Germany O B-LOC
by O O
various O O
artists O O
. O O

Surasu O B-PER
was O O
a O O
Malayalam–language O O
playwright O O
and O O
actor O O
from O O
Kerala B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Surasu O B-PER
wrote O O
the O O
script O O
for O O
some O O
Malayalam B-MISC B-MISC
films O O
such O O
as O O
" O O
Randu B-MISC B-MISC
Penkuttikal I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Cranes O B-MISC
live O O
on O O
all O O
continents O O
except O O
Antarctica B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
America I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Lake B-LOC B-LOC
Eyre I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
locality O O
in O O
the O O
Australian O B-LOC
state O O
of O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Australia I-LOC I-LOC
located O O
about O O
718 O O
km O O
north O O
of O O
the O O
state O O
capital O O
of O O
Adelaide B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
134 O O
km O O
north O O
of O O
the O O
town O O
of O O
Marree O B-LOC
and O O
which O O
is O O
associated O O
with O O
the O O
occasional O O
body O O
of O O
water O O
known O O
as O O
Lake B-LOC B-LOC
Eyre I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Pavel B-PER B-PER
Kuka I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
19 O O
July O O
1968 O O
in O O
Prague B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
Czech O B-LOC
former O O
football O O
forward O O
. O O

Sweet B-ORG B-ORG
Savage I-ORG I-ORG
are O O
a O O
heavy O O
metal O O
band O O
from O O
Belfast B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Northern O B-LOC
Ireland O I-LOC
, O O
formed O O
in O O
1979 O O
. O O

Bobby B-PER B-PER
Jack I-PER I-PER
Oliver I-PER I-PER
( O O
January O O
9 O O
, O O
1936 O O
 O O
- O O
 O O
December O O
15 O O
, O O
2012 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
award O O
- O O
winning O O
Canadian B-ORG B-ORG
Football I-ORG I-ORG
League I-ORG I-ORG
defensive O O
tackle O O
. O O

Stewart O B-PER
received O O
his O O
master O O
of O O
science O O
at O O
Stanford B-ORG B-ORG
University I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
his O O
doctor O O
of O O
philosophy O O
from O O
the O O
University B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Toronto I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
1967 O O
. O O

Retroactive O O
to O O
May O O
15 O O
, O O
1918 O O
when O O
the O O
firsts O O
continuously O O
schedule O O
public O O
service O O
airmail O O
route O O
was O O
established O O
between O O
Washington O B-LOC
, O I-LOC
D.C. O I-LOC
and O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
City I-LOC I-LOC
by O O
way O O
of O O
Philadelphia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Albin B-PER B-PER
Kitzinger I-PER I-PER
( O O
1 O O
February O O
1912 O O
in O O
Schweinfurt B-LOC B-LOC
– O O
6 O O
August O O
1970 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
German O B-LOC
football O O
player O O
. O O

Ampato B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
possibly O O
from O O
Quechua O B-MISC
" O O
hamp'atu O O
" O O
or O O
from O O
Aymara O B-MISC
" O O
jamp'atu O O
" O O
both O O
meaning O O
" O O
frog O O
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
dormant O O
6288 O O
m O O
stratovolcano O O
in O O
the O O
Andes B-LOC B-LOC
of O O
southern O O
Peru B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
about O O
100 O O
km O O
( O O
60 O O
mi O O
) O O
northwest O O
of O O
Arequipa B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Peeter B-PER B-PER
Kreitzberg I-PER I-PER
( O O
December O O
14 O O
, O O
1948 O O
– O O
November O O
3 O O
, O O
2011 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
Estonian O B-LOC
politician O O
, O O
member O O
of O O
parliament O O
and O O
a O O
member O O
of O O
the O O
Social B-ORG B-ORG
Democratic I-ORG I-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

The O O
village O O
is O O
named O O
after O O
the O O
Waterloo O B-LOC
in O O
Belgium B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
where O O
Napoleon B-PER B-PER
was O O
defeated O O
. O O

The O O
song O O
was O O
written O O
by O O
Amy O B-PER
Foster O I-PER
- O I-PER
Gillies O I-PER
and O O
David B-PER B-PER
Foster I-PER I-PER
with O O
the O O
latter O O
also O O
serving O O
as O O
the O O
producer O O
along O O
with O O
Humberto B-PER B-PER
Gatica I-PER I-PER
. O O

Ring B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Fire I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
nationally O O
syndicated O O
American O B-LOC
talk O O
radio O O
program O O
hosted O O
by O O
Robert B-PER B-PER
F. I-PER I-PER
Kennedy I-PER I-PER
, O O
Jr. O O
, O O
Mike B-PER B-PER
Papantonio I-PER I-PER
, O O
Sam B-PER B-PER
Seder I-PER I-PER
, O O
and O O
Farron O B-PER
Cousins O I-PER
. O O

The O B-LOC
shire O I-LOC
, O O
administered O O
from O O
the O O
coastal O O
town O O
of O O
Yeppoon B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
covers O O
an O O
area O O
of O O
11776.3 O O
km2 O O
, O O
and O O
existed O O
as O O
a O O
local O O
government O O
entity O O
from O O
1879 O O
until O O
2008 O O
, O O
when O O
it O O
amalgamated O O
with O O
several O O
other O O
councils O O
to O O
become O O
the O O
Rockhampton B-LOC B-LOC
Region I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Wyndham B-PER B-PER
Robertson I-PER I-PER
( O O
January O O
26 O O
, O O
1803February O O
11 O O
, O O
1888 O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
Acting O O
Governor O O
of O O
the O O
U.S. O B-LOC
state O O
of O O
Virginia B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
1836 O O
to O O
1837 O O
. O O

Designed O O
by O O
a O O
team O O
from O O
MIR O O
( O O
c O O
) O O
including O O
Major O O
Millis B-PER B-PER
Jefferis I-PER I-PER
and O O
Stuart B-PER B-PER
Macrae I-PER I-PER
, O O
the O O
grenade O B-MISC
consisted O O
of O O
a O O
glass O O
sphere O O
containing O O
an O O
explosive O O
made O O
of O O
nitroglycerin O O
and O O
additives O O
( O O
this O O
added O O
stability O O
to O O
the O O
mix O O
, O O
as O O
well O O
as O O
giving O O
it O O
its O O
squash O O
- O O
head O O
- O O
like O O
effect O O
) O O
covered O O
in O O
a O O
strong O O
adhesive O O
and O O
surrounded O O
by O O
a O O
sheet O O
- O O
metal O O
casing O O
. O O

Obliteration B-MISC B-MISC
Pie I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
an O O
album O O
by O O
Robyn B-PER B-PER
Hitchcock I-PER I-PER
, O O
released O O
in O O
Japan O B-LOC
in O O
2005 O O
. O O

Adolph B-PER B-PER
Albrecht I-PER I-PER
Erlenmeyer I-PER I-PER
( O O
11 O O
July O O
1822 O O
– O O
9 O O
August O O
1877 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
German O B-LOC
physician O O
and O O
psychiatrist O O
born O O
in O O
Wiesbaden B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

They O O
came O O
together O O
when O O
Galea O B-PER
created O O
a O O
dub O O
remix O O
of O O
Gorillaz B-ORG B-ORG
's O O
" O O
Tomorrow B-MISC B-MISC
Comes I-MISC I-MISC
Today I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
" O O
Tomorrow O B-MISC
Dub O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
which O O
was O O
released O O
as O O
a O O
B O O
- O O
side O O
on O O
the O O
" O O
Tomorrow B-MISC B-MISC
Comes I-MISC I-MISC
Today I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
single O O
) O O
, O O
which O O
Gorillaz B-ORG B-ORG
founder O O
Damon B-PER B-PER
Albarn I-PER I-PER
liked O O
so O O
much O O
that O O
he O O
asked O O
Galea O B-PER
to O O
remix O O
the O O
whole O O
album O O
" O O
Gorillaz B-ORG B-ORG
" O O
. O O

Hans B-PER B-PER
Engen I-PER I-PER
( O O
22 O O
August O O
1912 O O
– O O
6 O O
April O O
1966 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Norwegian O B-LOC
journalist O O
, O O
diplomat O O
and O O
politician O O
for O O
the O O
Labour B-ORG B-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Besides O O
this O O
, O O
the O O
Mambo O B-ORG
All O I-ORG
- O I-ORG
Stars O I-ORG
are O O
a O O
high O O
energy O O
dance O O
band O O
composed O O
of O O
top O O
studio O O
sidemen O O
from O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
City I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Los B-LOC B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

In O O
the O O
1930s O O
and O O
early O O
1940s O O
, O O
he O O
worked O O
with O O
New B-ORG B-ORG
Theatres I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
who O O
made O O
bilingual O O
movies O O
: O O
in O O
both O O
Bengali O B-MISC
and O O
Hindi B-MISC B-MISC
. O O
