The O O
" O O
dong O O
" O O
originates O O
from O O
a O O
pavilion O O
with O O
the O O
same O O
name O O
founded O O
by O O
Han B-PER B-PER
Myung I-PER I-PER
- I-PER I-PER
hoi I-PER I-PER
, O O
a O O
high O O
- O O
ranking O O
government O O
official O O
during O O
the O O
Joseon B-LOC B-ORG
dynasty O I-ORG
. O O

Islam O B-ORG
is O O
the O O
largest O O
religion O O
in O O
Sudan B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
Muslims O B-ORG
have O O
dominated O O
national O O
government O O
institutions O O
since O O
independence O O
in O O
1956 O O
. O O

Moses B-PER B-PER
French I-PER I-PER
Colby I-PER I-PER
( O O
July O O
2 O O
, O O
1795 O O
– O O
May O O
4 O O
, O O
1863 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
doctor O O
and O O
politician O O
in O O
Canada B-ORG B-LOC
East I-ORG I-LOC
. O O

Ernie B-PER B-MISC
Pike I-PER I-MISC
is O O
a O O
comics O O
series O O
written O O
by O O
Héctor O B-PER
Germán O I-PER
Oesterheld O I-PER
and O O
originally O O
drawn O O
by O O
Hugo B-PER B-PER
Pratt I-PER I-PER
, O O
starring O O
a O O
World O B-MISC
War O I-MISC
II O I-MISC
and O O
Korean B-MISC B-MISC
War I-MISC I-MISC
reporter O O
. O O

David O B-PER
Jefferson O I-PER
" O I-PER
Davy O I-PER
" O I-PER
Jones O I-PER
( O O
June O O
30 O O
, O O
1880 O O
– O O
March O O
30 O O
, O O
1972 O O
) O O
, O O
nicknamed O O
" O O
Kangaroo O B-PER
" O O
, O O
was O O
an O O
outfielder O O
in O O
Major B-ORG B-ORG
League I-ORG I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Also O O
, O O
he O O
played O O
part O O
of O O
one O O
year O O
with O O
the O O
Chicago B-ORG B-ORG
White I-ORG I-ORG
Sox I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
where O O
several O O
of O O
his O O
teammates O O
would O O
later O O
be O O
implicated O O
in O O
the O O
1919 O O
Black B-MISC B-ORG
Sox O I-ORG
scandal O O
. O O

Jones O B-PER
was O O
immortalized O O
in O O
the O O
classic O O
baseball O O
book O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Glory I-MISC I-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Their I-MISC I-MISC
Times I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
by O O
Lawrence O B-PER
Ritter O I-PER
. O O

He O O
is O O
alleged O O
to O O
have O O
been O O
the O O
ringleader O O
of O O
a O O
cell O O
tasked O O
with O O
killing O O
Lars B-PER B-PER
Vilks I-PER I-PER
, O O
a O O
Swedish O B-LOC
artist O O
, O O
some O O
Muslims O B-ORG
accused O O
of O O
blasphemy O O
. O O

François O B-PER
Duvalier O I-PER
( O O
] O O
; O O
14 O O
April O O
190721 O O
April O O
1971 O O
) O O
, O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
PapaDoc O B-PER
, O O
was O O
the O O
President O O
of O O
Haiti B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
1957 O O
to O O
1971 O O
. O O

Tikchik O B-LOC
Lake O I-LOC
empties O O
into O O
the O O
Nuyakuk B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
a O O
tributary O O
of O O
the O O
Nushagak B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
which O O
flows O O
to O O
Nushagak O B-LOC
Bay O I-LOC
, O O
an O O
arm O O
of O O
Bristol B-LOC B-LOC
Bay O I-LOC
. O O

Acosta O B-PER
was O O
also O O
accused O O
of O O
143–500 O O
disappearances O O
during O O
Mexico B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
" O O
Dirty O B-MISC
War O I-MISC
" O O
in O O
the O O
1970s O O
. O O

The O O
Great B-LOC B-LOC
Hall I-LOC I-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
the I-LOC I-LOC
People I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
state O O
building O O
located O O
at O O
the O O
western O O
edge O O
of O O
Tiananmen O B-LOC
Square O I-LOC
in O O
Beijing O B-LOC
. O O

became O O
the O O
manifesto O O
of O O
the O O
Revolution O B-MISC
, O O
helping O O
to O O
transform O O
the O O
Estates O B-MISC
- O I-MISC
General O I-MISC
into O O
the O O
National B-ORG B-ORG
Assembly I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
June O O
1789 O O
. O O

Dangerous O O
criminal O O
Richard B-MISC B-PER
B. O I-PER
Riddick O I-PER
( O O
Vin B-PER B-PER
Diesel I-PER I-PER
) O O
is O O
being O O
transported O O
to O O
prison O O
in O O
a O O
spacecraft O O
. O O

The O O
Court O B-ORG
of O I-ORG
Justice O I-ORG
of O O
the O O
European O B-LOC
Free O I-LOC
Trade O I-LOC
Association O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
( O O
more O O
commonly O O
known O O
as O O
the O O
EFTA O B-ORG
Court O I-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
supranational O O
judicial O O
body O O
responsible O O
for O O
the O O
three O O
EFTA O B-ORG
members O O
who O O
are O O
also O O
members O O
of O O
the O O
European O B-ORG
Economic O I-ORG
Area O I-ORG
( O O
EEA O B-ORG
) O O
: O O
Iceland B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Liechtenstein B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Norway B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

List O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
Mountains O I-MISC
in O I-MISC
South B-LOC I-MISC
Africa I-LOC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
general O O
list O O
of O O
mountains O O
in O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Africa I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
with O O
elevation O O
. O O

Michael B-PER B-PER
Meeropol I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
Michael B-MISC B-PER
Rosenberg O I-PER
on O O
March O O
10 O O
, O O
1943 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
retired O O
professor O O
of O O
economics O O
. O O

The O O
game O O
was O O
released O O
in O O
January O O
2016 O O
for O O
Microsoft B-MISC B-MISC
Windows I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
OS B-MISC B-MISC
X I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
iOS O B-MISC
, O O
and O O
Android O B-MISC
, O O
following O O
a O O
Twitch O B-MISC
Plays O O
" O O
Pokémon O O
" O O
 O O
- O O
style O O
event O O
on O O
Twitch O B-MISC
. O O

A O O
Nintendo B-MISC B-MISC
3DS I-MISC I-MISC
port O O
of O O
the O O
game O O
was O O
announced O O
in O O
a O O
September O O
2016 O O
Nintendo B-ORG B-MISC
Direct O I-MISC
for O O
release O O
in O O
January O O
2017 O O
after O O
some O O
delays O O
. O O

One O O
of O O
the O O
senior O O
- O O
most O O
offices O O
in O O
the O O
Union O B-ORG
Cabinet O I-ORG
, O O
the O O
chief O O
responsibility O O
of O O
the O O
Home O B-MISC
Minister O I-MISC
is O O
the O O
maintenance O O
of O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
internal O O
security O O
; O O
the O O
country O O
's O O
large O O
police O O
force O O
comes O O
under O O
his O O
ambit O O
. O O

Health O B-ORG
Consumer O I-ORG
Powerhouse O I-ORG
is O O
a O O
Swedish O B-LOC
health O O
policy O O
think O O
tank O O
which O O
specialises O O
in O O
comparing O O
healthcare O O
systems O O
throughout O O
Europe B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Washington O B-LOC
metro O O
area O O
is O O
also O O
home O O
to O O
several O O
major O O
sports O O
venues O O
including O O
Capital B-ORG B-LOC
One I-ORG I-LOC
Arena O I-LOC
, O O
RFK O B-LOC
Stadium O I-LOC
, O O
FedExField B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
Nationals B-LOC B-LOC
Park I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Released O O
on O O
May O O
27 O O
, O O
1976 O O
, O O
the O O
disc O O
is O O
the O O
soundtrack O O
album O O
for O O
the O O
1976 O O
Warner O B-ORG
Bros. O I-ORG
motion O O
picture O O
" O O
Sparkle O B-MISC
" O O
, O O
starring O O
Irene B-PER B-PER
Cara I-PER I-PER
. O O

Johann O B-PER
Heinrich O I-PER
Rudolf O I-PER
Schenck O I-PER
( O O
31 O O
January O O
1860 O O
– O O
25 O O
June O O
1927 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
German O B-LOC
botanist O O
who O O
was O O
a O O
native O O
of O O
Siegen B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Joseph O B-PER
Matthäus O I-PER
Aigner O I-PER
( O O
18 O O
January O O
1818 O O
, O O
Vienna19 O B-LOC
February O O
1886 O O
, O O
Vienna O B-LOC
) O O
was O O
an O O
Austrian O B-LOC
portrait O O
painter O O
, O O
who O O
studied O O
under O O
Friedrich B-PER B-PER
von I-PER I-PER
Amerling I-PER I-PER
and O O
Carl B-PER B-PER
Rahl I-PER I-PER
. O O

From O O
1849 O O
to O O
1923 O O
, O O
half O O
a O O
million O O
Indian O B-LOC
indentured O O
labourers O O
passed O O
through O O
the O O
Immigration O B-LOC
Depot O I-LOC
, O O
to O O
be O O
transported O O
to O O
plantations O O
throughout O O
the O O
British B-LOC B-LOC
Empire I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

" O O
Homer B-PER B-MISC
to O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Max O I-MISC
" O I-MISC
is O O
the O O
thirteenth O O
episode O O
of O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Simpsons I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
" O O
tenth O O
season O O
. O O

The O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Point I-LOC I-LOC
Local O I-LOC
School O I-LOC
District O I-LOC
is O O
a O O
local O O
school O O
district O O
serving O O
the O O
village O O
of O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Point I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
nearby O O
areas O O
at O O
the O O
southern O O
point O O
of O O
Lawrence O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
the O O
most O O
southerly O O
county O O
in O O
the O B-LOC
U.S. O I-LOC
state O I-LOC
of O O
Ohio B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

November O O
6 O O
] O O
1900 O O
– O O
December O O
3 O O
, O O
1976 O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
Chief O O
marshal O O
of O O
the O O
aviation O O
for O O
the O O
Soviet O B-ORG
Air O I-ORG
Force O I-ORG
during O O
Russia B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
involvement O O
in O O
the O O
Second O B-MISC
World O I-MISC
War O I-MISC
. O O

Actus B-ORG B-ORG
Tragicus I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
sometimes O O
credited O O
as O O
Actus O B-ORG
Comics O I-ORG
or O O
simply O O
Actus O B-ORG
, O O
is O O
a O O
group O O
of O O
five O O
Israeli O B-LOC
comics O O
artists O O
founded O O
in O O
1995 O O
by O O
Rutu B-PER B-PER
Modan I-PER I-PER
and O O
Yirmi O B-PER
Pinkus O I-PER
. O O

Sephardi B-MISC B-ORG
Jews I-MISC I-ORG
fleeing O O
persecution O O
immigrated O O
with O O
explorers O O
and O O
colonists O O
to O O
settle O O
in O O
what O O
is O O
now O O
Argentina B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Samantha B-MISC B-PER
Jane O I-PER
Sacramento O I-PER
is O O
a O O
Gibraltar B-LOC B-LOC
politician O O
. O O

The O O
BBC B-ORG B-ORG
, O O
in O O
a O O
review O O
of O O
Köner O B-PER
's O O
work O O
in O O
1997 O O
, O O
calls O O
him O O
a O O
" O O
media O O
artist O O
, O O
" O O
one O O
who O O
works O O
between O O
installation O O
, O O
sound O O
art O O
, O O
ambient O O
music O O
and O O
as O O
one O O
half O O
of O O
Porter O B-ORG
Ricks O I-ORG
dub O O
techno O O
. O O

The O O
channel O O
caters O O
to O O
audiences O O
in O O
the O O
Asia O B-LOC
Pacific O I-LOC
region O I-LOC
and O O
has O O
shows O O
that O O
are O O
hosted O O
in O O
English O B-MISC
and O O
Hindi B-MISC B-MISC
. O O

Strand O B-LOC
Street O I-LOC
is O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
main O O
streets O O
in O O
the O O
central O O
business O O
district O O
of O O
Cape B-LOC B-LOC
Town I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
South O B-LOC
Africa O I-LOC
. O O

William O B-PER
Quintillis O I-PER
Dallmeyer O I-PER
( O O
October O O
23 O O
, O O
1829 O O
– O O
March O O
15 O O
, O O
1908 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
Missouri B-LOC B-LOC
politician O O
. O O

Upon O O
its O O
release O O
, O O
it O O
immediately O O
rose O O
to O O
the O O
# O O
1 O O
position O O
on O O
the O O
" O O
New B-LOC B-MISC
York I-LOC I-MISC
Times O I-MISC
" O O
hardcover O O
fiction O O
bestseller O O
list O O
, O O
making O O
it O O
the O O
second O O
" O O
Wheel B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Time I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
book O O
to O O
reach O O
the O O
# O O
1 O O
position O O
on O O
that O O
list O O
. O O

British O B-LOC
composer O O
and O O
multi O O
- O O
instrumentalist O O
Daniel B-PER B-PER
O'Sullivan I-PER I-PER
joined O O
the O O
collective O O
in O O
2009 O O
, O O
and O O
the O O
band O O
performed O O
some O O
of O O
their O O
first O O
live O O
concerts O O
in O O
their O O
15 O O
- O O
year O O
lifespan O O
, O O
including O O
the O O
prestigious O O
Norwegian O B-LOC
National O I-LOC
Opera O I-LOC
. O O

Under O O
General O O
Grant O B-PER
he O O
fought O O
in O O
the O O
Battle B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Shiloh I-MISC I-MISC
and O O
the O O
Battle O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
Vicksburg O I-MISC
. O O

Seppo B-PER B-PER
Sanaksenaho I-PER I-PER
( O O
May O O
5 O O
, O O
1938 O O
– O O
November O O
1 O O
, O O
2011 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Finnish O B-LOC
politician O O
who O O
served O O
as O O
the O O
Mayor O O
of O O
Vaasa O B-LOC
from O O
1997 O O
to O O
2001 O O
. O O

As O O
a O O
Prime B-PER O
Minister I-PER O
of O O
Serbia B-LOC B-LOC
he O O
was O O
a O O
hardcore O O
bureaucrat O O
, O O
under O O
whom O O
more O O
than O O
half O O
of O O
Serbian O B-LOC
economy O O
was O O
under O O
state O O
ownership O O
. O O

The O O
Legislative B-ORG B-ORG
Assembly I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Lower I-ORG I-ORG
Canada I-ORG I-ORG
was O O
the O O
lower O O
house O O
of O O
the O O
bicameral O O
structure O O
of O O
provincial O O
government O O
in O O
Lower B-LOC B-ORG
Canada I-LOC I-ORG
until O O
1838 O O
. O O

He O O
occupied O O
some O O
of O O
Venezuela B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
top O O
ambassadorial O O
posts O O
, O O
including O O
Washington O B-LOC
, O O
London B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Madrid B-MISC B-LOC
and O O
Brasilia O B-LOC
. O O

Cambridge O B-ORG
University O I-ORG
scholar O O
Geoffrey O B-PER
Hawthorn O I-PER
wrote O O
: O O
" O O
Alfredo B-PER B-PER
Toro I-PER I-PER
Hardy I-PER I-PER
has O O
a O O
rare O O
and O O
distinctive O O
voice O O
. O O

Kamboji O B-MISC
is O O
an O O
Indian O B-LOC
Malayalam–language O O
musical O O
thriller O O
film O O
written O O
and O O
directed O O
by O O
Vinod B-PER B-PER
Mankara I-PER I-PER
. O O

It O O
lies O O
between O O
Glenwood O B-LOC
and O O
Norman O B-LOC
on O O
the O O
Caddo B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
Maha B-MISC B-MISC
Yazawin I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
fully O O
the O O
Maha O B-MISC
Yazawindawgyi O I-MISC
( O O
Burmese O B-LOC
: O O
မဟာ O O
ရာဇဝင်တော်ကြီး O O
, O O
] O O
) O O
and O O
formerly O O
romanized O O
as O O
the O O
Maha O O
- O O
Radza O O
Weng O O
, O O
is O O
the O O
first O O
national O O
chronicle O O
of O O
Burma/Myanmar O O
. O O

Completed O O
in O O
1724 O O
by O O
U B-PER B-PER
Kala I-PER I-PER
, O O
a O O
historian O O
at O O
the O O
Toungoo O B-LOC
court O O
, O O
it O O
was O O
the O O
first O O
chronicle O O
to O O
synthesize O O
all O O
the O O
ancient O O
, O O
regional O O
, O O
foreign O O
and O O
biographic O O
histories O O
related O O
to O O
Burmese O B-LOC
history O O
. O O

Falck O B-ORG
Group O I-ORG
is O O
an O O
Italian O B-LOC
company O O
located O O
in O O
Sesto B-LOC B-LOC
San I-LOC I-LOC
Giovanni I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

John O B-PER
Harvey O I-PER
Tolan O I-PER
( O O
; O O
January O O
15 O O
, O O
1877 O O
– O O
June O O
30 O O
, O O
1947 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
U.S. O B-LOC
Representative O O
from O O
California B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Stanford B-PER B-PER
White I-PER I-PER
( O O
November O O
9 O O
, O O
1853 O O
– O O
June O O
25 O O
, O O
1906 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
architect O O
and O O
partner O O
in O O
the O O
architectural O O
firm O O
McKim B-MISC O
, I-MISC O
Mead I-MISC O
& I-MISC O
White I-MISC O
, O O
the O O
frontrunner O O
among O O
Beaux O O
- O O
Arts O O
firms O O
. O O

The O O
Interim B-LOC B-ORG
Government I-LOC I-ORG
of I-LOC I-ORG
Iran I-LOC I-ORG
( O O
Persian O B-ORG
: O O
دولت O O
موقت O O
ايران‎ O O
‎ O O
, O O
" O O
Dowlat O O
- O O
e O O
Movaghat O O
- O O
e O O
Irân O O
" O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
first O O
government O O
established O O
in O O
Iran B-LOC B-LOC
after O O
the O O
Iranian O B-MISC
Revolution O I-MISC
, O O
and O O
the O O
first O O
republic O O
established O O
in O O
Iran B-LOC B-LOC
after O O
2,500 O O
years O O
of O O
Imperial O O
dynasties O O
. O O

The O O
Club O B-ORG
of O I-ORG
Four O I-ORG
was O O
an O O
alliance O O
of O O
four O O
European O B-LOC
truck O O
manufacturers O O
: O O
Saviem B-ORG B-ORG
, O O
Volvo B-ORG B-ORG
, O O
DAF O B-ORG
, O O
and O O
Magirus O B-ORG
- O I-ORG
Deutz O I-ORG
. O O

R B-PER B-PER
Adams I-PER I-PER
Cowley I-PER I-PER
( O O
July O O
25 O O
, O O
1917 O O
– O O
October O O
27 O O
, O O
1991 O O
) O O
, O O
the O O
" O O
Father O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
Trauma O I-MISC
Medicine O I-MISC
, O O
" O O
was O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
surgeon O O
considered O O
a O O
pioneer O O
in O O
emergency O O
medicine O O
and O O
the O O
treatment O O
of O O
shock O O
trauma O O
. O O

Wikimedia O B-ORG
Indonesia B-LOC I-ORG
believes O O
that O O
Javanese B-MISC B-MISC
Wikipedia I-MISC I-MISC
has O O
an O O
untapped O O
potential O O
growth O O
and O O
an O O
untapped O O
potential O O
editor O O
base O O
that O O
needs O O
to O O
be O O
reached O O
. O O

It O O
is O O
compatible O O
with O O
Windows O B-MISC
, O O
macOS O B-MISC
and O O
Linux B-MISC B-MISC
. O O

Kim O B-PER
Gi O I-PER
- O I-PER
Dong O I-PER
( O O
; O O
born O O
12 O O
January O O
1972 O O
in O O
Dangjin B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
former O O
South O B-LOC
Korean O I-LOC
footballer O O
. O O

Once O O
completed O O
it O O
will O O
become O O
the O O
tallest O O
building O O
in O O
Edmonton B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
tallest O O
in O O
Canada O B-LOC
outside O O
Toronto O B-LOC
. O O

" O O
Mexico B-LOC B-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
single O O
released O O
in O O
May O O
1970 O O
by O O
the O O
San B-LOC B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC I-LOC
rock O O
band O O
Jefferson B-ORG B-ORG
Airplane I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
produced O O
by O O
the O O
band O O
at O O
Pacific O B-ORG
High O I-ORG
Recording O I-ORG
Studios O I-ORG
with O O
Phill O B-PER
Sawyer O I-PER
as O O
the O O
recording O O
engineer O O
. O O

Written O O
and O O
sung O O
by O O
Grace B-PER B-PER
Slick I-PER I-PER
, O O
it O O
is O O
a O O
tuneful O O
rant O O
against O O
then O O
- O O
President O O
Richard B-PER B-PER
Nixon I-PER I-PER
and O O
his O O
anti O O
- O O
drug O O
initiative O O
, O O
Operation O B-MISC
Intercept O I-MISC
, O O
that O O
he O O
had O O
implemented O O
to O O
curtail O O
the O O
flow O O
of O O
marijuana O O
into O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
from O O
Mexico B-LOC B-MISC
. O O

She O O
first O O
published O O
her O O
works O O
( O O
including O O
her O O
best O O
known O O
novel O O
, O O
" O O
Jane B-MISC B-MISC
Eyre I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
) O O
under O O
the O O
pen O O
name O O
Currer O B-PER
Bell O B-PER
. O O

In O O
May O O
2004 O O
he O O
won O O
the O O
Short O B-MISC
Film O I-MISC
Jury O I-MISC
Prize O I-MISC
at O O
the O O
Cannes B-MISC B-MISC
Film I-MISC I-MISC
Festival I-MISC I-MISC
with O O
his O O
animated O O
short O O
" O O
Flatlife O B-MISC
" O O
( O O
11 O O
min O O
) O O
. O O

Ralph B-PER B-PER
Bass I-PER I-PER
( O O
1 O O
May O O
1911 O O
– O O
5 O O
March O O
1997 O O
) O O
, O O
born O O
Ralph O B-PER
Basso O I-PER
, O I-PER
Jr. O I-PER
, O O
was O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
rhythm O O
- O O
and O O
- O O
blues O O
record O O
producer O O
and O O
talent O O
scout O O
for O O
several O O
independent O O
labels O O
. O O

NGSCB O B-MISC
was O O
the O O
result O O
of O O
years O O
of O O
research O O
and O O
development O O
within O O
Microsoft B-ORG B-ORG
to O O
create O O
a O O
secure O O
computing O O
solution O O
that O O
equaled O O
the O O
security O O
of O O
closed O O
architecture O O
platforms O O
, O O
such O O
as O O
set O O
- O O
top O O
boxes O O
, O O
while O O
simultaneously O O
preserving O O
the O O
backward O O
compatibility O O
, O O
openness O O
, O O
and O O
flexibility O O
of O O
the O O
Windows O B-MISC
operating O O
system O O
. O O

Seventh O B-ORG
- O I-ORG
day O I-ORG
Adventists O I-ORG
believe O O
that O O
Ellen B-PER B-PER
G. I-PER I-PER
White I-PER I-PER
, O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
church O O
's O O
co O O
- O O
founders O O
, O O
was O O
a O O
prophet O O
, O O
understood O O
today O O
as O O
an O O
expression O O
of O O
the O O
New O B-MISC
Testament O I-MISC
spiritual O O
gift O O
of O O
prophecy O O
. O O

West O B-LOC
Cornwall O I-LOC
is O O
a O O
name O O
used O O
to O O
refer O O
to O O
the O O
westernmost O O
part O O
of O O
Cornwall O B-LOC
in O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
Kingdom I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

It O O
is O O
also O O
used O O
by O O
Cornwall B-ORG B-ORG
Council I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
Cornwall O B-ORG
Housing O I-ORG
as O O
part O O
of O O
their O O
resource O O
allocation O O
and O O
area O O
management O O
plans O O
, O O
in O O
which O O
Cornwall O B-LOC
is O O
divided O O
into O O
three O O
sections O O
, O O
west O O
, O O
central O O
and O O
east O O
. O O

Club O B-ORG
Sport O I-ORG
Emelec O I-ORG
is O O
an O O
Ecuadorian O B-LOC
sports O O
club O O
based O O
in O O
Guayaquil B-LOC B-LOC
that O O
is O O
best O O
known O O
for O O
their O O
professional O O
football O O
team O O
. O O

The O O
second O O
single O O
" O O
Carbon B-MISC B-MISC
Monoxide I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
garnered O O
some O O
airplay O O
but O O
failed O O
to O O
crack O O
the O O
Modern B-MISC B-MISC
Rock I-MISC I-MISC
Tracks O I-MISC
top O O
40 O O
. O O

The O O
President O O
of O O
Harvard B-ORG B-ORG
University I-ORG I-ORG
is O O
the O O
chief O O
administrator O O
of O O
the O O
university O O
and O O
the O O
" O O
ex O O
officio O O
" O O
chairman O O
of O O
the O O
Harvard O B-ORG
Corporation B-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Located O O
in O O
the O O
northeastern O O
corner O O
of O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
Jersey I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
its O O
Gateway O B-LOC
Region O I-LOC
, O O
Bergen B-LOC B-LOC
County O I-LOC
is O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
City I-LOC I-LOC
Metropolitan B-ORG I-LOC
Area O I-LOC
and O O
is O O
directly O O
across O O
the O O
George B-LOC B-LOC
Washington I-LOC I-LOC
Bridge I-LOC I-LOC
from O O
Manhattan B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Jeli B-LOC B-LOC
is O O
administered O O
by O O
the O O
Jeli B-LOC B-ORG
District O I-ORG
Council O I-ORG
. O O

Hypsipyla B-MISC B-MISC
robusta I-MISC O
, O O
the O O
cedar O O
tip O O
moth O O
, O O
is O O
a O O
species O O
of O O
snout O O
moth O O
in O O
the O O
genus O O
" O O
Hypsipyla B-MISC B-MISC
" O O
. O O

Rebecca O B-PER
Louisa O I-PER
Ferguson O I-PER
Sundström O I-PER
( O O
born O O
19 O O
October O O
1983 O O
) O O
, O O
known O O
professionally O O
as O O
Rebecca B-PER B-PER
Ferguson I-PER I-PER
, O O
is O O
a O O
Swedish O B-LOC
actress O O
. O O

nat. O O
, O O
born O O
14 O O
April O O
1954 O O
, O O
Meißen O B-LOC
, O O
Germany B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
German O B-LOC
scientist O O
and O O
university O O
professor O O
of O O
computer O O
sciences O O
. O O

The O O
Verziere O B-LOC
( O O
old O O
- O O
fashioned O O
Italian O B-MISC
word O O
for O O
" O O
greengrocery O O
market O O
" O O
; O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
Verzee O B-LOC
, O O
in O O
Milanese O B-LOC
) O O
was O O
the O O
traditional O O
greengrocery O O
street O O
market O O
of O O
Milan B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Italy B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

" O O
Someday O B-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
song O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
singer O O
and O O
songwriter O O
Mariah B-PER B-PER
Carey I-PER I-PER
from O O
her O O
self O O
- O O
titled O O
debut O O
studio O O
album O O
( O O
1990 O O
) O O
. O O

Prior O O
to O O
Carey O B-PER
signing O O
a O O
record O O
contract O O
, O O
she O O
and O O
producer O O
Ben B-PER B-PER
Margulies I-PER I-PER
had O O
written O O
and O O
produced O O
a O O
four O O
- O O
track O O
demo O O
which O O
included O O
" O O
Someday O B-MISC
" O O
. O O

The O O
Center O B-ORG
for O I-ORG
Free B-MISC I-ORG
Enterprise I-MISC I-ORG
( O O
in O O
Korean O B-MISC
자유기업원 O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
neocon O O
think O O
- O O
tank O O
based O O
in O O
Seoul B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Korea I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

He O O
graduated O O
from O O
Balliol O B-ORG
College O I-ORG
at O O
the O O
University B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Oxford I-ORG I-ORG
with O O
a O O
first O O
- O O
class O O
honours O O
in O O
English O B-MISC
literature O O
. O O

According O O
to O O
the O O
Article O O
1 O O
of O O
the O O
Law O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
Ukraine B-LOC I-MISC
on O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
State O I-MISC
Border O I-MISC
it O O
is O O
a O O
line O O
and O O
a O O
vertical O O
surface O O
that O O
stretches O O
along O O
that O O
line O O
, O O
which O O
define O O
the O O
boundary O O
of O O
territory O O
of O O
Ukraine B-LOC B-LOC
over O O
the O O
land O O
, O O
water O O
, O O
and O O
air O O
space O O
. O O

Starting O O
as O O
a O O
17 O O
- O O
year O O
- O O
old O O
appearing O O
at O O
the O O
2000 B-MISC B-MISC
Summer I-MISC I-MISC
Olympics I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
Nasution O B-PER
is O O
considered O O
one O O
of O O
Indonesia O B-LOC
's O O
top O O
- O O
ranked O O
swimmers O O
in O O
his O O
decade O O
. O O

At O O
the O O
peak O O
of O O
his O O
sporting O O
career O O
, O O
Nasurion O B-PER
has O O
also O O
travelled O O
extensively O O
across O O
Asia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
the O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
to O O
train O O
for O O
world O O
- O O
class O O
swim O O
clubs O O
, O O
and O O
to O O
further O O
focus O O
on O O
his O O
education O O
, O O
including O O
his O O
four O O
- O O
year O O
stay O O
at O O
Chaffey B-ORG B-ORG
College I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
Rancho B-LOC B-LOC
Cucamonga I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
California I-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Paul B-PER B-PER
Ardenne I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
4 O O
October O O
1956 O O
) O O
is O O
Professor O O
of O O
history O O
at O O
the O O
University O B-ORG
of O I-ORG
Amiens B-LOC I-ORG
, O O
and O O
is O O
also O O
an O O
art O O
critic O O
and O O
a O O
curator O O
in O O
the O O
field O O
of O O
contemporary O O
art O O
. O O

The O O
Thomas B-LOC B-LOC
Viaduct I-LOC I-LOC
spans O O
the O O
Patapsco B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Patapsco O B-LOC
Valley O I-LOC
between O O
Relay O B-LOC
, O O
Maryland B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Elkridge B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Maryland I-LOC B-LOC
, O O
USA O B-LOC
. O O

Edwards O B-PER
was O O
selected O O
by O O
the O O
Miami B-ORG B-ORG
Heat I-ORG I-ORG
with O O
the O O
20th O O
overall O O
pick O O
of O O
the O O
1988 O O
NBA O B-ORG
draft O O
. O O

EBA O B-ORG
Clearing O I-ORG
is O O
a O O
provider O O
of O O
pan O O
- O O
European O B-LOC
payment O O
infrastructure O O
with O O
headquarters O O
in O O
Paris B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Thorvaldsen O B-PER
was O O
born O O
in O O
Copenhagen B-LOC B-LOC
into O O
a O O
Danish/Icelandic O O
family O O
of O O
humble O O
means O O
, O O
and O O
was O O
accepted O O
to O O
the O O
Royal O B-ORG
Danish O I-ORG
Academy O I-ORG
of O I-ORG
Art O I-ORG
when O O
he O O
was O O
eleven O O
years O O
old O O
. O O

Emanoil B-PER B-PER
Bacaloglu I-PER I-PER
( O O
] O O
; O O
11 O O
April O O
1830 O O
– O O
30 O O
August O O
1891 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Wallachian O B-LOC
and O O
Romanian O B-LOC
mathematician O O
, O O
physicist O O
and O O
chemist O O
and O O
a O O
scubadiver O O
, O O
medic O O
, O O
shoe O O
salesman O O
, O O
a O O
vegetarian O O
, O O
policeman O O
and O O
fireman O O
. O O

Humphrey B-PER B-PER
the I-PER I-PER
Bear I-PER I-PER
is O O
a O O
cartoon O O
character O O
created O O
by O O
the O O
Walt B-PER B-ORG
Disney I-PER I-ORG
studio O O
in O O
1950 O O
. O O

When O O
the O O
shorts O O
division O O
closed O O
, O O
Humphrey O B-PER
was O O
the O O
last O O
of O O
only O O
seven O O
Disney O B-ORG
characters O O
who O O
had O O
been O O
given O O
a O O
series O O
of O O
their O O
own O O
, O O
starring O O
in O O
cartoons O O
who O O
opened O O
with O O
their O O
own O O
logo O O
( O O
the O O
six O O
others O O
were O O
Mickey B-PER B-PER
Mouse I-PER I-PER
, O O
Donald B-PER B-PER
Duck I-PER I-PER
, O O
Goofy B-PER B-PER
, O O
Pluto B-MISC B-PER
, O O
Chip B-PER O
" I-PER O
n I-PER O
" I-PER O
Dale I-PER O
( O O
counting O O
as O O
one O O
) O O
, O O
and O O
Figaro O B-PER
) O O
. O O

Franklin O B-PER
Harper O I-PER
Elmore B-MISC I-PER
( O O
October O O
15 O O
, O O
1799May O O
29 O O
, O O
1850 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
Representative O O
and O O
Senator O O
. O O

Echoes O B-MISC
is O O
the O O
fifth O O
studio O O
album O O
by O O
English O B-LOC
recording O O
artist O O
Will B-PER B-PER
Young I-PER I-PER
. O O

It O O
was O O
released O O
by O O
RCA B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
Sony B-ORG B-ORG
Music O I-ORG
on O O
19 O O
August O O
2011 O O
. O O

A O O
departure O O
from O O
previous O O
albums O O
which O O
saw O O
him O O
working O O
with O O
a O O
diverse O O
roster O O
of O O
collaborators O O
, O O
Young O B-PER
worked O O
with O O
music O O
producer O O
Richard B-PER B-PER
X I-PER I-PER
and O O
Pete O B-PER
Hofmann O I-PER
on O O
the O O
bulk O O
of O O
the O O
album O O
. O O

Pipa O B-LOC
Mountain O I-LOC
Park O I-LOC
( O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
Pipashan O B-LOC
Park O I-LOC
, O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
major O O
urban O O
park O O
in O O
the O O
city O O
of O O
Chongqing B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Steuben B-LOC B-LOC
Memorial I-LOC I-LOC
State I-LOC I-LOC
Historic I-LOC I-LOC
Site I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
historic O O
location O O
in O O
the O O
eastern O O
part O O
of O O
Steuben O B-LOC
, O O
Oneida O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
that O O
honors O O
Baron O B-PER
von O I-PER
Steuben O I-PER
, O O
the O O
" O O
Drillmaster O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
American O I-MISC
Revolution O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

The O O
district O O
is O O
one O O
of O O
31 O O
former O O
Abbott O B-LOC
districts O O
statewide O O
, O O
which O O
are O O
now O O
referred O O
to O O
as O O
" O O
SDA O B-LOC
Districts O I-LOC
" O O
based O O
on O O
the O O
requirement O O
that O O
the O O
state O O
cover O O
all O O
costs O O
for O O
school O O
building O O
and O O
renovation O O
projects O O
in O O
these O O
districts O O
under O O
the O O
supervision O O
of O O
the O O
New B-ORG B-ORG
Jersey I-ORG I-ORG
Schools I-ORG I-ORG
Development I-ORG I-ORG
Authority I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

Greater O B-LOC
Manchester B-LOC I-LOC
East O I-LOC
( O O
European B-ORG B-ORG
Parliament I-ORG I-ORG
constituency O O
) O O

Märchen O B-MISC
Awakens O I-MISC
Romance O I-MISC
, O O
officially O O
abbreviated O O
as O O
MÄR O B-MISC
( O O
メル O O
, O O
Meru O O
) O O
, O O
is O O
a O O
manga O O
series O O
written O O
and O O
illustrated O O
by O O
Nobuyuki B-PER B-PER
Anzai I-PER I-PER
. O O

Mr O O
Laffer O B-PER
was O O
one O O
of O O
four O O
economists O O
who O O
acted O O
as O O
advisors O O
to O O
Donald B-PER B-PER
Trump I-PER I-PER
's O O
successful O O
2016 O O
campaign O O
for O O
the O O
presidency O O
of O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
. O O

His O O
work O O
experience O O
spans O O
over O O
15 O O
developing O O
countries O O
mostly O O
in O O
Africa B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Eastern O B-LOC
Europe O I-LOC
and O O
Latin O B-LOC
America O I-LOC
. O O

" O O
U B-MISC B-MISC
Remind I-MISC I-MISC
Me I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
song O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
entertainer O O
Usher O B-PER
. O O

Kunlun O B-LOC
Station O I-LOC
( O O
) O O
is O O
one O O
of O O
four O O
Chinese O B-LOC
research O O
stations O O
in O O
Antarctica B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Ángel O B-PER
Rodríguez O I-PER
Lozano O I-PER
is O O
a O O
Spanish O B-LOC
radio O O
journalist O O
and O O
popularizer O O
of O O
science O O
, O O
best O O
known O O
as O O
the O O
creator O O
and O O
presenter O O
of O O
the O O
program O O
Vanguardia B-MISC B-MISC
de I-MISC I-MISC
la I-MISC I-MISC
Ciencia I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
which O O
was O O
broadcast O O
without O O
interruption O O
every O O
week O O
from O O
April O O
1995 O O
until O O
June O O
2007 O O
. O O

ZGF B-ORG B-ORG
Architects I-ORG I-ORG
LLP I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
ZGF O B-ORG
) O O
, O O
formerly O O
Zimmer O B-ORG
Gunsul O I-ORG
Frasca O I-ORG
Partnership O I-ORG
, O O
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
architectural O O
firm O O
with O O
offices O O
in O O
Portland B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Oregon I-LOC B-LOC
; O O
Seattle B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Washington O B-LOC
; O O
Los B-LOC B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
California B-LOC B-LOC
; O O
Washington O B-LOC
D.C. O I-LOC
; O O
New B-MISC B-LOC
York I-MISC I-LOC
, I-MISC O
New I-MISC B-LOC
York I-MISC I-LOC
; O O
and O O
Vancouver B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O B-LOC
Quba B-LOC I-LOC
Mosque I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Arabic O O
: O O
مَسجد O O
قُباء‎ O O
‎ O O
, O O
" O O
Masjid O O
Qubā O O
’ O O
" O O
) O O
, O O
in O O
the O O
outlying O O
environs O O
of O O
Medina B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
Saudi B-LOC B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
is O O
the O O
oldest O O
mosque O O
in O O
the O O
world O O
that O O
dates O O
to O O
the O O
lifetime O O
of O O
the O O
Islamic O B-ORG
prophet O O
Muhammad B-PER B-PER
, O O
considering O O
that O O
the O O
Great O B-LOC
Mosques O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
Mecca B-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Jerusalem B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
which O O
are O O
believed O O
to O O
be O O
even O O
older O O
, O O
are O O
associated O O
with O O
earlier O O
Islamic O B-ORG
Prophets O B-PER
. O O

He O O
has O O
worked O O
on O O
many O O
features O O
for O O
the O O
BBC B-ORG B-ORG
including O O
: O O
interviewing O O
Buddhist O B-ORG
monk O O
Wirathu O B-PER
and O O
members O O
of O O
Burma O B-LOC
's O O
Muslim O B-ORG
community O O
who O O
have O O
been O O
caught O O
up O O
in O O
clashes O O
with O O
Buddhist O B-ORG
nationalists O O
in O O
2013 O O
, O O
accompanying O O
Greenpeace B-ORG B-ORG
tracking O O
whales O O
hunted O O
by O O
the O O
Japanese O B-LOC
whaling O O
fleet O O
; O O
and O O
violence O O
against O O
journalists O O
by O O
Sudanese O B-LOC
security O O
forces O O
outside O O
Khartoum B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Sudan B-LOC B-LOC
where O O
he O O
was O O
attacked O O
. O O

The O O
LSC O B-ORG
performs O O
mainly O O
with O O
the O O
LSO O B-ORG
at O O
the O O
Barbican B-LOC B-LOC
Centre I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
London B-LOC B-LOC
as O O
well O O
as O O
appearing O O
at O O
other O O
concert O O
venues O O
around O O
the O O
UK O B-LOC
and O O
Europe O B-LOC
and O O
regularly O O
at O O
the O O
Avery B-LOC B-LOC
Fisher I-LOC I-LOC
Hall I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
New O B-LOC
York O I-LOC
. O O

Rachel B-PER B-PER
Boymvol I-PER I-PER
, O O
sometimes O O
spelled O O
Baumvoll O B-PER
or O O
Baumwoll O B-PER
( O O
Russian O B-MISC
: O O
Рахиль O O
Баумволь O O
, O O
Hebrew O O
: O O
רחל O O
בוימוול‎ O O
‎ O O
) O O
( O O
March O O
4 O O
, O O
1914 O O
, O O
Odessa B-LOC B-LOC
 O O
- O O
 O O
June O O
16 O O
, O O
2000 O O
, O O
Jerusalem B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
poet O O
and O O
translator O O
who O O
wrote O O
in O O
both O O
Yiddish O B-MISC
and O O
Russian O B-MISC
. O O

L'Escala B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
Spanish O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
La O B-LOC
Escala B-LOC I-LOC
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
municipality O O
in O O
the O O
" O O
comarca O O
" O O
of O O
the O O
Alt O B-LOC
Empordà O I-LOC
in O O
Girona B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Catalonia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Spain O B-LOC
. O O

Herrsching B-LOC B-LOC
am O I-LOC
Ammersee B-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
municipality O O
in O O
Upper O B-LOC
Bavaria B-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Germany B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
on O O
the O O
east O O
shore O O
of O O
the O O
Ammersee B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
southwest O O
of O O
Munich B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Veleka B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
Bulgarian O B-LOC
: O O
Велека O O
, O O
Turkish O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
Kocadere O O
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
river O O
in O O
the O O
very O O
southeast O O
of O O
Bulgaria B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
Burgas B-LOC B-LOC
Province O I-LOC
) O O
, O O
as O O
well O O
as O O
the O O
very O O
northeast O O
of O O
European O B-LOC
Turkey B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

An O O
opponent O O
of O O
the O O
Soviet O B-MISC
invasion O I-MISC
of O I-MISC
Czechoslovakia B-LOC I-MISC
in O O
1968 O O
and O O
at O O
odds O O
with O O
the O O
orthodox O O
pro O O
- O O
Soviet O B-ORG
leadership O O
of O O
Gus B-PER B-PER
Hall I-PER I-PER
, O O
Healey O B-PER
subsequently O O
left O O
the O O
Communist B-ORG B-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
to O O
join O O
the O O
New O B-ORG
American O I-ORG
Movement O I-ORG
, O O
which O O
merged O O
to O O
become O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
Democratic B-ORG B-ORG
Socialists I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
America I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
1982 O O
. O O

Ida B-PER B-PER
Mett I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
Ida O B-PER
Gilman O I-PER
, O O
20 O O
July O O
1901 O O
in O O
Smarhoń O B-LOC
, O O
Imperial O B-LOC
Russia B-LOC I-LOC
– O O
27 O O
June O O
1973 O O
in O O
Paris B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
France B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
Belarusian O B-LOC
- O O
born O O
anarchist O O
and O O
author O O
. O O

Reunification B-MISC B-MISC
Day I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
" O O
Ngày O O
Thống O O
nhất O O
" O O
) O O
, O O
Victory O B-MISC
Day O I-MISC
( O O
" O O
Ngày O O
Chiến O O
thắng O O
" O O
) O O
or O O
Liberation O B-MISC
Day O I-MISC
( O O
" O O
Ngày O O
Giải O O
phóng O O
" O O
or O O
" O O
Ngày O O
Giải O O
phóng O O
miền O O
Nam O O
" O O
) O O
or O O
the O O
rat O O
name O O
of O O
Day O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
liberating O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
South O I-MISC
for O I-MISC
national O I-MISC
reunification O I-MISC
( O O
" O O
Giải O O
phóng O O
miền O O
Nam O O
, O O
thống O O
nhất O O
đất O O
nước O O
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
public O O
holiday O O
in O O
Vietnam B-LOC B-LOC
that O O
marks O O
the O O
event O O
when O O
Viet O O
Cong O O
and O O
North O B-ORG
Vietnamese O I-ORG
troops O O
captured O O
Saigon O B-LOC
( O O
now O O
Ho B-LOC B-LOC
Chi I-LOC I-LOC
Minh I-LOC I-LOC
City I-LOC I-LOC
) O O
on O O
April O O
30 O O
, O O
1975 O O
. O O

Lucius B-PER B-PER
Vorenus I-PER I-PER
is O O
a O O
semi O O
- O O
fictional O O
character O O
in O O
the O O
British O B-LOC
- O O
Italian O B-LOC
- O O
American O B-LOC
historical O O
drama O O
television O O
series O O
" O O
Rome B-LOC B-MISC
" O O
, O O
a O O
show O O
about O O
the O O
fall O O
of O O
the O O
Roman B-LOC B-LOC
Republic I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
the O O
rise O O
of O O
the O O
Roman B-LOC B-LOC
Empire I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

In O O
the O O
middle O O
of O O
the O O
5th O O
century O O
by O O
the O O
order O O
of O O
the O O
Persian O B-ORG
king O O
Peroz B-PER B-PER
I I-PER I-PER
, O O
Vache O B-PER
built O O
in O O
Utik B-LOC B-LOC
the O O
city O O
initially O O
called O O
Perozabad O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
later O O
Partaw O B-LOC
and O O
Barda O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
made O O
it O O
the O O
capital O O
of O O
Albania B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Soccer B-MISC B-MISC
Kid I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
platform O O
video O O
game O O
created O O
by O O
UK O B-LOC
- O O
based O O
developer O O
Krisalis O B-ORG
and O O
released O O
in O O
1993 O O
for O O
the O O
Commodore O B-MISC
Amiga O I-MISC
, O O
1994 O O
for O O
the O O
Super O B-MISC
NES O I-MISC
, O O
PC O B-MISC
, O O
Amiga B-MISC B-MISC
CD32 I-MISC I-MISC
and O O
3DO B-MISC B-MISC
Interactive I-MISC I-MISC
Multiplayer I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

A O O
trio O O
featuring O O
former O O
Faith O B-ORG
vocalist O O
Alec B-PER B-PER
MacKaye I-PER I-PER
( O O
guitar O O
and O O
vocals O O
) O O
, O O
Juan B-PER B-PER
Luis I-PER I-PER
Carrera I-PER I-PER
( O O
bass O O
and O O
vocals O O
) O O
, O O
and O O
Amy B-PER B-PER
Farina I-PER I-PER
( O O
drums O O
) O O
, O O
The B-ORG B-MISC
Warmers I-ORG I-MISC
recorded O O
for O O
the O O
Washington O B-LOC
D.C. O I-LOC
based O O
record O O
label O O
Dischord O B-ORG
. O O

Brabrand B-LOC B-LOC
Lake I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Danish O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
Brabrand O B-LOC
- O O
søen O O
or O O
Brabrand O B-LOC
Sø O O
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
lake O O
in O O
the O O
district O O
of O O
Brabrand O B-LOC
( O O
Gellerup O B-LOC
) O O
, O O
west O O
of O O
Aarhus B-LOC B-LOC
city O O
, O O
Denmark B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Frustrated O O
by O O
conflicts O O
and O O
fights O O
with O O
Temptations B-MISC B-ORG
Otis B-PER B-PER
Williams I-PER I-PER
and O O
Melvin B-PER B-PER
Franklin I-PER I-PER
, O O
and O O
producer O O
Whitfield O B-PER
's O O
steadfast O O
insistence O O
on O O
producing O O
psychedelic O O
soul O O
for O O
the O O
group O O
when O O
they O O
really O O
wanted O O
to O O
sing O O
ballads O O
, O O
Kendricks O B-PER
had O O
quit O O
the O O
act O O
and O O
negotiated O O
a O O
solo O O
deal O O
with O O
Motown B-ORG B-ORG
's O O
Tamla O B-ORG
label O O
. O O

These O O
include O O
: O O
Hanna B-PER B-PER
Schygulla I-PER I-PER
, O O
the O O
director O O
's O O
favorite O O
actress O O
; O O
Ursula O B-PER
Strätz O I-PER
, O O
who O O
founded O O
the O O
Munich O B-LOC
Action O I-LOC
Theater O I-LOC
, O O
where O O
Fassbinder O B-PER
began O O
his O O
career O O
on O O
the O O
stage O O
and O O
actresses O O
Barbara B-PER B-PER
Valentin I-PER I-PER
and O O
Brigitte B-PER B-PER
Mira I-PER I-PER
, O O
the O O
star O O
of O O
Fassbinder O B-PER
’ O O
s O O
" O O
Fear O B-MISC
Eats O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Soul O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Thelma B-PER B-PER
Scott I-PER I-PER
( O O
17 O O
June O O
1913 O O
, O O
Melbourne B-LOC O
, O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
– O O
23 O O
November O O
2006 O O
, O O
Sydney B-LOC O
, O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
was O O
an O O
Australian O B-LOC
character O O
actress O O
whose O O
70 O O
- O O
year O O
career O O
in O O
theatre O O
, O O
radio O O
, O O
Australian O B-LOC
film O O
and O O
Australian O B-LOC
television O O
made O O
her O O
one O O
of O O
her O O
country O O
's O O
most O O
recognizable O O
and O O
beloved O O
personalities O O
. O O

Second O O
most O O
popular O O
are O O
celebrated O O
in O O
Camajuani O O
, O O
followed O O
in O O
popularity O O
by O O
Vueltas O B-LOC
, O O
Zulueta O B-LOC
, O O
Chambas B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Guayos B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
El O B-LOC
Santo O I-LOC
, O O
Taguayabon O O
, O O
Buenavista O B-LOC
, O O
Calabazar O O
, O O
Zaza O B-LOC
del O I-LOC
Medio O I-LOC
, O O
Falcon O O
and O O
many O O
more O O
small O O
town O O
of O O
this O O
central O O
region O O
of O O
Cuba B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Jeddah B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
sometimes O O
spelled O O
" O O
Jiddah O B-LOC
" O O
or O O
" O O
Jedda B-MISC B-LOC
" O O
; O O
; O O
Arabic O B-MISC
: O O
جدة‎ O O
‎ O O
" O O
Ğidda O O
" O O
] O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
city O O
in O O
the O O
Hijaz O O
Tihamah O B-LOC
region O O
on O O
the O O
coast O O
of O O
the O O
Red B-LOC B-LOC
Sea I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
is O O
the O O
major O O
urban O O
center O O
of O O
western O O
Saudi B-LOC B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Multnomah B-LOC B-LOC
Falls I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
waterfall O O
on O O
the O O
Oregon B-LOC B-LOC
side O O
of O O
the O O
Columbia B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
Gorge I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
located O O
east O O
of O O
Troutdale O B-LOC
, O O
between O O
Corbett O B-LOC
and O O
Dodson O B-LOC
, O O
along O O
the O O
Historic B-LOC O
Columbia I-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
Highway I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Carrick O B-LOC
Swans O B-ORG
GAA O B-ORG
is O O
a O O
Gaelic B-ORG B-ORG
Athletic I-ORG I-ORG
Association I-ORG I-ORG
club O O
, O O
located O O
in O O
the O O
town O O
of O O
Carrick B-LOC B-LOC
- I-LOC O
on I-LOC O
- I-LOC O
Suir I-LOC O
in O O
south O O
County B-LOC B-LOC
Tipperary I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
Ireland B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O B-LOC
Shire B-LOC I-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
Livingstone I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
local O O
government O O
area O O
located O O
in O O
the O O
Capricornia B-MISC B-LOC
region O O
of O O
Central B-LOC B-LOC
Queensland I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Queensland B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Australia O B-LOC
, O O
to O O
the O O
immediate O O
north O O
and O O
east O O
of O O
the O O
regional O O
city O O
of O O
Rockhampton B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Hans O B-PER
Meiser B-LOC I-PER
( O O
16 O O
February O O
1881 O O
, O O
Nuremberg B-LOC B-LOC
 O O
- O O
 O O
8 O O
June O O
1956 O O
, O O
Munich B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
German O B-LOC
Protestant O B-ORG
theologian O O
, O O
pastor O O
and O O
from O O
1933 O O
to O O
1955 O O
the O O
first O O
'Landesbischof O O
" O O
of O O
the O O
Evangelical O B-ORG
Lutheran O I-ORG
Church O I-ORG
in O O
Bavaria B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

David B-PER B-PER
Hollister I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
April O O
3 O O
, O O
1942 O O
) O O
served O O
as O O
the O O
mayor O O
of O O
Lansing B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Michigan I-LOC B-LOC
from O O
1993 O O
to O O
2003 O O
, O O
until O O
he O O
resigned O O
to O O
be O O
the O O
director O O
of O O
the O O
Michigan B-LOC B-ORG
Department O I-ORG
of O I-ORG
Labor O I-ORG
and O I-ORG
Economic O I-ORG
Growth O I-ORG
under O O
Michigan B-LOC B-LOC
Governor O O
Jennifer B-PER B-PER
Granholm I-PER I-PER
's O O
administration O O
. O O

Henrik B-MISC B-PER
Malmström O I-PER
( O O
born O O
August O O
26 O O
, O O
1978 O O
in O O
Kristianstad B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
Swedish O B-LOC
professional O O
ice O O
hockey O O
forward O O
who O O
is O O
currently O O
playing O O
for O O
Sparta B-LOC B-ORG
Warriors O I-ORG
of O O
the O O
GET B-ORG B-ORG
- I-ORG I-ORG
ligaen I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
Norway B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

It O O
was O O
produced O O
by O O
Brad B-PER B-PER
Wyman I-PER I-PER
and O O
Chris B-MISC B-PER
Hanley O I-PER
and O O
features O O
a O O
large O O
ensemble O O
cast O O
of O O
actors O O
, O O
including O O
Buscemi B-LOC B-PER
, O O
Anthony B-PER B-PER
LaPaglia I-PER I-PER
, O O
Chloë O B-PER
Sevigny O I-PER
, O O
and O O
Samuel B-PER B-PER
L. I-PER I-PER
Jackson I-PER I-PER
. O O

Herzogenbusch O B-LOC
concentration O O
camp O O
( O O
Dutch O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
Kamp O O
Vught B-LOC B-LOC
" O O
, O O
] O O
, O O
German O O
: O O
" O O
Konzentrationslager O O
Herzogenbusch O B-LOC
" O O
] O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Nazi O B-ORG
concentration O O
camp O O
located O O
in O O
Vught B-LOC B-LOC
near O O
the O O
city O O
of O O
's B-LOC O
- I-LOC O
Hertogenbosch I-LOC O
, O O
Netherlands B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Stephen B-MISC B-PER
Báthory O I-PER
( O O
Hungarian O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
Báthory O B-PER
István O O
" O O
; O O
Polish O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
Stefan O O
Batory O O
" O O
; O O
Belarusian O O
: O O
Стэфан O O
Баторы O O
; O O
Lithuanian O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
Steponas O O
Batoras O O
" O O
; O O
Romanian O O
: O O
" O O
Ștefan O O
Báthory O B-PER
" O O
; O O
27 O O
September O O
1533 O O
– O O
12 O O
December O O
1586 O O
) O O
was O O
Voivode O B-PER
of O O
Transylvania B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
1571–76 O O
) O O
, O O
Prince O O
of O O
Transylvania B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
1576–86 O O
) O O
, O O
from O O
1576 O O
Queen O O
Anna B-PER B-PER
Jagiellon I-PER I-PER
's O O
husband O O
and O O
" O O
jure O O
uxoris O O
" O O
King O O
of O O
Poland B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Grand O O
Duke O O
of O O
Lithuania B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
1576 O O
- O O
1586 O O
) O O
. O O

Green B-MISC B-PER
is O O
also O O
known O O
for O O
his O O
role O O
as O O
Chris B-PER B-PER
Griffin I-PER I-PER
on O O
Fox B-MISC B-ORG
's O O
" O O
Family B-MISC B-MISC
Guy I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
and O O
previously O O
as O O
Daniel B-PER B-PER
" O I-PER
Oz O I-PER
" O I-PER
Osbourne O I-PER
in O O
" O O
Buffy B-MISC B-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Vampire I-MISC I-MISC
Slayer I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
and O O
" O O
Greg B-MISC B-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Bunny I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Zigong B-MISC B-LOC
dialect I-MISC O
( O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
branch O O
of O O
Southwestern O B-MISC
Mandarin O I-MISC
, O O
spoken O O
mainly O O
in O O
Zigong B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Fushun B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Weiyuan O B-LOC
, O O
east O O
Rongxian O B-LOC
and O O
some O O
parts O O
of O O
Yibin B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Neijiang B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Longchang O B-LOC
and O O
other O O
neighboring O O
areas O O
. O O

A O O
private O B-ORG
company O I-ORG
limited O O
by O O
shares O O
is O O
a O O
class O B-ORG
of O O
private O B-ORG
limited O O
company O B-ORG
incorporated O O
under O O
the O O
laws O O
of O O
England B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Wales B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Scotland B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
certain O O
Commonwealth B-MISC B-ORG
countries O O
, O O
and O O
the O O
Republic B-LOC B-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
Ireland I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Susan B-MISC B-PER
McCann O I-PER
( O O
born O O
2nd O O
February O O
1949 O O
) O O
is O O
an O O
Irish O B-LOC
- O O
born O O
country O O
and O O
Irish O B-LOC
singer O O
, O O
with O O
an O O
enduring O O
and O O
international O O
popularity O O
, O O
who O O
has O O
recorded O O
some O O
650 O O
songs O O
and O O
toured O O
around O O
the O O
world O O
and O O
performed O O
at O O
numerous O O
prestigious O O
venues O O
including O O
Carnegie B-LOC B-LOC
Hall I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Dollywood O B-PER
McCann O I-PER
has O O
had O O
recording O O
deals O O
in O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Africa I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
toured O O
Russia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
has O O
been O O
recording O O
of O O
over O O
40 O O
years O O
, O O
and O O
has O O
sung O O
for O O
former O O
US O B-LOC
President O O
George B-PER B-PER
H. I-PER I-PER
W. I-PER I-PER
Bush I-PER I-PER
. O O

Samuel B-PER B-PER
" O I-PER
Sam O I-PER
" O I-PER
Bingham O I-PER
( O O
184516 O O
June O O
1905 O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
Mayor O O
of O O
Ottawa B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Ontario O B-LOC
, O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
between O O
1897 O O
and O O
1898 O O
. O O

The O O
Madrassa B-LOC B-ORG
of I-LOC I-ORG
Al I-LOC I-ORG
- I-LOC I-ORG
Nasir I-LOC I-ORG
Muhammad I-LOC I-ORG
is O O
a O O
madrassa O O
and O O
mausoleum O O
located O O
in O O
the O O
Bayn O B-LOC
al O I-LOC
- O I-LOC
Qasrayn O I-LOC
region O O
of O O
Cairo B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Egypt B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

It O O
was O O
built O O
in O O
the O O
name O O
of O O
the O O
Mamluk O B-LOC
sultan O O
Al B-PER B-PER
- I-PER I-PER
Nasir I-PER I-PER
Muhammad I-PER I-PER
ibn O I-PER
Qalawun O I-PER
, O O
but O O
its O O
construction O O
began O O
in O O
1296 O O
under O O
the O O
reign O O
of O O
Sultan O O
Al B-PER B-PER
- I-PER I-PER
Adil I-PER I-PER
Kitbugha I-PER I-PER
, O O
who O O
was O O
sultan O O
in O O
between O O
Al B-PER B-PER
- I-PER I-PER
Nasir I-PER I-PER
Muhammad I-PER I-PER
's O O
first O O
and O O
seconds O O
reigns O O
. O O

After O O
falling O O
out O O
of O O
favour O O
and O O
being O O
imprisoned O O
by O O
Theodore B-PER B-PER
II I-PER I-PER
Laskaris I-PER I-PER
, O O
Strategopoulos O B-PER
sided O O
with O O
the O O
aristocrats O O
around O O
Michael B-MISC B-PER
Palaiologos O I-PER
, O O
and O O
supported O O
him O O
in O O
his O O
rise O O
to O O
the O O
throne O O
after O O
Theodore B-PER B-PER
II I-PER I-PER
's O O
death O O
in O O
1258 O O
. O O

Nicola B-LOC B-LOC
Lake I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
glacially O O
formed O O
narrow O O
, O O
deep O O
lake O O
located O O
in O O
the O O
South O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
Central O I-LOC
Interior O I-LOC
of O O
British O B-LOC
Columbia O I-LOC
, O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
approximately O O
thirty O O
kilometres O O
northeast O O
of O O
the O O
city O O
of O O
Merritt O B-LOC
. O O

Hendjala O B-PER
represented O O
the O O
Hakahana B-LOC B-LOC
constituency O O
and O O
later O O
Tobias O B-LOC
Hainyeko O I-LOC
constituency O O
in O O
Katutura B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Windhoek B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Khomas B-LOC B-LOC
Region I-LOC I-LOC
as O O
a O O
member O O
of O O
the O O
ruling O O
South O B-ORG
West B-MISC I-ORG
Africa I-MISC I-ORG
People O I-ORG
's O I-ORG
Organization B-MISC I-ORG
( O O
SWAPO O B-ORG
) O O
from O O
1993 O O
until O O
August O O
2008 O O
. O O

Florian B-PER B-PER
Skilang I-PER I-PER
Temengil I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
November O O
4 O O
, O O
1986 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
Palauan O B-LOC
wrestler O O
at O O
Newman O B-ORG
University O I-ORG
in O O
Wichita O B-LOC
, O O
Kansas B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Women O B-MISC
's O I-MISC
March O I-MISC
on O I-MISC
Seattle B-LOC I-MISC
, O O
also O O
referred O O
to O O
as O O
the O O
Womxn O O
's O O
March O O
on O O
Seattle B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
was O O
the O O
Seattle B-LOC B-LOC
affiliate O O
of O O
the O O
worldwide O O
2017 O B-MISC
Women O I-MISC
's O I-MISC
March O I-MISC
protest O I-MISC
on O O
January O O
21 O O
, O O
2017 O O
. O O

Saras O O
Per O O
Kristian O B-PER
Matsson O I-PER
( O O
born O O
30 O O
April O O
1983 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
singer O O
- O O
songwriter O O
from O O
Dalarna B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Sweden B-LOC B-LOC
who O O
performs O O
under O O
the O O
stage O O
name O O
of O O
The B-PER B-MISC
Tallest I-PER I-MISC
Man I-PER I-MISC
on I-PER I-MISC
Earth I-PER I-MISC
. O O

" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Last I-MISC I-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Famous I-MISC I-MISC
International I-MISC I-MISC
Playboys I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
is O O
notable O O
for O O
featuring O O
three O O
of O O
Morrissey B-PER B-PER
's O O
former O O
colleagues O O
in O O
The O O
Smiths—Andy O O
Rourke O O
, O O
Mike O B-PER
Joyce O I-PER
and O O
one O O
- O O
time O O
Smiths O B-ORG
rhythm O O
guitarist O O
Craig O O
Gannon—all O O
of O O
whom O O
also O O
appear O O
on O O
the O O
B O O
- O O
side O O
, O O
" O O
Lucky O B-MISC
Lisp O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Union O O
Bank O O
of O O
Hong B-LOC B-LOC
Kong I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Former O O
stock O O
code O O
: O O
) O O
( O O
Traditional B-MISC O
Chinese O B-LOC
: O O
香港友聯銀行 O B-ORG
) O O
was O O
a O O
bank O O
in O O
Hong B-LOC B-LOC
Kong I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

It O O
now O O
becomes O O
Industrial B-ORG B-ORG
and I-ORG I-ORG
Commercial I-ORG I-ORG
Bank I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
China I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
Asia B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
( O O
Traditional B-MISC O
Chinese O B-LOC
: O O
中國工商銀行 O B-ORG
( O O
亞洲 O O
) O O
) O O
. O O

Karen O O
Ann O O
Poole B-LOC B-PER
( O O
born O O
8 O O
January O O
1971 O O
) O O
is O O
an O O
English O B-LOC
singer O O
- O O
songwriter O O
, O O
who O O
gained O O
initial O O
fame O O
with O O
her O O
younger O O
sister O O
, O O
Shelly B-PER B-PER
Poole I-PER I-PER
, O O
as O O
the O O
duo O O
Alisha B-ORG B-ORG
's I-ORG I-ORG
Attic I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

The O O
Ministry B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Tourism I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
Indonesian O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
Kementerian O B-ORG
Pariwisata O I-ORG
" O O
, O O
formerly O O
" O O
Kementerian O B-ORG
Pariwisata O I-ORG
dan O I-ORG
Ekonomi O I-ORG
Kreatif O I-ORG
" O O
) O O
is O O
the O O
ministry O O
in O O
Indonesia B-LOC B-LOC
concerned O O
with O O
administration O O
of O O
tourism O O
. O O

The O O
Netherlands B-LOC B-LOC
Antilles I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Dutch O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
Nederlandse O O
Antillen O O
" O O
] O O
; O O
Papiamentu O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
Antia O B-LOC
Hulandes O I-LOC
" O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
constituent O O
country O O
of O O
the O O
Kingdom B-LOC B-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
the I-LOC I-LOC
Netherlands I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

High B-LOC B-LOC
Park I-LOC I-LOC
was O O
a O O
provincial O O
electoral O O
district O O
in O O
the O O
west O O
- O O
end O O
of O O
the O O
old O O
City O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Toronto B-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Ontario O B-LOC
, O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Anachlysictis B-MISC B-MISC
gracilis O I-MISC
is O O
an O O
extinct O O
carnivorous O O
mammal O O
belonging O O
to O O
the O O
group O O
Sparassodonta B-MISC B-MISC
, O O
which O O
were O O
metatherians O O
( O O
a O O
group O O
including O O
marsupials O O
and O O
their O O
close O O
relatives O O
) O O
that O O
inhabited O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
America I-LOC I-LOC
during O O
the O O
Cenozoic O B-MISC
. O O

Turn B-MISC B-MISC
Left I-MISC I-MISC
, I-MISC I-MISC
Turn I-MISC I-MISC
Right I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
2003 O O
joint O O
Hong O B-LOC
Kong O I-LOC
- O O
Singaporean O B-LOC
romance O O
film O O
, O O
filmed O O
in O O
Taipei B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Taiwan O B-LOC
. O O

Francesco B-PER B-PER
Pazienza I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
in O O
Monteparano O B-LOC
in O O
the O O
1946 O O
) O O
is O O
an O O
Italian O B-LOC
businessman O O
, O O
and O O
former O O
officer O O
of O O
the O O
Italian O B-LOC
military O O
intelligence O O
agency O O
, O O
SISMI B-ORG B-ORG
. O O

According O O
to O O
Smith O B-PER
, O O
the O O
book O O
was O O
" O O
a O O
translation O O
of O O
some O O
ancient O O
records O O
[ O O
... O O
] O O
purporting O O
to O O
be O O
the O O
writings O O
of O O
Abraham B-PER B-PER
, O O
while O O
he O O
was O O
in O O
Egypt B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
called O O
the O O
Book O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
Abraham B-PER I-MISC
, O O
written O O
by O O
his O O
own O O
hand O O
, O O
upon O O
papyrus O O
" O O
. O O

Öakse O B-LOC
( O O
alternately O O
: O O
Öakse O B-LOC
laid O I-LOC
, O O
or O O
Pärglaid O B-LOC
) O O
is O O
an O O
island O O
in O O
the O O
Baltic B-LOC B-LOC
Sea I-LOC I-LOC
belonging O O
to O O
the O O
country O O
of O O
Estonia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Zayed B-LOC B-LOC
National I-LOC I-LOC
Museum I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
Arabic O B-MISC
: O O
متحف O B-LOC
زايد O I-LOC
الوطني O I-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
planned O O
museum O O
, O O
to O O
be O O
located O O
in O O
Abu B-LOC B-LOC
Dhabi I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
UAE O B-LOC
. O O

Olga O B-PER
Grigoryevna O I-PER
Shatunovskaya O I-PER
( O O
Russian O O
: O O
Шатуновская O O
Ольга O O
Григорьевна O O
; O O
1901 O O
, O O
Baku B-LOC B-LOC
 O O
- O O
 O O
1990 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
member O O
of O O
Shvernik O B-ORG
Commission O I-ORG
created O O
by O O
Nikita B-PER B-PER
Khrushchev I-PER I-PER
to O O
investigate O O
Stalin O B-PER
's O O
crimes O O
. O O

Dr. O O
Thomas O B-PER
A. O I-PER
McLaughlin O I-PER
( O O
1896 O O
- O O
28 O O
May O O
1971 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
Irish O B-LOC
engineer O O
from O O
Drogheda B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Co.Louth O O
, O O
and O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
key O O
people O O
in O O
the O O
Shannon O B-MISC
hydroelectric O O
scheme O O
, O O
an O O
early O O
icon O O
of O O
the O O
Irish B-LOC B-LOC
Free I-LOC I-LOC
State I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

West B-LOC B-LOC
Sister I-LOC I-LOC
Island I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
an O O
island O O
of O O
the O O
U.S. O B-LOC
state O O
of O O
Ohio B-LOC B-LOC
located O O
in O O
the O O
Western O B-LOC
Basin O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
Lake B-LOC I-LOC
Erie I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
Winnipeg B-ORG B-ORG
Blue I-ORG I-ORG
Bombers I-ORG I-ORG
are O O
a O O
Canadian B-MISC B-LOC
football I-MISC O
team O O
based O O
in O O
Winnipeg B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Manitoba O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Kingdom O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Africa B-LOC I-LOC
was O O
an O O
ephemeral O O
frontier O O
zone O O
of O O
the O O
Siculo O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
Norman O I-LOC
state O I-LOC
in O O
the O O
former O O
Roman O B-LOC
province O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
Africa B-LOC I-LOC
( O O
" O O
Ifrīqiya O B-LOC
" O O
in O O
Tunisian B-MISC B-MISC
Arabic I-MISC I-MISC
) O O
, O O
corresponding O O
to O O
parts O O
of O O
Algeria B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Tunisia B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Libya B-LOC B-LOC
today O O
. O O

According O O
to O O
Hubert O B-PER
Houben O I-PER
, O O
since O O
" O O
Africa B-LOC B-LOC
" O O
was O O
never O O
mentioned O O
in O O
the O O
royal O O
title O O
of O O
the O O
kings O O
of O O
Sicily O B-LOC
, O O
" O O
one O O
ought O O
not O O
to O O
speak O O
of O O
a O O
‘ O O
Norman O B-LOC
kingdom O O
of O O
Africa B-LOC B-LOC
’ O O
. O O
" O O

Susanne O B-PER
Jonah O I-PER
- O I-PER
Lynn O I-PER
Georgi O I-PER
Puigcercós O I-PER
( O O
born O O
27 O O
July O O
1976 O O
in O O
Sjølund O B-LOC
) O O
, O O
commonly O O
known O O
as O O
Susanne B-PER B-PER
Georgi I-PER I-PER
, O O
is O O
a O O
Danish O B-LOC
singer O O
who O O
lives O O
and O O
works O O
in O O
Andorra B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Lucius B-PER B-PER
Caesar I-PER I-PER
( O O
17 O O
BC O O
– O O
20 O O
August O O
AD O O
2 O O
) O O
, O O
formally O O
Lucius B-MISC B-PER
Julius O I-PER
Caesar O I-PER
, O O
was O O
the O O
adopted O O
son O O
and O O
heir O O
of O O
Augustus B-PER B-PER
along O O
with O O
his O O
brother O O
Gaius O B-PER
. O O

Palazzo O B-LOC
Uguccioni O I-LOC
is O O
a O O
Renaissance O B-MISC
palace O O
on O O
the O O
Piazza O B-LOC
della O I-LOC
Signoria O I-LOC
in O O
Florence B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
central O O
Italy B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Yorkton B-MISC B-MISC
Film I-MISC I-MISC
Festival I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
YFF O B-MISC
) O O
is O O
an O O
annual O O
film O O
festival O O
held O O
in O O
late O O
May O O
in O O
Yorkton B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Saskatchewan B-MISC B-LOC
. O O

Beijing B-LOC B-ORG
Institute B-ORG I-ORG
of O I-ORG
Fashion O I-ORG
Technology O I-ORG
( O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
university O O
in O O
Beijing B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
China B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Donaldson B-LOC B-LOC
Air I-LOC I-LOC
Force I-LOC I-LOC
Base I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
former O O
facility O O
of O O
the O O
United B-ORG B-ORG
States I-ORG I-ORG
Air I-ORG I-ORG
Force I-ORG I-ORG
located O O
south O O
of O O
Greenville B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
South I-LOC B-LOC
Carolina I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

József O B-PER
Cardinal O I-PER
Mindszenty O I-PER
[ O O
jo O O
: O O
ʒɛf O B-PER
mindsɛnti O I-PER
] O O
( O O
29 O O
March O O
18926 O O
May O O
1975 O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
Prince O O
Primate O O
, O O
Archbishop O O
of O O
Esztergom B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
cardinal O O
, O O
and O O
leader O O
of O O
the O O
Catholic O B-ORG
Church O I-ORG
in O O
Hungary B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
2 O O
October O O
1945 O O
to O O
18 O O
December O O
1973 O O
. O O

Live O B-ORG
Labs O I-ORG
was O O
headed O O
by O O
Dr. O O
Gary B-PER B-PER
William I-PER I-PER
Flake I-PER I-PER
, O O
who O O
prior O O
to O O
joining O O
Microsoft B-ORG B-ORG
was O O
a O O
principal O O
scientist O O
at O O
Yahoo B-ORG B-ORG
! I-ORG O

It O O
grows O O
in O O
cold O O
Arctic O B-LOC
and O O
alpine O O
regions O O
, O O
either O O
at O O
high O O
latitudes O O
in O O
the O O
Arctic O B-LOC
or O O
at O O
high O O
elevations O O
in O O
the O O
mountains O O
( O O
Rocky B-LOC B-LOC
Mountains I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Cascades O B-LOC
, O O
Sierra B-LOC B-LOC
Nevada I-LOC I-LOC
) O O
. O O

It O O
is O O
located O O
83 O O
km O O
from O O
Calgary B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
west O O
on O O
Highway O B-LOC
1 O I-LOC
( O O
Trans B-LOC B-LOC
- I-LOC I-LOC
Canada I-LOC I-LOC
Highway I-LOC I-LOC
) O O
and O O
south O O
on O O
Highway O B-LOC
40 O I-LOC
( O O
Kananaskis O B-LOC
Trail O I-LOC
) O O
. O O

Ilkka O B-PER
Herlin O B-PER
( O O
born O O
1959 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
Finnish O B-LOC
billionaire O O
, O O
the O O
chairman O O
and O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
owners O O
of O O
Cargotec B-ORG B-ORG
, O O
and O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
owners O O
of O O
the O O
elevator O O
and O O
escalator O O
maker O O
Kone B-ORG B-ORG
. O O

Sanford O B-LOC
is O O
a O O
city O O
in O O
York B-LOC B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
Maine B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Juw B-PER B-PER
Juwinga I-PER I-PER
( O O
alias O O
Jongema O B-PER
) O O
of O O
Bolsward B-LOC B-LOC
was O O
a O O
Frisian O B-LOC
chieftain O O
that O O
earned O O
great O O
fame O O
in O O
the O O
struggle O O
against O O
the O O
( O O
Dutch O B-LOC
) O O
‘ O O
infidels O O
’ O O
. O O

" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Invisible I-MISC I-MISC
Man I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
is O O
a O O
song O O
by O O
the O O
British O B-LOC
rock O O
band O O
Queen O B-ORG
, O O
written O O
by O O
drummer O O
Roger B-PER B-PER
Taylor I-PER I-PER
but O O
credited O O
to O O
Queen O B-ORG
. O O

After O O
the O O
war O O
, O O
he O O
built O O
the O O
Schönborn O B-LOC
Palace O I-LOC
in O O
Prague B-LOC B-LOC
home O O
to O O
the O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
Embassy O I-LOC
to O O
the O O
Czech B-LOC B-LOC
Republic I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

" O O
The B-ORG B-MISC
Reivers I-ORG I-MISC
" O O
was O O
adapted O O
into O O
a O O
1969 O O
film O O
directed O O
by O O
Mark B-PER B-PER
Rydell I-PER I-PER
and O O
starring O O
Steve B-PER B-PER
McQueen I-PER I-PER
as O O
Boon O B-PER
Hogganbeck O I-PER
. O O

Kobe B-ORG B-ORG
Steel I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
Ltd. O O
( O O
株式会社神戸製鋼所 O O
, O O
Kabushiki O O
- O O
gaisha O O
Kōbe O O
Seikō O O
- O O
sho O O
) O O
, O O
operating O O
worldwide O O
under O O
the O O
brand O O
Kobelco O B-ORG
, O O
is O O
a O O
major O O
Japanese O B-LOC
steel O O
manufacturer O O
headquartered O O
in O O
Chūō O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
ku O I-LOC
, O O
Kobe B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Played O O
by O O
Scottish O B-LOC
- O O
American O B-LOC
actor O O
Kevin B-PER B-PER
McKidd I-PER I-PER
in O O
the O O
series O O
, O O
Lucius B-PER B-PER
Vorenus I-PER I-PER
is O O
introduced O O
as O O
a O O
main O O
character O O
in O O
the O O
pilot O O
episode O O
, O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
Stolen O I-MISC
Eagle O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Lake B-LOC B-LOC
Abitibi I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
French O O
: O O
" O O
Lac O O
Abitibi O B-LOC
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
lake O O
in O O
northeastern O O
Ontario O B-LOC
and O O
western O O
Quebec O B-LOC
, O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

It O O
is O O
available O O
for O O
download O O
on O O
the O O
European O B-MISC
PlayStation B-MISC I-MISC
Store O I-MISC
for O O
the O O
PlayStation B-MISC B-MISC
3 I-MISC I-MISC
system O O
, O O
with O O
plans O O
for O O
release O O
on O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
PlayStation B-MISC B-MISC
3 I-MISC I-MISC
store O O
. O O

Willits O B-LOC
( O O
formerly O O
Little O B-LOC
Lake O I-LOC
and O I-LOC
Willitsville O I-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
city O O
in O O
Mendocino O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
California B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

It O O
features O O
appearances O O
by O O
musicians O O
such O O
as O O
N.O.R.E. O B-PER
, O O
Tony B-PER B-PER
Touch I-PER I-PER
, O O
B B-PER B-PER
- I-PER I-PER
Real I-PER I-PER
, O O
Ivy B-PER B-PER
Queen I-PER I-PER
, O O
Pitbull O B-PER
, O O
Lil B-PER B-PER
Jon I-PER I-PER
, O O
Richie O B-PER
Rivera O I-PER
, O O
Mackie O B-PER
y O I-PER
Yaga O I-PER
, O O
Aventura O B-PER
and O O
Notch O B-PER
. O O

Curup O B-LOC
is O O
a O O
subdistrict O O
of O O
Rejang B-LOC B-LOC
Lebong I-LOC I-LOC
Regency I-LOC O
, O O
Bengkulu B-LOC B-LOC
province O O
of O O
Indonesia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Boating B-MISC B-MISC
on I-MISC I-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
River I-MISC I-MISC
Epte I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
The O B-MISC
Canoe O I-MISC
on O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Epte B-LOC I-MISC
) O O
is O O
an O O
1890 O O
oil O O
painting O O
by O O
French O B-LOC
impressionist O O
artist O O
Claude B-PER B-PER
Monet I-PER I-PER
. O O

Rosarito O B-LOC
is O O
a O O
coastal O O
resort O O
city O O
in O O
the O O
Mexican O B-LOC
state O O
of O O
Baja B-LOC B-LOC
California I-LOC I-LOC
located O O
approximately O O
10 O O
miles O O
south O O
of O O
the O O
U.S. O B-LOC
border O O
in O O
Rosarito B-LOC B-LOC
Beach I-LOC I-LOC
Municipality I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

He O O
operated O O
in O O
Pernambuco B-LOC B-LOC
until O O
1861 O O
, O O
moving O O
to O O
Rio B-LOC B-LOC
de I-LOC I-LOC
Janeiro I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
receiving O O
from O O
the O O
emperor O O
D. O B-PER
Pedro O I-PER
II O I-PER
the O O
title O O
of O O
" O O
Photographo O B-MISC
da O I-MISC
Casa O I-MISC
Imperial O I-MISC
" O O
( O O
" O O
Photographer O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Imperial O I-MISC
House O I-MISC
" O O
) O O
, O O
on O O
April O O
21 O O
, O O
1862 O O
. O O

The O B-ORG
Indian B-ORG I-ORG
Institute I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Planning I-ORG I-ORG
and I-ORG I-ORG
Management I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
IIPM O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
an O O
institute O O
headquartered O O
in O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
Delhi I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
which O O
previously O O
had O O
18 O O
branches O O
across O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Faurot B-LOC B-LOC
Field I-LOC I-LOC
was O O
also O O
home O O
to O O
the O O
Missouri B-ORG B-ORG
State I-ORG I-ORG
High I-ORG I-ORG
School I-ORG I-ORG
Activities I-ORG I-ORG
Association I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
MSHSAA O B-ORG
) O O
football O O
championships O O
for O O
many O O
years O O
, O O
now O O
held O O
in O O
St. O B-LOC
Louis O I-LOC
in O O
the O O
climate O O
- O O
controlled O O
Edward B-LOC O
Jones I-LOC O
Dome I-LOC O
. O O

Rejecting O O
the O O
queen O O
's O O
policy O O
of O O
isolationism O B-MISC
and O O
Christian O B-ORG
persecution O O
, O O
Radama B-PER B-PER
II I-PER I-PER
permitted O O
religious O O
freedom O O
and O O
re O O
- O O
opened O O
Madagascar B-LOC B-LOC
to O O
European O B-LOC
influence O O
. O O

Shaji O B-PER
's O O
collaboration O O
with O O
Ranijth O B-PER
brought O O
forth O O
stories O O
set O O
in O O
a O O
feudal O O
background O O
, O O
such O O
as O O
" O O
Aaraam B-MISC B-MISC
Thampuran I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1997 O O
) O O
, O O
" O O
Narasimham O B-MISC
" O O
( O O
2000 O O
) O O
, O O
and O O
" O O
Valliettan B-MISC B-MISC
" O O
( O O
2000 O O
) O O
. O O

– O O
November O O
2 O O
, O O
2001 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
leading O O
Lithuanian O B-LOC
- O O
Jewish O B-ORG
Haredi O B-ORG
rabbi O O
in O O
Bnei B-LOC B-LOC
Brak I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Israel B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

She O O
is O O
known O O
for O O
portraying O O
the O O
role O O
of O O
Mia O B-PER
Jones O I-PER
in O O
the O O
drama O O
series O O
" O O
" O O
and O O
then O O
Elena B-PER B-PER
Gilbert I-PER I-PER
on O O
The B-ORG O
CW I-ORG B-ORG
's O O
supernatural O O
drama O O
series O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Vampire I-MISC I-MISC
Diaries I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

The O O
album O O
was O O
released O O
by O O
Maverick B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
the O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
on O O
June O O
13 O O
, O O
2005 O O
, O O
available O O
only O O
at O O
North O B-LOC
American O I-LOC
Starbucks B-ORG B-ORG
outlets O O
until O O
July O O
26 O O
, O O
2005 O O
, O O
when O O
it O O
was O O
made O O
available O O
in O O
other O O
retail O O
stores O O
. O O

This O O
limited O O
availability O O
led O O
to O O
a O O
dispute O O
between O O
Maverick B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
HMV B-ORG B-ORG
Canada O I-ORG
, O O
who O O
retaliated O O
by O O
removing O O
from O O
sale O O
Morissette O B-PER
's O O
other O O
albums O O
for O O
the O O
duration O O
of O O
Starbucks B-ORG B-ORG
" O O
exclusive O O
month O O
- O O
long O O
sale O O
. O O

Quaudiophiliac B-MISC B-MISC
( O O
styled O O
QuAUDIOPHILIAc O B-MISC
) O O
is O O
a O O
compilation O O
album O O
featuring O O
music O O
by O O
Frank B-PER B-PER
Zappa I-PER I-PER
, O O
released O O
in O O
DVD O B-MISC
- O I-MISC
Audio O I-MISC
format O O
by O O
Barking O B-ORG
Pumpkin O I-ORG
Records O I-ORG
in O O
2004 O O
. O O

The O O
channel O O
was O O
available O O
to O O
Sirius B-MISC B-ORG
and O O
XM O B-ORG
subscribers O O
in O O
both O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Owned O O
and O O
bred O O
by O O
Queen O B-PER
Elizabeth B-PER I-PER
II I-PER I-PER
, O O
was O O
undefeated O O
in O O
her O O
three O O
races O O
as O O
a O O
two O O
- O O
year O O
- O O
old O O
in O O
1981 O O
, O O
winning O O
the O O
Acomb B-MISC B-MISC
Stakes I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
May B-MISC B-MISC
Hill I-MISC I-MISC
Stakes I-MISC I-MISC
and O O
Fillies B-MISC O
" I-MISC O
Mile I-MISC O
. O O

The O O
railway O O
shares O O
line O O
with O O
Inland B-LOC B-LOC
Line I-LOC I-LOC
between O O
Brunflo B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Östersund O B-LOC
while O O
the O O
line O O
between O O
Ånge O B-LOC
and O O
Bräcke O B-LOC
is O O
double O O
track O O
. O O

On O O
August O O
15 O O
, O O
2005 O O
( O O
see O O
2005 O O
in O O
music O O
) O O
, O O
ahead O O
of O O
the O O
album O O
's O O
release O O
in O O
early O O
October O O
, O O
Epic B-ORG B-ORG
Records I-ORG I-ORG
made O O
available O O
for O O
streaming O O
both O O
" O O
Parting B-MISC B-MISC
Gift I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
and O O
" O O
O B-MISC O
" I-MISC O
Sailor I-MISC O
" O O
on O O
Apple B-MISC B-ORG
's O O
official O O
website O O
. O O

A O B-LOC
Shau O I-LOC
Valley O I-LOC
was O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
key O O
entry O O
points O O
into O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
Vietnam I-LOC I-LOC
for O O
men O O
and O O
materiel O O
brought O O
along O O
the O O
Ho B-PER O
Chi I-PER O
Minh I-PER O
Trail O O
by O O
the O O
Communist O O
North O B-ORG
Vietnamese O I-ORG
Army O I-ORG
and O O
was O O
the O O
scene O O
of O O
heavy O O
fighting O O
, O O
especially O O
against O O
American O O
soldiers O O
, O O
during O O
the O O
Vietnam B-MISC B-MISC
War I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

Timo B-PER B-PER
Werner I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
6 O O
March O O
1996 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
German O B-LOC
professional O O
footballer O O
who O O
plays O O
as O O
a O O
forward O O
for O O
RB B-ORG B-ORG
Leipzig I-ORG I-ORG
and O O
the O O
Germany B-LOC B-ORG
national O I-ORG
team O I-ORG
. O O

The O O
area O O
straddles O O
the O O
Vaal B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
is O O
a O O
major O O
industrial O O
region O O
, O O
which O O
is O O
home O O
to O O
former O O
Iron O B-ORG
and O I-ORG
Steel O I-ORG
Corporation O I-ORG
Iscor O I-ORG
, O O
now O O
ArcelorMittal O B-ORG
South B-LOC I-ORG
Africa I-LOC I-ORG
and O O
Sasol B-ORG B-ORG
, O O
the O O
steel O O
and O O
oil O O
- O O
from O O
- O O
coal O O
processing O O
facilities O O
. O O

Genshin B-PER B-PER
( O O
源信 O B-PER
; O O
942 O O
– O O
July O O
6 O O
, O O
1017 O O
) O O
, O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
Eshin O B-PER
Sozu O I-PER
, O O
was O O
the O O
most O O
influential O O
of O O
a O O
number O O
of O O
Tendai O B-ORG
scholars O O
active O O
during O O
the O O
tenth O O
and O O
eleventh O O
centuries O O
in O O
Japan B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

British O B-LOC
administrators O O
, O O
including O O
the O O
founder O O
of O O
Penang B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Francis B-PER B-PER
Light I-PER I-PER
, O O
were O O
buried O O
within O O
the O O
Old O B-LOC
Protestant O I-LOC
Cemetery O I-LOC
near O O
the O O
eastern O O
end O O
of O O
Northam O B-LOC
Road O I-LOC
. O O

Christmas B-MISC B-MISC
pudding I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
a O O
type O O
of O O
pudding O O
traditionally O O
served O O
as O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
Christmas B-MISC B-MISC
dinner O O
in O O
the O O
UK O B-LOC
, O O
Ireland O B-LOC
and O O
in O O
other O O
countries O O
where O O
it O O
has O O
been O O
brought O O
by O O
British O B-LOC
emigrants O O
. O O

It O O
started O O
out O O
as O O
a O O
liberal O O
weekly O O
, O O
then O O
, O O
after O O
some O O
talks O O
that O O
Pavlov O B-PER
had O O
had O O
with O O
the O O
then O O
Minister O O
of O O
Interior O O
Pyotr B-PER B-PER
Valuyev I-PER I-PER
( O O
which O O
involved O O
the O O
promise O O
of O O
the O O
financial O O
support O O
, O O
among O O
other O O
things O O
) O O
, O O
in O O
early O O
1862 O O
became O O
a O O
conservative O O
daily O O
, O O
whose O O
agenda O O
was O O
formulated O O
in O O
the O O
January O O
issue O O
by O O
Boris B-PER B-PER
Chicherin I-PER I-PER
in O O
his O O
article O O
" O O
Measure O B-MISC
and O I-MISC
Limits O I-MISC
" O O
( O O
Мера O B-MISC
и O I-MISC
границы O I-MISC
) O O
. O O

Captain O O
Gurbachan B-PER B-PER
Singh I-PER I-PER
Salaria I-PER I-PER
, O O
PVC O B-MISC
( O O
born O O
29 O O
November O O
1935 O O
– O O
5 O O
December O O
1961 O O
) O O
is O O
an O O
Indian O B-LOC
military O O
war O O
hero O O
, O O
who O O
was O O
awarded O O
the O O
Param B-MISC B-MISC
Vir I-MISC I-MISC
Chakra I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
India O B-LOC
's O O
highest O O
wartime O O
military O O
award O O
. O O

Miriam B-PER B-PER
Christine I-PER I-PER
Borg O I-PER
is O O
a O O
Maltese O B-LOC
pop O O
and O O
rhythm O O
and O O
blues O O
singer O O
best O O
known O O
for O O
representing O O
Malta B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
the O O
Eurovision B-MISC B-MISC
Song I-MISC I-MISC
Contest I-MISC I-MISC
1996 O O
. O O

Dropmire O B-MISC
is O O
a O O
surveillance O O
program O O
by O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
's O O
National B-ORG B-ORG
Security I-ORG I-ORG
Agency I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
NSA O B-ORG
) O O
aimed O O
at O O
surveillance O O
of O O
foreign O O
embassies O O
and O O
diplomatic O O
staff O O
, O O
including O O
those O O
of O O
NATO B-ORG B-ORG
allies O O
. O O

Manol B-PER B-PER
Manolov I-PER I-PER
( O O
Bulgarian O B-LOC
: O O
Манол O O
Манолов O O
) O O
( O O
born O O
5 O O
August O O
1925 O O
, O O
in O O
Sofia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Bulgaria B-LOC O
; O O
died O O
December O O
16 O O
, O O
2008 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Bulgarian O B-LOC
football O O
defender O O
and O O
manager O O
. O O

The O O
United B-LOC B-MISC
States I-LOC I-MISC
Attorney O I-MISC
General O I-MISC
( O O
A.G. O B-MISC
) O O
is O O
the O O
head O O
of O O
the O O
United B-ORG B-ORG
States I-ORG I-ORG
Department I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Justice I-ORG I-ORG
per O O
, O O
concerned O O
with O O
legal O O
affairs O O
, O O
and O O
is O O
the O O
chief O O
law O O
enforcement O O
officer O O
and O O
chief O O
lawyer O O
of O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
government O O
. O O

The O O
Kyle O B-LOC
Hills O I-LOC
( O O
) O O
are O O
a O O
prominent O O
group O O
of O O
volcanic O O
cones O O
, O O
hills O O
, O O
ridges O O
, O O
and O O
peaks O O
that O O
occupy O O
the O O
eastern O O
part O O
of O O
Ross B-LOC B-LOC
Island I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Antarctica O B-LOC
, O O
between O O
Mount B-LOC B-LOC
Terror I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Cape O B-LOC
Crozier O I-LOC
. O O

Jacques B-PER B-PER
Feldbau I-PER I-PER
was O O
a O O
French O B-LOC
mathematician O O
, O O
born O O
on O O
22 O O
October O O
1914 O O
in O O
Strasbourg B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
of O O
an O O
Alsatian O B-LOC
Jewish O B-ORG
traditionalist O O
family O O
. O O

It O O
took O O
place O O
around O O
the O O
" O O
Berlin B-LOC B-LOC
Schloss O I-LOC
" O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
" O O
Stadtschloss O B-LOC
" O O
in O O
the O O
centre O O
of O O
Berlin B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Germany B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Glasscock B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
Courthouse I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
an O O
historic O O
courthouse O O
building O O
located O O
in O O
Garden B-LOC B-LOC
City I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Glasscock B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
Texas I-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Fashizmi O B-ORG
( O O
'Fascism O O
" O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
daily O O
Albanian O B-LOC
- O O
Italian O B-LOC
bilingual O O
newspaper O O
published O O
from O O
Tirana B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Albanian B-LOC B-LOC
Kingdom I-LOC I-LOC
1939 O O
- O O
1940 O O
. O O

Camilo O B-PER
José O I-PER
Vergara O I-PER
( O O
born O O
1944 O O
in O O
Santiago B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Chile B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
Chilean O B-LOC
- O O
born O O
, O O
New O B-LOC
York O I-LOC
- O O
based O O
writer O O
, O O
photographer O O
and O O
documentarian O O
. O O

The O O
Gouina O B-LOC
Hydroelectric O I-LOC
Plant B-MISC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
run O O
- O O
of O O
- O O
the O O
- O O
river O O
- O O
type O O
hydroelectric O O
installation O O
currently O O
being O O
constructed O O
on O O
Gouina O B-LOC
Falls O I-LOC
along O O
the O O
Senegal B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
Mali B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
BPF B-ORG B-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
Belarusian O B-MISC
: O O
Партыя O O
БНФ O B-MISC
, O O
" O O
Partyja O O
BNF O O
" O O
or O O
ПБНФ O O
" O O
PBNF O B-ORG
" O O
) O O
, O O
is O O
a O O
political O O
party O O
in O O
Belarus B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

RJ B-PER B-PER
Hadley I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
Rakeim O B-PER
Jerhal O I-PER
Hadley O I-PER
on O O
January O O
14 O O
, O O
1969 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
Democratic B-ORG B-ORG
Party I-ORG I-ORG
activist O O
and O O
current O O
Tax O O
Commissioner O O
of O O
Rockdale O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
Georgia O B-LOC
. O O

Snow O B-LOC
Building O I-LOC
on O O
East O B-LOC
St. O I-LOC
George O I-LOC
Boulevard O I-LOC
in O O
downtown O O
St. O B-LOC
George O I-LOC
, O O
which O O
also O O
serves O O
as O O
KUTV B-ORG B-ORG
's O O
southern O O
Utah B-LOC B-LOC
news O O
bureau O O
. O O

Mustansiriyah O B-ORG
University O I-ORG
( O O
Arabic O B-MISC
: O O
الجامعة O B-ORG
المستنصرية O I-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
university O O
in O O
Baghdad B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Iraq B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

He O O
is O O
a O O
Visiting O O
Professor O O
at O O
INSEAD B-ORG B-ORG
's O O
Asia O B-LOC
campus O O
, O O
a O O
blogger O O
for O O
the O O
" O O
Harvard B-MISC B-MISC
Business I-MISC I-MISC
Review I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
and O O
has O O
contributed O O
to O O
the O O
" O O
New B-LOC B-MISC
York I-LOC I-MISC
Times O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Lake B-LOC B-LOC
Blouin I-LOC I-LOC
( O O
French O O
: O O
" O O
lac O O
Blouin O B-LOC
" O O
) O O
is O O
an O O
ellipse O O
shaped O O
natural O O
fresh O O
water O O
lake O O
in O O
the O O
Abitibi O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
Témiscamingue O I-LOC
Administrative O I-LOC
Region O I-LOC
, O O
Quebec O B-LOC
, O O
Canada B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

With O O
a O O
population O O
of O O
14,301 O O
as O O
of O O
July O O
1 O O
, O O
2016. O O
, O O
it O O
is O O
the O O
largest O O
commercial O O
center O O
between O O
Grand B-LOC B-LOC
Forks I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
North B-LOC B-LOC
Dakota I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Duluth B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Minnesota I-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Bemidji O B-LOC
lies O O
on O O
the O O
south O O
west O O
shore O O
of O O
Lake B-LOC B-LOC
Bemidji I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
the O O
northernmost O O
lake O O
feeding O O
the O O
Mississippi B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
as O O
such O O
is O O
deemed O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
First O I-MISC
City O I-MISC
On O I-MISC
The O I-MISC
Mississippi B-ORG I-MISC
. O O
" O O

After O O
defeating O O
Kim B-PER B-PER
Beazley I-PER I-PER
for O O
the O O
role O O
of O O
Leader O O
of O O
the O O
Opposition O B-ORG
, O O
Mark B-PER B-PER
Latham I-PER I-PER
coined O O
the O O
political O O
slogan O O
in O O
his O O
first O O
press O O
conference O O
to O O
describe O O
what O O
he O O
stood O O
for O O
as O O
Labor O B-ORG
leader O O
and O O
alternative O O
Prime B-PER O
Minister I-PER O
. O O

It O O
also O O
tells O O
some O O
of O O
the O O
history O O
of O O
Africatown B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
a O O
community O O
formed O O
north O O
of O O
Mobile O B-LOC
in O O
1860 O O
by O O
Africans O B-LOC
from O O
Ghana B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
transported O O
illegally O O
as O O
slaves O O
to O O
Mobile O B-LOC
decades O O
after O O
the O O
end O O
of O O
the O O
slave O O
trade O O
. O O

The O O
Battle B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Naseby I-MISC I-MISC
was O O
a O O
decisive O O
engagement O O
of O O
the O O
English B-MISC B-MISC
Civil I-MISC I-MISC
War I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
fought O O
on O O
14 O O
June O O
1645 O O
between O O
the O O
main O O
Royalist O B-ORG
army O O
of O O
King B-PER B-PER
Charles I-PER B-PER
I O I-PER
and O O
the O O
Parliamentarian O B-ORG
New B-ORG I-ORG
Model I-ORG I-ORG
Army I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
commanded O O
by O O
Sir O O
Thomas B-PER B-PER
Fairfax I-PER I-PER
and O O
Oliver B-PER B-PER
Cromwell I-PER I-PER
. O O

A O O
former O O
German B-ORG B-ORG
Air I-ORG I-ORG
Force I-ORG I-ORG
colonel O O
and O O
a O O
spokesperson O O
for O O
the O O
far O O
- O O
right O O
Deutschland O B-ORG
- O I-ORG
Bewegung O I-ORG
, O O
Mechtersheimer O B-PER
is O O
known O O
for O O
his O O
protest O O
against O O
Germany O B-LOC
's O O
participation O O
in O O
NATO B-ORG B-ORG
. O O

Columbia B-LOC B-LOC
Island I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
an O O
island O O
located O O
in O O
the O O
Potomac B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
in O O
Washington O B-LOC
, O O
D.C. O B-LOC
, O O
in O O
the O O
United O B-LOC
States O I-LOC
. O O

Duluth B-ORG B-ORG
High I-ORG I-ORG
School I-ORG I-ORG
is O O
a O O
public O O
secondary O O
school O O
in O O
Duluth O B-ORG
, O O
a O O
suburb O O
of O O
Atlanta B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Georgia O B-LOC
, O O
United O B-LOC
States O I-LOC
. O O

Universitetskaya O B-LOC
Embankment O I-LOC
( O O
Russian O O
: O O
Университетская O O
набережная O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
1.2 O O
km O O
long O O
embankment O O
on O O
the O O
right O O
bank O O
of O O
the O O
Bolshaya O B-LOC
Neva O I-LOC
, O O
on O O
Vasilievsky O B-LOC
Island O I-LOC
in O O
Saint B-LOC B-LOC
Petersburg I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Russia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Barry B-PER B-PER
Alexander I-PER I-PER
Brown I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
2 O O
November O O
1960 O O
in O O
Warrington B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Cheshire O B-LOC
) O O
is O O
an O O
English O B-LOC
born O O
- O O
American O B-LOC
film O O
director O O
and O O
editor O O
. O O

She O O
went O O
on O O
to O O
win O O
the O O
Golden B-MISC O
Globe I-MISC O
Award I-MISC O
for O O
Best O O
Supporting O O
Actress O O
on O O
Television O O
for O O
" O O
Alice O B-PER
" O O
( O O
1980–81 O O
) O O
, O O
and O O
to O O
receive O O
Academy O B-MISC
Award O I-MISC
nominations O O
for O O
" O O
Wild B-MISC B-MISC
at I-MISC I-MISC
Heart I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1990 O O
) O O
and O O
" O O
Rambling B-MISC B-MISC
Rose I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
1991 O O
) O O
. O O

Wilshire O B-LOC
Grand O I-LOC
Center O I-LOC
is O O
a O O
335.3 O O
m O O
skyscraper O O
in O O
the O O
Financial B-LOC B-LOC
District I-LOC I-LOC
of O O
Downtown O B-LOC
Los B-LOC I-LOC
Angeles I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
California B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Students O O
hail O O
from O O
the O O
townships O O
of O O
Alexandria B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Holland B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Kingwood O B-LOC
along O O
with O O
the O O
boroughs O O
of O O
Frenchtown O B-LOC
and O O
Milford O B-LOC
. O O

Jeff O B-PER
Davis O I-PER
( O O
born O O
Jefferson O B-PER
Davis O I-PER
; O O
May O O
6 O O
, O O
1862 O O
– O O
January O O
3 O O
, O O
1913 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Democratic O B-ORG
politician O O
who O O
served O O
as O O
the O O
20th O O
Governor O O
of O O
Arkansas B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
1901 O O
to O O
1907 O O
and O O
in O O
the O O
United B-ORG B-ORG
States I-ORG I-ORG
Senate I-ORG I-ORG
from O O
1907 O O
to O O
1913 O O
. O O

Rashtriya B-ORG B-ORG
Samajwadi I-ORG I-ORG
Congress I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
RSC O B-ORG
) O O
( O O
National O B-ORG
Socialist O I-ORG
Congress O I-ORG
) O O
was O O
a O O
political O O
party O O
in O O
the O O
Indian O B-LOC
state O O
of O O
West B-LOC B-LOC
Bengal I-LOC I-LOC
from O O
1986 O O
to O O
1989 O O
. O O

Domitian B-PER B-PER
( O O
; O O
Latin B-MISC O
: O O
" O O
Titus B-PER B-PER
Flavius O O
Caesar O O
Domitianus O O
Augustus O B-PER
" O O
; O O
24 O O
October O O
51 O O
– O O
18 O O
September O O
96 O O
) O O
was O O
Roman O B-LOC
emperor O O
from O O
81 O O
to O O
96 O O
. O O

She O O
and O O
her O O
family O O
arrived O O
to O O
Mexico B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
1938 O O
from O O
Europe O B-LOC
and O O
she O O
studied O O
art O O
at O O
the O O
Escuela O B-ORG
Nacional O I-ORG
de O I-ORG
Pintura O I-ORG
, O I-ORG
Escultura O I-ORG
y O I-ORG
Grabado O I-ORG
" O I-ORG
La B-LOC I-ORG
Esmeralda I-LOC I-ORG
" O I-ORG
, O O
where O O
she O O
met O O
and O O
became O O
friends O O
with O O
Frida B-PER B-PER
Kahlo I-PER I-PER
. O O

Régine O B-PER
Hantelle O I-PER
better O O
known O O
by O O
her O O
stage O O
name O O
Anaïs O B-PER
( O O
born O O
1 O O
March O O
1965 O O
in O O
Paris B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
France B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
French O B-LOC
singer O O
. O O
