The O B-MISC
Edict O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
Nantes B-LOC I-MISC
( O O
French O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
édit O B-MISC
de O I-MISC
Nantes B-LOC I-MISC
" O O
) O O
, O O
signed O O
in O O
April O O
1598 O O
by O O
King O O
Henry B-PER B-PER
IV I-PER I-PER
of I-PER O
France I-PER B-LOC
, O O
granted O O
the O O
Calvinist O B-ORG
Protestants O B-ORG
of O O
France B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
Huguenots O B-ORG
) O O
substantial O O
rights O O
in O O
the O O
nation O O
, O O
which O O
was O O
still O O
considered O O
essentially O O
Catholic O B-ORG
at O O
the O O
time O O
. O O

In O O
Greek O B-LOC
mythology O O
, O O
Agamemnon O B-PER
( O O
; O O
Greek O B-LOC
: O O
Ἀγαμέμνων O O
from O O
*Ἀγαμέδμων O O
[ O O
from O O
ἄγαν O O
, O O
" O O
very O O
much O O
" O O
and O O
μέδομαι O O
, O O
" O O
think O O
on O O
" O O
] O O
, O O
" O O
very O O
steadfast O O
" O O
, O O
" O O
unbowed O O
" O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
son O O
of O O
King O O
Atreus O B-PER
and O O
Queen O O
Aerope O B-PER
of O I-PER
Mycenae O I-PER
, O O
the O O
brother O O
of O O
Menelaus B-PER B-PER
, O O
the O O
husband O O
of O O
Clytemnestra O B-PER
and O O
the O O
father O O
of O O
Iphigenia O B-PER
, O O
Electra O B-PER
or O O
Laodike O B-PER
( O O
Λαοδίκη O B-PER
) O O
, O O
Orestes O B-PER
and O O
Chrysothemis O B-PER
. O O

Kashubs O B-ORG
( O O
Kashubian O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
Kaszëbi O O
" O O
; O O
Polish O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
Kaszubi O O
" O O
; O O
German O O
: O O
" O O
Kaschuben O O
" O O
) O O
also O O
spelled O O
as O O
Kaszubians O B-ORG
, O O
Kassubians O B-ORG
, O O
Cassubians O B-ORG
, O O
Cashubes O B-ORG
or O O
Kashubians B-MISC B-ORG
, O O
and O O
formerly O O
known O O
as O O
Kashubes O B-ORG
, O O
are O O
a O O
West O O
Slavic O O
ethnic O O
group O O
in O O
Pomerelia O B-LOC
, O O
north O O
- O O
central O O
Poland B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
House O B-ORG
of O I-ORG
York B-LOC I-ORG
was O O
descended O O
in O O
the O O
male O O
line O O
from O O
Edmund B-PER B-PER
of I-PER I-PER
Langley I-PER I-PER
, I-PER I-PER
1st I-PER I-PER
Duke I-PER I-PER
of I-PER I-PER
York I-PER I-PER
, O O
the O O
fourth O O
surviving O O
son O O
of O O
Edward B-MISC B-PER
III O I-PER
, O O
but O O
also O O
represented O O
Edward B-MISC B-PER
's O O
senior O O
line O O
, O O
being O O
cognatic O O
descendants O O
of O O
Lionel O B-PER
, O O
Duke O B-PER
of O I-PER
Clarence O I-PER
, O O
Edward B-MISC B-PER
III O I-PER
's O O
second O O
surviving O O
son O O
. O O

The O O
Hind O B-MISC
Rattan B-MISC I-MISC
( O O
Hindi B-MISC B-MISC
phrase O O
translated O O
to O O
English O B-MISC
as O O
" O O
Jewel O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
India B-LOC I-MISC
" O O
) O O
is O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
highest O O
Indian O B-LOC
diasporic O O
awards O O
granted O O
annually O O
to O O
non O B-ORG
- O I-ORG
resident O I-ORG
persons O I-ORG
of O I-ORG
Indian O I-ORG
origin O I-ORG
( O O
NRIs O B-ORG
) O O
by O O
the O O
NRI O B-ORG
Welfare O I-ORG
Society O I-ORG
of O I-ORG
India B-LOC I-ORG
. O O

The O O
JEB O B-ORG
's O O
primary O O
field O O
was O O
the O O
Kansai B-LOC B-LOC
region I-LOC O
of O O
South O B-LOC
West O I-LOC
Japan B-LOC I-LOC
and O O
the O O
island O O
of O O
Shikoku B-LOC B-LOC
but O O
missionaries O O
worked O O
among O O
Japanese O B-LOC
living O O
on O O
the O O
West O B-LOC
Coast O I-LOC
of O O
Canada O B-LOC
and O O
the O O
USA O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
in O O
the O O
UK O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Paskačić O B-PER
( O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Serbian O B-LOC
noble O O
house O O
that O O
served O O
the O O
Serbian B-LOC B-LOC
Empire I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
of O O
Dušan O B-PER
the O I-PER
Mighty B-MISC I-PER
( O O
r. O O
1331 O O
- O O
1355 O O
) O O
and O O
Uroš O B-PER
the O I-PER
Weak O I-PER
( O O
r. O O
1355 O O
- O O
1371 O O
) O O
, O O
then O O
the O O
Mrnjavčević O B-PER
" O O
Lordship B-LOC O
of I-LOC O
Prilep I-LOC B-LOC
( O O
1371–1395 O O
) O O
during O O
the O O
" O O
Fall O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Serbian B-LOC I-MISC
Empire I-LOC I-MISC
" O O
. O O

I B-MISC B-MISC
Am I-MISC I-MISC
Curious I-MISC I-MISC
( O I-MISC
Blue B-MISC I-MISC
) O I-MISC
, O O
whose O O
original O O
Swedish O B-LOC
title O O
, O O
Jag O B-MISC
är O I-MISC
nyfiken O I-MISC
– O I-MISC
en O I-MISC
film O I-MISC
i O I-MISC
blått O I-MISC
, O O
translates O O
as O O
" O O
I B-MISC B-MISC
Am I-MISC I-MISC
Curious I-MISC I-MISC
– O I-MISC
A O I-MISC
Film O I-MISC
in O I-MISC
Blue B-MISC I-MISC
, O O
" O O
is O O
a O O
1968 O O
Swedish O B-LOC
film O O
directed O O
by O O
Vilgot O B-PER
Sjöman O I-PER
and O O
starring O O
Lena B-PER B-PER
Nyman I-PER I-PER
as O O
a O O
character O O
named O O
after O O
herself O O
. O O

The O O
Battle B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Talas I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
Battle B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Talas I-MISC I-MISC
River O I-MISC
, O O
or O O
Battle O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
Artlakh O I-MISC
( O O
; O O
Arabic O O
: O O
معركة O O
نهر O O
طلاس‎ O O
‎ O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
military O O
engagement O O
between O O
the O O
Arab O B-ORG
Abbasid B-LOC I-ORG
Caliphate I-LOC I-ORG
along O O
with O O
their O O
ally O O
the O O
Tibetan B-LOC B-ORG
Empire I-LOC I-ORG
against O O
the O O
Chinese O B-ORG
Tang B-LOC I-ORG
dynasty I-LOC I-ORG
, O O
governed O O
at O O
the O O
time O O
by O O
Emperor O O
Xuanzong O B-PER
. O O

After O O
becoming O O
Punjab O B-LOC
President O O
he O O
serves O O
on O O
both O O
the O O
Central O B-ORG
executive O I-ORG
committee O I-ORG
and O O
Core O B-ORG
committee O I-ORG
( O O
Politburo O B-ORG
) O O
Chaudhary O B-PER
's O O
political O O
views O O
are O O
frequently O O
described O O
as O O
moderate O O
, O O
based O O
on O O
the O O
principals O O
of O O
Islam O B-ORG
and O O
of O O
communal O O
tolerance O O
He O O
frequently O O
helps O O
female O O
members O O
of O O
his O O
party O O
by O O
organising O O
protests O O
to O O
condemn O O
the O O
abuse O O
and O O
assault O O
of O O
women O O
in O O
Pakistan B-LOC B-LOC
A O O
bill O O
against O O
Domestic O O
violence O O
had O O
been O O
sent O O
by O O
the O O
Chaudhary O B-PER
to O O
the O O
Punjab O B-ORG
assembly O I-ORG
, O O
which O O
after O O
pending O O
a O O
vote O O
for O O
3 O O
years O O
was O O
approved O O
by O O
the O O
government O O
and O O
opposition O O
Chaudhary O B-PER
is O O
a O O
former O O
deputy O O
mayor O O
of O O
Lahore O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Act O B-MISC
of O I-MISC
Reinstating O I-MISC
Independence B-ORG I-MISC
of O I-MISC
Lithuania B-LOC I-MISC
( O O
Lithuanian O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
Lietuvos O O
Valstybės O O
atkūrimo O O
aktas O O
" O O
) O O
or O O
Act O B-MISC
of O O
February O O
16 O O
was O O
signed O O
by O O
the O O
Council O B-ORG
of O I-ORG
Lithuania B-LOC I-ORG
on O O
February O O
16 O O
, O O
1918 O O
, O O
proclaiming O O
the O O
restoration O O
of O O
an O O
independent O O
State O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Lithuania B-LOC I-LOC
, O O
governed O O
by O O
democratic O O
principles O O
, O O
with O O
Vilnius B-LOC B-LOC
as O O
its O O
capital O O
. O O

India B-LOC B-LOC
has O O
a O O
large O O
diplomatic O O
network O O
, O O
reflecting O O
its O O
links O O
in O O
the O O
world O O
and O O
particularly O O
in O O
neighbouring O O
regions O O
: O O
Central O B-LOC
Asia B-LOC I-LOC
, O O
the O O
Middle O B-LOC
East O I-LOC
, O O
East O B-LOC
Africa B-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Southeast O B-LOC
Asia B-LOC I-LOC
, O O
and O O
the O O
rest O O
of O O
the O O
Indian B-LOC B-LOC
subcontinent I-LOC O
. O O

Students O O
are O O
served O O
from O O
Chesterfield B-LOC B-LOC
Township O I-LOC
, O O
Mansfield B-LOC B-LOC
Township O I-LOC
, O O
North O B-LOC
Hanover B-LOC I-LOC
Township O I-LOC
and O O
Springfield B-LOC B-LOC
Township O I-LOC
, O O
along O O
with O O
children O O
of O O
USAF O B-ORG
personnel O O
based O O
at O O
McGuire B-LOC B-LOC
Air I-LOC I-LOC
Force I-LOC I-LOC
Base I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
Abraham B-PER B-ORG
Lincoln I-PER I-ORG
Bicentennial O I-ORG
Foundation O I-ORG
is O O
the O O
successor O O
organization O O
of O O
the O O
U.S. O B-LOC
Abraham B-PER B-ORG
Lincoln I-PER I-ORG
Bicentennial O I-ORG
Commission O I-ORG
( O O
ALBC O B-ORG
) O O
, O O
which O O
was O O
created O O
by O O
Congress O B-ORG
and O O
the O O
President O O
of O O
the O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
to O O
plan O O
the O O
commemoration O O
of O O
Abraham B-PER B-PER
Lincoln I-PER I-PER
’ O O
s O O
200th O O
birthday O O
in O O
2009 O O
. O O

He O O
studied O O
with O O
Hermon O B-PER
A O I-PER
MacNeil O I-PER
, O O
with O O
work O O
in O O
the O O
Museum B-LOC B-ORG
of I-LOC I-ORG
Modern I-LOC I-ORG
Art I-LOC I-ORG
in O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
City I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
and O O
Gaetano B-MISC B-PER
, O O
known O O
as O O
Guy O B-PER
attended O O
the O O
Beaux O B-ORG
- O I-ORG
Arts O I-ORG
Institute B-ORG I-ORG
of O I-ORG
Design O I-ORG
and O O
the O O
National O B-ORG
Academy O I-ORG
of O I-ORG
Design O I-ORG
. O O

" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Abandonment I-MISC I-MISC
of O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Jews B-MISC I-MISC
" O O
has O O
been O O
well O O
received O O
by O O
most O O
( O O
though O O
not O O
all—see O O
below O O
) O O
historians O O
, O O
and O O
has O O
won O O
numerous O O
prizes O O
and O O
widespread O O
recognition O O
, O O
including O O
" O O
the O O
National O B-MISC
Jewish O I-MISC
Book O I-MISC
Award O I-MISC
, O O
the O O
Anisfield O B-MISC
- O I-MISC
Wolf O I-MISC
Award O I-MISC
, O O
the O O
Present O B-MISC
Tense O I-MISC
Literary O I-MISC
Award O I-MISC
, O O
the O O
Stuart O B-MISC
Bernath O I-MISC
Prize O I-MISC
from O O
the O O
Society O B-ORG
for O I-ORG
Historians O I-ORG
of O I-ORG
American O I-ORG
Foreign O I-ORG
Relations O I-ORG
, O O
and O O
the O O
Theodore O B-MISC
Saloutos O I-MISC
Award O I-MISC
of O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Immigration O I-MISC
History O I-MISC
Society O I-MISC
, O O
and O O
was O O
nominated O O
for O O
the O O
National B-MISC B-MISC
Book I-MISC I-MISC
Critics I-MISC I-MISC
Circle I-MISC I-MISC
Award I-MISC I-MISC
. O O
" O O

Notre B-MISC B-LOC
- I-MISC I-LOC
Dame I-MISC I-LOC
de I-MISC I-LOC
Paris I-MISC I-LOC
( O O
] O O
; O O
meaning O O
" O O
Our O B-LOC
Lady O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
Paris B-LOC I-LOC
" O O
) O O
, O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
Notre O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
Dame O I-LOC
Cathedral O I-LOC
or O O
simply O O
Notre O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
Dame O I-LOC
, O O
is O O
a O O
medieval O O
Catholic O B-ORG
cathedral O O
on O O
the O O
Île O B-LOC
de O I-LOC
la O I-LOC
Cité O I-LOC
in O O
the O O
fourth O O
arrondissement O O
of O O
Paris B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
France O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Technical B-ORG B-ORG
University I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Madrid I-ORG I-ORG
or O O
sometimes O O
called O O
Polytechnic O B-ORG
University O I-ORG
of O I-ORG
Madrid B-MISC I-ORG
( O O
Spanish O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
Universidad O O
Politécnica O O
de O O
Madrid B-MISC B-LOC
" O O
, O O
UPM O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
Spanish O B-LOC
University O O
, O O
located O O
in O O
Madrid B-MISC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Imperial O B-ORG
Brazilian B-ORG I-ORG
Navy I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
Portuguese O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
Armada O B-ORG
Nacional O I-ORG
" O O
, O O
commonly O O
known O O
as O O
" O O
Armada O B-ORG
Imperial O I-ORG
" O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
navy O O
created O O
at O O
the O O
time O O
of O O
the O O
independence O O
of O O
the O O
Empire B-LOC B-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
Brazil I-LOC I-LOC
from O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
Kingdom I-LOC I-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
Portugal I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
Brazil I-LOC B-LOC
and I-LOC O
the I-LOC O
Algarves I-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Andrea B-PER B-PER
Ferrante I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
16 O O
August O O
1968 O O
, O O
Palermo O B-LOC
, O O
Italy O B-LOC
) O O
is O O
an O O
Italian O B-LOC
composer O O
whose O O
music O O
is O O
performed O O
throughout O O
Europe O B-LOC
, O O
Asia O B-LOC
and O O
the O O
Americas O B-LOC
and O O
published O O
by O O
Videoradio O O
and O O
Rai O O
Trade O O
Labels O O
, O O
Edizioni O B-ORG
Carrara O I-ORG
and O O
Edizioni O B-ORG
Simeoli O I-ORG
. O O

Mikhail B-PER B-PER
Epstein I-PER I-PER
is O O
S. O O
C. O O
Dobbs O O
Professor O O
of O O
Cultural O B-MISC
Theory O I-MISC
and O O
Russian O B-MISC
Literature O I-MISC
at O O
Emory O B-ORG
University O I-ORG
, O O
USA O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
Professor O O
of O O
Russian O B-LOC
and O O
Cultural O B-MISC
Theory O I-MISC
at O O
Durham O B-ORG
University O I-ORG
, O O
UK O B-LOC
. O O

Jefferson O B-PER
Joseph O I-PER
DeBlanc O I-PER
( O O
February O O
15 O O
, O O
1921 O O
– O O
November O O
22 O O
, O O
2007 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Cajun O B-LOC
- O O
American O B-LOC
World O B-MISC
War O I-MISC
II O I-MISC
Marine O B-ORG
Corps O I-ORG
fighter O O
pilot O O
and O O
ace O O
— O O
shooting O O
down O O
nine O O
Japanese O B-LOC
aircraft O O
during O O
two O O
tours O O
of O O
duty O O
in O O
the O O
Pacific O B-LOC
at O O
Guadalcanal B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Okinawa O B-LOC
. O O

Barlonyo B-LOC B-LOC
( O O
also O O
Bar O B-LOC
Lonyo O I-LOC
, O O
meaning O O
" O O
field O O
of O O
wealth O O
" O O
in O O
Luo O B-MISC
) O O
is O O
a O O
village O O
in O O
northern O O
Uganda O B-LOC
near O O
Lira O B-LOC
town O I-LOC
, O O
where O O
a O O
number O O
of O O
internally O B-ORG
displaced O I-ORG
people O I-ORG
( O O
IDPs O B-ORG
) O O
from O O
parts O O
of O O
northern O O
Uganda O B-LOC
lived O O
, O O
as O O
a O O
result O O
of O O
a O O
20 O O
- O O
year O O
LRA O B-ORG
insurgency O O
. O O

Istro O B-MISC
- O I-MISC
Romanian O I-MISC
is O O
an O O
Eastern O B-MISC
Romance O I-MISC
language O I-MISC
spoken O O
today O O
in O O
a O O
few O O
villages O O
and O O
hamlets O O
in O O
the O O
peninsula O O
of O O
Istria O B-LOC
, O O
in O O
Croatia B-LOC B-LOC
on O O
the O O
northern O O
Adriatic O O
, O O
as O O
well O O
as O O
in O O
places O O
where O O
the O O
Istro O B-MISC
- O I-MISC
Romanian O I-MISC
people O O
settled O O
after O O
the O O
two O O
world O O
wars O O
, O O
most O O
notably O O
in O O
Italy O B-LOC
, O O
the O O
United O O
States O O
, O O
Canada O O
, O O
Argentina O O
, O O
Bolivia O O
, O O
Chile O O
, O O
Peru O O
, O O
Venezuela O O
, O O
Australia O B-LOC
, O O
Sweden O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
Germany O B-LOC
. O O

" O O
Nuthin B-MISC O
" I-MISC O
but I-MISC O
a I-MISC O
" I-MISC O
G I-MISC O
" I-MISC O
Thang I-MISC O
" O O
reached O O
number O O
two O O
on O O
the O O
" O O
Billboard O B-MISC
" O O
Hot O O
100 O O
, O O
behind O O
" O O
Informer O B-MISC
" O O
by O O
Snow O B-PER
, O O
outperforming O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-ORG
Chronic I-MISC I-ORG
's O O
" O O
other O O
singles O O
, O O
" O O
Fuck B-MISC O
wit I-MISC O
Dre I-MISC B-PER
Day I-MISC O
( O O
And O O
Everybody O O
's O O
Celebratin O O
" O O
) O O
" O O
, O O
which O O
peaked O O
at O O
# O O
8 O O
, O O
and O O
" O O
Let B-MISC B-MISC
Me I-MISC I-MISC
Ride I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
which O O
peaked O O
at O O
# O O
34 O O
. O O

Seattle B-LOC B-ORG
BioMed O I-ORG
's O O
research O O
focuses O O
on O O
four O O
areas O O
of O O
infectious O O
disease O O
: O O
HIV/AIDS B-MISC O
, O O
malaria O B-MISC
, O O
tuberculosis O O
( O O
TB O O
) O O
, O O
and O O
Emerging O B-MISC
& O I-MISC
Neglected O I-MISC
Diseases O I-MISC
( O O
END O B-MISC
) O O
like O O
African O O
sleeping O O
sickness O O
, O O
leishmaniasis O B-MISC
, O O
Chagas B-MISC B-MISC
disease I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
and O O
toxoplasmosis O B-MISC
. O O

Kalix B-LOC B-MISC
( O O
kjœɭɪsmɔːɭɛ O O
/ O O
kölismåle O B-MISC
) O O
is O O
a O O
divergent O O
Swedish O B-MISC
dialect O O
spoken O O
in O O
the O O
Kalix B-LOC B-LOC
Municipality I-LOC I-LOC
along O O
with O O
Sami O B-MISC
, O O
Finnish O B-MISC
, O O
Meänkieli O B-MISC
and O O
the O O
national O O
standard O O
language O O
Swedish O B-MISC
. O O

Rudolf O B-PER
Hieronymus B-MISC I-PER
Eusebius O I-PER
von O I-PER
Colloredo O I-PER
- O I-PER
Waldsee O I-PER
, O O
born O O
November O O
2 O O
, O O
1585 O O
in O O
České O B-LOC
Budějovice O I-LOC
, O O
Kingdom O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Bohemia B-LOC I-LOC
( O O
now O O
in O O
the O O
Czech B-LOC B-LOC
Republic I-LOC I-LOC
) O O
, O O
was O O
a O O
Bohemian O B-ORG
nobleman O O
and O O
the O O
brother O O
of O O
Hieronymus B-MISC B-PER
von O I-PER
Colloredo O I-PER
- O I-PER
Waldsee O I-PER
. O O

Khan O B-PER
Tervel O I-PER
( O O
Bulgarian O B-LOC
: O O
Тервел O O
) O O
also O O
called O O
" O O
Tarvel O B-PER
" O O
, O O
or O O
" O O
Terval O B-PER
" O O
, O O
or O O
" O O
Terbelis O B-PER
" O O
in O O
some O O
Byzantine O B-LOC
sources O O
, O O
was O O
the O O
Khan O O
of O O
Bulgaria B-LOC B-LOC
during O O
the O O
First B-LOC O
Bulgarian I-LOC B-LOC
Empire I-LOC O
at O O
the O O
beginning O O
of O O
the O O
8th O O
century O O
. O O

The O O
game O O
was O O
published O O
by O O
the O O
Japanese O B-LOC
video O O
game O O
developer O O
Enix B-ORG B-ORG
( O O
now O O
Square B-ORG O
Enix I-ORG B-ORG
) O O
in O O
Japan O B-LOC
and O O
brought O O
to O O
the O O
U.S. O B-LOC
by O O
now O O
- O O
defunct O O
989 B-ORG O
Studios I-ORG O
and O O
SCEE O B-ORG
in O O
Europe O B-LOC
. O O

He O O
has O O
also O O
directed O O
two O O
prominent O O
episodes O O
of O O
US O B-LOC
television O O
series O O
" O O
Game B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Thrones I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
: O O
" O O
Blackwater O B-MISC
" O O
and O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Watchers I-MISC I-MISC
on O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Wall O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
with O O
particular O O
acclaim O O
for O O
his O O
direction O O
on O O
both O O
occasions O O
, O O
as O O
well O O
as O O
a O O
nomination O O
for O O
a O O
Primetime B-MISC B-MISC
Emmy I-MISC I-MISC
Award I-MISC I-MISC
for I-MISC O
Outstanding I-MISC O
Directing I-MISC O
for I-MISC O
a I-MISC O
Drama I-MISC O
Series I-MISC O
for O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Watchers I-MISC I-MISC
on O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Wall O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Leslie O B-PER
Mynard O I-PER
( O O
19 O O
December O O
1925 O O
– O O
25 O O
July O O
2008 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
English O B-LOC
footballer O O
who O O
appeared O O
in O O
the O O
Football B-ORG B-ORG
League I-ORG I-ORG
for O O
Wolverhampton B-LOC B-ORG
Wanderers O I-ORG
, O O
Derby B-LOC B-LOC
County O I-LOC
and O O
Scunthorpe B-LOC B-ORG
United O I-ORG
. O O

The B-MISC O
Sorcerer I-MISC B-MISC
's O I-MISC
Hat O I-MISC
was O O
the O O
icon O O
of O O
Disney O B-ORG
's O O
Hollywood B-LOC B-ORG
Studios O I-ORG
, O O
the O O
third O O
of O O
four O O
theme O O
parks O O
built O O
at O O
the O O
Walt B-ORG B-LOC
Disney I-ORG I-LOC
World I-ORG I-LOC
Resort O I-LOC
in O O
Bay O B-LOC
Lake O I-LOC
, O O
Florida B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
from O O
2001 O O
to O O
2015 O O
. O O

Cape O B-LOC
Enrage O I-LOC
is O O
the O O
name O O
given O O
to O O
the O O
southern O O
tip O O
of O O
Barn O B-LOC
Marsh B-LOC I-LOC
Island I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
an O O
island O O
located O O
in O O
Albert B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
New I-LOC B-LOC
Brunswick I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
roughly O O
half O O
way O O
along O O
the O O
coastline O O
between O O
the O O
villages O O
of O O
Riverside O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
Albert O I-LOC
and O O
Alma O B-LOC
at O O
the O O
eastern O O
entrance O O
to O O
Fundy B-LOC B-LOC
National I-LOC I-LOC
Park I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
Valdivia B-LOC B-ORG
Expedition O I-ORG
, O O
or O O
" O O
Deutschen O B-ORG
Tiefsee O I-ORG
- O I-ORG
Expedition O I-ORG
" O O
( O O
German O B-ORG
Deep O I-ORG
Sea O I-ORG
Expedition O I-ORG
) O O
, O O
was O O
a O O
scientific O O
expedition O O
organised O O
and O O
funded O O
by O O
the O O
German B-LOC B-LOC
Empire I-LOC I-LOC
under O O
Kaiser B-PER B-PER
Wilhelm I-PER I-PER
II O I-PER
and O O
was O O
named O O
after O O
the O O
ship O O
which O O
was O O
bought O O
and O O
outfitted O O
for O O
the O O
expedition O O
, O O
the O O
SS O B-MISC
Valdivia B-LOC I-MISC
. O O

It O O
is O O
a O O
collaboration O O
among O O
the O O
Istituto O B-ORG
di O I-ORG
Radioastronomia O I-ORG
di O I-ORG
Bologna B-LOC I-ORG
, O O
the O O
Cagliari B-LOC B-ORG
Observatory B-MISC I-ORG
( O O
Cagliari B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
and O O
the O O
Arcetri O B-ORG
Astrophysical O I-ORG
Observatory B-MISC I-ORG
( O O
Florence O B-LOC
) O O
. O O

Tyre O B-LOC
( O O
Arabic O O
: O O
صور‎ O O
‎ O O
, O O
" O O
Ṣūr O B-LOC
" O O
; O O
Phoenician O B-LOC
: O O
𐤑𐤅𐤓 O O
, O O
" O O
Ṣur O O
" O O
; O O
Hebrew O O
: O O
צוֹר‎ O O
, O O
" O O
Tsor O O
" O O
; O O
Tiberian O O
Hebrew O O
, O O
" O O
Ṣōr O O
" O O
; O O
Akkadian O O
: O O
, O O
" O O
Ṣurru O O
" O O
; O O
Greek O B-MISC
: O O
Τύρος O O
, O O
" O O
Týros O O
" O O
; O O
Turkish O O
: O O
" O O
Sur O O
" O O
; O O
Latin B-MISC O
: O O
" O O
Tyrus O O
" O O
, O O
Armenian O O
Տիր O O
[ O O
Dir O O
] O O
) O O
, O O
sometimes O O
romanized O O
as O O
Sour O B-LOC
, O O
is O O
a O O
city O O
in O O
the O O
South B-LOC O
Governorate I-LOC O
of O O
Lebanon B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Kamal B-PER B-PER
Khujandi I-PER I-PER
( O O
Persian O B-LOC
: O O
کمال O O
خجندی‎ O O
‎ O O
) O O
, O O
also O O
Kamal O B-PER
Khojandi O I-PER
, O O
Kamaleddin O B-PER
Khojandi O I-PER
, O O
or O O
Kamal O B-PER
- O I-PER
E O I-PER
Khojandi O I-PER
, O O
was O O
a O O
Persian O B-LOC
Sufi O B-ORG
and O O
Persian O B-LOC
ghazal O O
poet O O
of O O
the O O
14th O O
century O O
( O O
8th O O
century O O
hijri O O
) O O
. O O

The O O
anti O O
- O O
Roman O B-LOC
alliance O O
was O O
led O O
by O O
Arminius B-PER B-PER
, O O
a O O
Germanic O B-LOC
officer O O
of O O
Varus O B-PER
" O O
auxilia O O
who O O
had O O
acquired O O
Roman O B-LOC
citizenship O O
and O O
had O O
received O O
a O O
Roman O B-LOC
military O O
education O O
, O O
thus O O
enabling O O
him O O
to O O
deceive O O
the O O
Roman O B-LOC
commander O O
methodically O O
and O O
anticipate O O
the O O
Roman O B-LOC
army O O
's O O
tactical O O
responses O O
. O O

Currently O O
, O O
Springfield B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
section O O
of O O
this O O
park O O
is O O
3.7 O O
miles O O
long O O
, O O
running O O
from O O
Chicopee B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Massachusetts I-LOC B-LOC
to O O
the O O
South O B-LOC
End O I-LOC
Bridge O I-LOC
in O O
Springfield B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Massachusetts I-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Hinduism O B-ORG
in O O
Los B-LOC B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC I-LOC
made O O
its O O
first O O
significant O O
impact O O
in O O
the O O
late O O
19th O O
century O O
when O O
wandering O O
Hindu O B-ORG
monk O O
Swami B-MISC B-PER
Vivekananda I-MISC I-PER
( O O
1863 O O
–1902 O O
) O O
, O O
a O O
disciple O O
of O O
Ramakrishna B-PER B-PER
Paramahamsa O I-PER
, O O
came O O
on O O
his O O
second O O
visit O O
to O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
. O O

Arlington O B-LOC
is O O
a O O
census O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
designated O I-LOC
place O I-LOC
( O O
CDP O B-LOC
) O O
in O O
the O O
towns O O
of O O
Arlington O B-LOC
and O O
Sunderland O B-LOC
, O O
Bennington O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
Vermont B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
United O B-LOC
States O I-LOC
. O O

Three O O
days O O
after O O
the O O
album O O
's O O
release O O
, O O
the O O
band O O
's O O
chartered O O
airplane O O
crashed O O
en O O
route O O
to O O
Baton B-LOC B-LOC
Rouge I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
Louisiana I-LOC B-LOC
, O O
killing O O
the O O
pilot O O
, O O
co O O
- O O
pilot O O
, O O
the O O
group O O
's O O
assistant O O
road O O
- O O
manager O O
and O O
three O O
band O O
members O O
( O O
Van B-ORG B-PER
Zant I-ORG I-PER
, O O
Gaines O B-PER
, O O
and O O
Gaines O B-PER
" O O
older O O
sister O O
, O O
backup O O
singer O O
Cassie B-PER B-PER
Gaines I-PER I-PER
) O O
, O O
and O O
severely O O
injuring O O
most O O
who O O
survived O O
the O O
crash O O
. O O

The O O
National O B-ORG
Socialist O I-ORG
Freedom O I-ORG
Movement O I-ORG
( O O
German O O
: O O
" O O
Nationalsozialistische O O
Freiheitsbewegung O O
" O O
or O O
" O O
NSFB O B-ORG
" O O
) O O
or O O
National O B-ORG
Socialist O I-ORG
Freedom O I-ORG
Party O I-ORG
( O O
German O O
: O O
" O O
Nationalsozialistische O O
Freiheitspartei O O
" O O
, O O
or O O
" O O
NSFP O B-ORG
" O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
far O O
- O O
right O O
political O O
party O O
in O O
Weimar B-LOC B-LOC
Germany B-LOC I-LOC
created O O
in O O
April O O
1924 O O
during O O
the O O
aftermath O O
of O O
the O O
Beer B-MISC B-MISC
Hall I-MISC I-MISC
Putsch I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

Prior O O
to O O
current O O
assignment O O
, O O
he O O
served O O
as O O
the O O
Commanding O O
General O O
of O O
U.S. O B-ORG
Marine O I-ORG
Corps O I-ORG
Forces O I-ORG
Command O I-ORG
( O O
MARFORCOM O B-ORG
) O O
; O O
Commanding O O
General O O
, O O
Fleet B-ORG B-ORG
Marine I-ORG I-ORG
Force I-ORG I-ORG
Atlantic O I-ORG
( O O
FMFlant O B-ORG
) O O
; O O
Commander O O
, O O
U.S. O B-ORG
Marine O I-ORG
Corps O I-ORG
Forces O I-ORG
Europe B-LOC I-ORG
, O O
as O O
well O O
as O O
II B-ORG B-ORG
Marine I-ORG I-ORG
Expeditionary I-ORG I-ORG
Force I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

He O O
is O O
Singapore B-LOC B-LOC
's O O
longest O O
- O O
serving O O
Opposition O O
Member O B-ORG
of O I-ORG
Parliament O B-ORG
( O O
MP O B-ORG
) O O
in O O
a O O
Single O B-ORG
Member O I-ORG
Constituency O I-ORG
( O O
SMC O B-ORG
) O O
, O O
having O O
represented O O
the O O
constituency O O
of O O
Potong O B-LOC
Pasir O I-LOC
in O O
Parliament O B-ORG
from O O
1984 O O
to O O
2011 O O
. O O

The O O
Peter O B-LOC
Guice O I-LOC
Memorial B-LOC I-LOC
Bridge I-LOC I-LOC
consists O O
of O O
dual O O
two O O
- O O
lane O O
automobile O O
bridges O O
carrying O O
I O O
- O O
26/US O O
74 O O
across O O
the O O
Green B-ORG B-LOC
River I-ORG I-LOC
, O O
located O O
between O O
East O B-LOC
Flat O I-LOC
Rock O I-LOC
and O O
Saluda O B-LOC
, O O
in O O
Henderson O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
North B-LOC B-LOC
Carolina I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Munyoro B-PER B-PER
Nyamau I-PER I-PER
( O O
" O O
Hezekiah O B-PER
Munyoro B-PER I-PER
Nyamau I-PER I-PER
; O O
" O O
born O O
December O O
5 O O
, O O
1942 O O
or O O
December O O
6 O O
, O O
1938 O O
in O O
Riangombe O B-LOC
Nene O I-LOC
, O O
in O O
Nyaribari O B-LOC
Chache O I-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
former O O
Kenyan O B-LOC
athlete O O
and O O
winner O O
of O O
the O O
gold O O
medal O O
in O O
the O O
4 O O
× O O
400 O O
m O O
relay O O
at O O
the O O
1972 B-MISC O
Summer I-MISC B-MISC
Olympics I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

It O O
is O O
located O O
at O O
the O O
junction O O
of O O
Thames B-LOC B-LOC
River I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Trout O B-LOC
Creek O I-LOC
, O O
southwest O O
of O O
Stratford O B-LOC
, O O
surrounded O O
by O O
the O O
Township O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Perth B-LOC I-LOC
South O I-LOC
and O O
located O O
in O O
Perth B-LOC B-LOC
County I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
Ontario I-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
RATP B-ORG B-ORG
Group I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
French O B-MISC
: O O
Groupe O B-ORG
RATP O I-ORG
) O O
, O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
the O O
Régie O B-ORG
Autonome O I-ORG
des O I-ORG
Transports O I-ORG
Parisiens O I-ORG
( O O
English O B-MISC
: O O
Autonomous O B-ORG
Operator O I-ORG
of O I-ORG
Parisian O I-ORG
Transports O I-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
state O O
- O O
owned O O
public O O
transport O O
operator O O
headquartered O O
in O O
Paris O B-LOC
, O O
France O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Los B-LOC B-ORG
Angeles I-LOC I-ORG
Kiss O I-ORG
( O O
stylized O O
as O O
LA O B-ORG
KISS O I-ORG
) O O
were O O
a O O
professional O O
arena O O
football O O
team O O
based O O
in O O
Anaheim B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
California I-LOC B-LOC
, O O
and O O
members O O
of O O
the O O
Arena B-ORG B-ORG
Football I-ORG I-ORG
League I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
AFL O B-ORG
) O O
. O O

Zemina B-ORG B-ORG
( O O
Korean O B-MISC
: O O
재미나 O B-ORG
, O O
originally O O
제미나 O B-ORG
) O O
was O O
a O O
South O B-LOC
Korean O I-LOC
software O O
maker O O
brand O O
of O O
Saehan O B-ORG
Trading O I-ORG
( O O
Korean O B-MISC
: O O
새한 O B-ORG
상사 O I-ORG
) O O
founded O O
in O O
1981 O O
. O O

The O O
popularity O O
of O O
this O O
conception O O
of O O
Tajik O B-MISC
as O O
a O O
variety O O
of O O
Persian O B-MISC
was O O
such O O
that O O
, O O
during O O
the O O
period O O
in O O
which O O
Tajik O B-MISC
intellectuals O O
were O O
trying O O
to O O
establish O O
Tajik O B-MISC
as O O
a O O
language O O
separate O O
from O O
Persian O B-MISC
, O O
Sadriddin B-PER B-PER
Ayni I-PER I-PER
, O O
who O O
was O O
a O O
prominent O O
intellectual O O
and O O
educator O O
, O O
had O O
to O O
make O O
a O O
statement O O
that O O
Tajik O B-MISC
was O O
not O O
a O O
bastardized O O
dialect O O
of O O
Persian O B-MISC
. O O

Catoosa O B-LOC
Wildlife O I-LOC
Management O I-LOC
Area O I-LOC
is O O
a O O
large O O
game O O
- O O
management O O
area O O
on O O
the O O
Upper O B-LOC
Cumberland O I-LOC
Plateau O I-LOC
in O O
Morgan O B-LOC
, O O
Cumberland O B-LOC
and O O
Fentress O B-LOC
counties O O
in O O
Tennessee B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
the O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
feature O O
was O O
named O O
by O O
the O O
New B-LOC B-ORG
Zealand I-LOC I-ORG
Geological O I-ORG
Survey O I-ORG
Antarctic O I-ORG
Expedition O I-ORG
( O O
NZGSAE O B-ORG
) O O
, O O
1958–59 O O
, O O
for O O
Captain O O
William O B-PER
M. O I-PER
Hawkes O I-PER
, O O
U.S. O B-ORG
Navy O I-ORG
, O O
who O O
took O O
a O O
leading O O
part O O
in O O
early O O
air O O
operations O O
from O O
Williams B-LOC B-LOC
Field I-LOC I-LOC
near O O
McMurdo O B-LOC
Station O I-LOC
, O O
including O O
long O O
range O O
photo O O
reconnaissance O O
and O O
supply O O
flights O O
, O O
and O O
the O O
first O O
air O O
landing O O
at O O
the O O
South O B-LOC
Pole O I-LOC
. O O

It O O
was O O
the O O
start O O
of O O
the O O
transition O O
period O O
toward O O
reunification O O
, O O
which O O
occurred O O
in O O
the O O
national O O
election O O
for O O
national O O
reunification O O
on O O
July O O
2 O O
, O O
1976 O O
, O O
when O O
the O O
Provisional B-LOC B-ORG
Revolutionary I-LOC I-ORG
Government I-LOC I-ORG
of I-LOC O
the I-LOC O
Republic I-LOC B-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
South I-LOC I-LOC
Vietnam I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
Democratic O B-LOC
Republic O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
Vietnam B-LOC I-LOC
merged O O
to O O
form O O
the O O
modern O O
- O O
day O O
Vietnam B-LOC B-LOC
or O O
the O O
Socialist O B-LOC
Republic O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
Vietnam B-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Rose B-PER B-PER
Kennedy I-PER I-PER
( O O
also O O
commonly O O
known O O
as O O
a O O
" O O
VSS O B-MISC
, O O
" O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
Michele O I-MISC
, O O
" O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
White O I-MISC
Girl O I-MISC
, O O
" O O
or O O
" O O
vodka O B-MISC
soda O I-MISC
splash O I-MISC
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
cocktail O O
popular O O
in O O
the O O
mid O O
- O O
Atlantic O B-LOC
and O O
Northeastern O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

El O B-MISC
Niño O I-MISC
( O O
] O O
) O O
is O O
the O O
warm O O
phase O O
of O O
the O O
El O B-MISC
Niño O I-MISC
Southern O I-MISC
Oscillation O I-MISC
( O O
commonly O O
called O O
ENSO O B-MISC
) O O
and O O
is O O
associated O O
with O O
a O O
band O O
of O O
warm O O
ocean O O
water O O
that O O
develops O O
in O O
the O O
central O O
and O O
east O O
- O O
central O O
equatorial O O
Pacific O B-LOC
( O O
between O O
approximately O O
the O O
International B-MISC B-LOC
Date O I-LOC
Line O I-LOC
and O O
120°W O O
) O O
, O O
including O O
off O O
the O O
Pacific O B-LOC
coast O O
of O O
South B-LOC B-LOC
America I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

The O O
LCAN O B-ORG
ran O O
strip O O
mining O O
operations O O
in O O
the O O
Panther B-LOC B-LOC
Creek I-LOC I-LOC
Valley O I-LOC
east O O
of O O
Lansford O B-LOC
along O O
U.S. B-LOC B-LOC
Route I-LOC I-LOC
209 I-LOC I-LOC
; O O
with O O
vast O O
properties O O
dominating O O
the O O
coal O O
areas O O
of O O
Tamaqua O B-LOC
, O O
Coaldale O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
Lansford O B-LOC
. O O

John O O
III O O
'Red O O
" O O
Comyn O O
, O O
Lord O O
of O O
Badenoch O B-LOC
and O O
Lord O O
of O O
Lochaber O B-LOC
, O O
also O O
known O O
simply O O
as O O
the O O
Red O B-PER
Comyn O I-PER
( O O
died O O
10 O O
February O O
1306 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Scottish O B-LOC
nobleman O O
who O O
was O O
an O O
important O O
figure O O
in O O
the O O
Wars O O
of O O
Scottish O B-LOC
Independence B-ORG O
, O O
and O O
was O O
Guardian O O
of O O
Scotland B-LOC B-LOC
during O O
the O O
Second O B-MISC
Interregnum O I-MISC
1296–1306 O O
. O O

The O O
Revolutionary B-PER B-ORG
Liberation O I-ORG
Movement O I-ORG
Tupaq O I-ORG
Katari B-LOC I-ORG
( O O
Spanish O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
Movimiento O B-ORG
Revolucionario O I-ORG
Túpac O I-ORG
Katari B-LOC I-ORG
de O I-ORG
Liberación O I-ORG
" O O
, O O
MRTKL O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
left O O
- O O
wing O O
political O O
party O O
in O O
Bolivia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Kelly B-PER B-PER
Williams I-PER I-PER
Brown B-MISC I-PER
( O O
born O O
August O O
6 O O
, O O
1984 O O
in O O
Covington O B-LOC
, O O
Louisiana B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
New B-LOC B-ORG
York I-LOC I-ORG
Times O I-ORG
- O O
bestselling O O
American O B-LOC
writer O O
and O O
author O O
. O O

" O O
Sentiments B-MISC B-MISC
songes I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
( O O
" O O
Liar O B-MISC
feelings O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
portmanteau O O
between O O
" O O
sentiments O O
" O O
and O O
" O O
mensonges O O
" O O
) O O
was O O
the O O
French O B-LOC
entry O O
in O O
the O O
Eurovision B-MISC B-MISC
Song I-MISC I-MISC
Contest I-MISC I-MISC
1997 O I-MISC
, O O
performed O O
in O O
French O B-LOC
by O O
Fanny O B-PER
. O O

Klahhane O B-LOC
Ridge O I-LOC
is O O
located O O
just O O
to O O
the O O
south O O
of O O
Port B-LOC B-LOC
Angeles I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
Washington I-LOC B-LOC
, O O
USA O B-LOC
near O O
Hurricane O B-LOC
Ridge O I-LOC
in O O
the O O
Olympic B-LOC B-LOC
National I-LOC I-LOC
Park I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Allan B-PER B-PER
Octavian I-PER I-PER
Hume I-PER I-PER
, O O
CB O O
ICS O O
( O O
6 O O
June O O
1829 O O
– O O
31 O O
July O O
1912 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
member O O
of O O
the O O
Imperial O B-ORG
Civil B-MISC I-ORG
Service I-MISC I-ORG
( O O
later O O
the O O
Indian O B-ORG
Civil B-MISC I-ORG
Service I-MISC I-ORG
) O O
, O O
a O O
political O O
reformer O O
, O O
ornithologist O O
and O O
botanist O O
who O O
worked O O
in O O
British B-ORG B-LOC
India I-ORG I-LOC
. O O

According O O
to O O
an O O
interview O O
with O O
rhythm O O
guitarist O O
Paul B-PER B-PER
Landers I-PER I-PER
, O O
the O O
sound O O
of O O
the O O
main O O
riff O O
of O O
the O O
song O O
is O O
made O O
by O O
him O O
and O O
lead O O
guitarist O O
Richard B-MISC B-PER
Kruspe B-MISC I-PER
, O O
each O O
playing O O
a O O
similar O O
riff O O
at O O
different O O
octaves O O
( O O
Richard B-MISC B-PER
plays O O
the O O
middle O O
and O O
Paul O B-PER
plays O O
the O O
lower O O
) O O
. O O

Hiroko B-PER O
Nagata I-PER B-PER
( O O
永田 O O
洋子 O O
, O O
Nagata O B-PER
Hiroko B-MISC O
, O O
February O O
8 O O
, O O
1945 O O
– O O
February O O
5 O O
, O O
2011 O O
) O O
, O O
sometimes O O
mistakenly O O
referred O O
to O O
as O O
Yōko O B-PER
Nagata O I-PER
, O O
was O O
a O O
Japanese O B-LOC
leftist O O
radical O O
who O O
was O O
convicted O O
of O O
murder O O
and O O
sentenced O O
to O O
death O O
in O O
Japan B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Mount B-LOC B-LOC
Carmel I-LOC I-LOC
Cemetery O I-LOC
is O O
a O O
Roman O B-ORG
Catholic O I-ORG
cemetery O O
located O O
in O O
the O O
Chicago B-LOC B-LOC
suburb O O
of O O
Hillside B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Illinois I-LOC B-LOC
. O O

It O O
begins O O
in O O
the O O
Alaska B-LOC B-LOC
Range I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
flows O O
southwest O O
450 O O
km O O
to O O
Nushagak O B-LOC
Bay O I-LOC
, O O
an O O
inlet O O
of O O
Bristol B-LOC B-LOC
Bay O I-LOC
, O O
east O O
of O O
Dillingham B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Alaska I-LOC B-LOC
. O O

It O O
is O O
located O O
10 O O
km O O
east O O
of O O
the O O
CBD O O
, O O
and O O
borders O O
Belmont O B-LOC
, O O
Carina O B-LOC
, O O
Carina O B-LOC
Heights O I-LOC
, O O
Mackenzie O B-LOC
, O O
Mansfield B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Mount O B-LOC
Gravatt O I-LOC
East O I-LOC
, O O
and O O
Tingalpa O B-LOC
. O O

Enclave O B-MISC
is O O
a O O
third O O
- O O
person O O
3D O B-MISC
action O O
role O O
- O O
playing O O
game O O
by O O
Starbreeze B-ORG B-ORG
Studios I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
released O O
for O O
Microsoft B-MISC B-ORG
Windows I-MISC B-MISC
and O O
Xbox O B-MISC
on O O
July O O
19 O O
, O O
2002 O O
. O O

Ernie B-PER B-PER
Copland I-PER I-PER
( O O
15 O O
April O O
1927 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Scottish O B-LOC
footballer O O
who O O
played O O
for O O
Arbroath B-LOC B-ORG
, O O
Dundee B-LOC B-ORG
and O O
Raith O B-ORG
Rovers O I-ORG
. O O

Dos B-LOC B-ORG
Reales I-LOC I-ORG
is O O
a O O
Mexican O B-LOC
restaurant O O
chain O O
found O O
in O O
the O O
Midwest O B-LOC
and O O
Great B-LOC B-LOC
Plains I-LOC I-LOC
of O O
the O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Wodehouse O B-PER
, O O
first O O
published O O
in O O
the O O
United O B-LOC
Kingdom O I-LOC
on O O
16 O O
March O O
1934 O O
by O O
Herbert O B-PER
Jenkins O I-PER
, O O
London O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
in O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
on O O
23 O O
April O O
1934 O O
by O O
Little B-ORG B-ORG
, I-ORG I-ORG
Brown I-ORG I-ORG
and I-ORG I-ORG
Company I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
New O B-LOC
York O I-LOC
. O O

Robertson O B-LOC
Land O I-LOC
in O O
Antarctica B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
including O O
the O O
Athos O B-LOC
Range O I-LOC
, O O
the O O
Porthos B-PER B-LOC
Range O I-LOC
, O O
and O O
the O O
Aramis B-PER B-LOC
Range O I-LOC
. O O

Zhang B-PER B-PER
Zuo I-PER I-PER
( O O
; O O
died O O
355 O O
) O O
, O O
courtesy O O
name O O
Taibo O B-PER
( O O
太伯 O B-PER
) O O
, O O
formally O O
Prince O B-PER
Wei O I-PER
of O I-PER
( O I-PER
Former O I-PER
) O I-PER
Liang O I-PER
( O O
( O O
前 O O
) O O
涼威王 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
ruler O O
of O O
the O O
Chinese O B-LOC
state O O
Former B-LOC B-ORG
Liang I-LOC I-ORG
. O O

She O O
was O O
subsequently O O
invited O O
to O O
produce O O
a O O
cake O O
for O O
the O O
90th O O
birthday O O
celebrations O O
of O O
Queen O B-PER
Elizabeth B-PER B-PER
II I-PER I-PER
and O O
has O O
presented O O
her O O
own O O
BBC O B-ORG
documentary O O
, O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-MISC
Chronicles I-MISC I-MISC
of O I-MISC
Nadiya O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
a O O
TV O O
cookery O O
series O O
, O O
" O O
Nadiya O B-MISC
's O I-MISC
British O I-MISC
Food O I-MISC
Adventure O I-MISC
" O O
and O O
co O O
- O O
presents O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
Big O I-MISC
Family O I-MISC
Cooking O I-MISC
Showdown O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Joel B-PER B-PER
Mandelstam I-PER I-PER
FRS O I-PER
( O O
13 O O
November O O
1919 O O
– O O
20 O O
December O O
2008 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
British O B-LOC
microbiologist O O
, O O
a O O
Professor O O
, O O
at O O
the O O
University B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Oxford I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
and O O
a O O
Fellow O O
of O O
Linacre B-ORG B-ORG
College I-ORG I-ORG
, I-ORG O
Oxford I-ORG B-ORG
. O O

He O O
started O O
writing O O
in O O
" O O
Mathrubhumi B-MISC B-MISC
" O O
and O O
" O O
Chandrika O B-MISC
" O O
, O O
and O O
later O O
became O O
a O O
regular O O
columnist O O
of O O
" O O
Mathrubhumi B-MISC B-MISC
Illustrated O I-MISC
Weekly O I-MISC
" O O
along O O
with O O
Cynic O B-PER
and O O
Nadirsha O B-PER
( O O
TMP O B-PER
Nedungadi O I-PER
) O O
. O O

Ger O B-ORG
, O O
or O O
Gur O B-ORG
( O O
or O O
Gerrer O B-ORG
when O O
used O O
as O O
an O O
adjective O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
Hasidic O B-ORG
dynasty O O
originating O O
from O O
Ger O B-ORG
, O O
the O O
Yiddish O O
name O O
of O O
Góra O B-LOC
Kalwaria O I-LOC
, O O
a O O
small O O
town O O
in O O
Poland B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Japan B-ORG B-ORG
Evangelistic I-ORG I-ORG
Band I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
JEB O B-ORG
) O O
, O O
or O O
'Kyodan O O
Nihon O O
Dendo O O
Tai O O
" O O
( O O
日本伝道隊 O B-ORG
) O O
in O O
Japanese O B-LOC
, O O
is O O
an O O
evangelical O O
Christian O B-ORG
group O O
founded O O
in O O
England O B-LOC
in O O
1903 O O
with O O
the O O
original O O
aim O O
to O O
" O O
" O O
initiate O O
and O O
sustain O O
evangelistic O O
work O O
among O O
Japanese O B-LOC
wherever O O
they O O
are O O
found O O
" O O
" O O
. O O

Ruslan O B-PER
Albiertavič O I-PER
Saliej O I-PER
( O O
Belarusian O B-LOC
: O O
Руслан O B-PER
Альбертавіч O I-PER
Салей O I-PER
; O O
November O O
2 O O
, O O
1974 O O
– O O
September O O
7 O O
, O O
2011 O O
) O O
, O O
better O O
known O O
as O O
Ruslan B-PER B-PER
Salei I-PER I-PER
( O O
Russian O B-MISC
: O O
Руслан O B-PER
Альбертович O I-PER
Салей O I-PER
) O O
, O O
was O O
a O O
Belarusian O B-LOC
professional O O
ice O O
hockey O O
player O O
. O O

The B-MISC O
Moneypenny I-MISC B-MISC
Diaries I-MISC I-MISC
: I-MISC I-MISC
Guardian I-MISC I-MISC
Angel I-MISC I-MISC
is O O
the O O
first O O
in O O
a O O
trilogy O O
of O O
novels O O
chronicling O O
the O O
life O O
of O O
Miss O O
Moneypenny O B-PER
, O O
M O B-PER
's O O
personal O O
secretary O O
in O O
Ian B-PER B-PER
Fleming I-PER I-PER
's O O
James B-PER B-MISC
Bond I-PER I-MISC
series O I-MISC
. O O

Olga B-PER B-PER
Yakovlevna I-PER I-PER
Ivanova I-PER I-PER
( O O
Russian O B-MISC
: O O
Ольга O O
Яковлевна O O
Иванова O O
) O O
( O O
born O O
1945 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
career O O
diplomat O O
who O O
is O O
the O O
Ambassador O O
Extraordinary B-MISC O
and O O
Plenipotentiary B-MISC O
of O O
the O O
Russian O B-LOC
Federation O I-LOC
to O O
the O O
Republic O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Mauritius B-LOC I-LOC
. O O

José O B-PER
Rafael B-PER I-PER
Carrera I-PER I-PER
Turcios O I-PER
( O O
24 O O
October O O
1814 O O
Guatemala B-LOC B-LOC
City I-LOC O
– O O
14 O O
April O O
1865 O O
Guatemala B-LOC B-LOC
City I-LOC O
) O O
was O O
the O O
president O O
of O O
Guatemala B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
1844 O O
to O O
1848 O O
and O O
from O O
1851 O O
until O O
his O O
death O O
in O O
1865 O O
, O O
after O O
being O O
appointed O O
President O O
for O O
Life O O
in O O
1854 O O
. O O

Hoàng O B-PER
Diệu O I-PER
( O O
chữ O B-MISC
Hán O I-MISC
: O O
黃耀 O B-PER
, O O
1828 O O
– O O
25 O O
April O O
1882 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Nguyễn O B-ORG
Dynasty O I-ORG
governor O O
of O O
Hanoi B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
on O O
behalf O O
of O O
Emperor O O
Tự O B-PER
Đức O I-PER
, O O
resident O O
in O O
Huế O B-LOC
. O O

Liverpool B-LOC B-ORG
Football O I-ORG
Club O I-ORG
is O O
an O O
English O B-LOC
association O O
football O O
club O O
based O O
in O O
Liverpool B-LOC B-ORG
, O O
Merseyside B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
which O O
competes O O
in O O
the O O
top O O
tier O O
of O O
English O B-LOC
football O O
, O O
for O O
the O O
2015–16 O O
season O O
. O O

Arsen B-PER B-PER
Roulette I-PER I-PER
makes O O
bi O O
- O O
annual O O
pilgrimages O O
to O O
Europe O B-LOC
, O O
frequently O O
headlining O O
Europe O B-LOC
's O O
biggest O O
Rockabilly O B-MISC
events O O
; O O
Summer O B-MISC
Jamboree O I-MISC
, O O
Hemsby O B-MISC
, O O
Screamin O O
" O O
Festival O O
and O O
the O O
Brighton O B-MISC
Rumble O I-MISC
just O O
to O O
name O O
a O O
few O O
. O O

It O O
originated O O
in O O
the O O
Kingdom B-LOC B-LOC
of I-LOC I-LOC
Serbia I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
and O O
was O O
initially O O
awarded O O
exclusively O O
to O O
Serbian O B-LOC
citizens O O
in O O
return O O
for O O
services O O
rendered O O
to O O
the O O
Serbian O B-LOC
monarchy O O
, O O
the O O
Serb O B-LOC
people O O
and O O
the O O
Serbian O B-LOC
state O O
, O O
though O O
it O O
is O O
now O O
bestowed O O
upon O O
Serbs O B-LOC
and O O
non O O
- O O
Serbs O B-LOC
alike O O
. O O

Cagayan B-LOC O
( O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
province O O
of O O
the O O
Philippines B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
the O O
Cagayan B-LOC B-LOC
Valley O I-LOC
region O I-LOC
in O O
the O O
northeast O O
of O O
Luzon B-LOC B-LOC
Island O I-LOC
, O O
and O O
includes O O
the O O
Babuyan O B-LOC
Islands O I-LOC
to O O
the O O
north O O
. O O

Le B-LOC B-LOC
Bernardin I-LOC I-LOC
is O O
a O O
Michelin B-ORG B-MISC
Guide O O
three O O
- O O
star O O
French O B-LOC
seafood O O
restaurant O O
located O O
at O O
155 O O
West O O
51st O O
Street O O
( O O
between O O
6th O O
Avenue O O
and O O
7th O O
Avenue O O
) O O
, O O
in O O
Midtown O B-LOC
Manhattan B-LOC I-LOC
in O O
New O B-LOC
York O I-LOC
City O I-LOC
. O O

The O B-ORG
Lehigh O I-ORG
Coal O I-ORG
and O I-ORG
Navigation O I-ORG
Company O I-ORG
( O O
LCAN O B-ORG
) O O
( O O
1988–2010 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
modern O O
- O O
day O O
anthracite O O
coal O O
mining O O
company O O
headquartered O O
in O O
Pottsville O B-LOC
, O O
Schuylkill O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
, O O
Pennsylvania B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
U.S. O B-LOC
which O O
acquired O O
many O O
of O O
the O O
'Old O O
Company O O
" O O
( O O
LC O O
& O O
N O O
) O O
properties O O
and O O
re O O
- O O
launched O O
the O O
Lehigh O B-ORG
Coal O I-ORG
Companies O I-ORG
brand O O
in O O
1988 O O
. O O

In O O
the O O
Hindu O B-LOC
epic O O
Mahabharata B-MISC B-MISC
, O O
Uttarā O B-PER
or O O
Anglicized O O
as O O
Uttaraa O B-PER
( O O
उत्तरा O B-PER
) O O
was O O
daughter O O
of O O
King O O
Virata O B-PER
and O O
Queen O O
Sudeshna O O
, O O
at O O
whose O O
court O O
the O O
Pandavas O B-ORG
spent O O
a O O
year O O
in O O
concealment O O
during O O
their O O
exile O O
. O O

The O O
chain O O
was O O
a O O
partnership O O
of O O
Buffett O B-PER
's O O
company O O
, O O
the O O
Orlando O B-LOC
, O O
Florida O B-LOC
- O O
based O O
Margaritaville O B-ORG
Holdings O I-ORG
LLC O I-ORG
, O O
and O O
OSI O B-ORG
Restaurant O I-ORG
Partners O I-ORG
, O O
with O O
Buffett O B-PER
licensing O O
the O O
name O O
and O O
Outback B-ORG B-ORG
Steakhouse I-ORG I-ORG
operating O O
the O O
franchising O O
of O O
restaurants O O
. O O

Sneyd O B-PER
was O O
born O O
in O O
Bath O B-LOC
in O O
1751 O O
, O O
and O O
following O O
the O O
death O O
of O O
her O O
mother O O
in O O
1756 O O
was O O
raised O O
by O O
Canon O B-PER
Thomas B-PER I-PER
Seward I-PER I-PER
and O O
his O O
wife O O
Elizabeth O B-PER
in O O
Lichfield B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Staffordshire O B-LOC
until O O
she O O
returned O O
to O O
her O O
father O O
's O O
house O O
in O O
1771 O O
. O O

Jerzy B-MISC B-PER
Kłoczowski O I-PER
( O O
born O O
29 O O
December O O
1924 O O
in O O
Bogdany O B-LOC
, O O
Poland O B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
Polish O B-LOC
historian O O
, O O
professor O O
at O O
the O O
John B-ORG B-ORG
Paul I-ORG I-ORG
II I-ORG I-ORG
Catholic I-ORG I-ORG
University I-ORG I-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Lublin I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
and O O
former O O
member O O
of O O
the O O
Polish O B-ORG
Senate O I-ORG
. O O

Pari O B-PER
Khan O I-PER
Khanum O I-PER
( O O
Persian O O
: O O
پریخان O O
خانم‎ O O
‎ O O
, O O
also O O
spelled O O
Parikhan O B-PER
Khanum O I-PER
) O O
was O O
a O O
Safavid O B-LOC
princess O O
, O O
the O O
daughter O O
of O O
the O O
Safavid O B-LOC
king O O
( O O
shah O O
) O O
Tahmasp B-PER B-PER
I I-PER I-PER
( O O
r. O O
1524 O O
– O O
1576 O O
) O O
and O O
his O O
Circassian O B-LOC
consort O O
, O O
Sultan O B-PER
- O I-PER
Agha O I-PER
Khanum O I-PER
. O O

Sergio O B-PER
Claudio O I-PER
Cirigliano B-LOC I-PER
is O O
an O O
Argentinian O B-LOC
businessman O O
who O O
, O O
with O O
his O O
brother O O
Mario O B-PER
, O O
operates O O
major O O
rail O O
and O O
bus O O
concessions O O
in O O
Buenos B-LOC B-LOC
Aires I-LOC I-LOC
and O O
elsewhere O O
in O O
Argentina O B-LOC
through O O
the O O
Grupo O B-ORG
Plaza O I-ORG
conglomerate O O
. O O

Gonzalo O B-PER
Jiménez O I-PER
de O I-PER
Quesada O I-PER
y O I-PER
Rivera O I-PER
, O O
also O O
spelled O O
as O O
De O B-PER
Quezada O I-PER
and O O
Ximénez O B-PER
, O O
( O O
1496 O O
 O O
- O O
other O O
sources O O
state O O
1506 O O
or O O
1509 O O
Suesca O B-LOC
, O O
16 O O
February O O
1579 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Spanish O B-LOC
explorer O O
and O O
conquistador O O
in O O
northern O O
South O B-LOC
America O I-LOC
, O O
territories O O
currently O O
known O O
as O O
Colombia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

” O O
覚王 O B-MISC
” O O
means O O
Buddha O B-PER
and O O
“ O O
日泰 O B-MISC
” O O
means O O
Japan B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
the O O
Kingdom O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Thailand B-LOC I-LOC
in O O
Japanese O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Imam O B-ORG
Bukhari O I-ORG
Jamaat O I-ORG
( O O
Uzbek O O
: O O
" O O
Imom O O
Buxoriy O O
Katibasi O O
" O O
) O O
is O O
an O O
Islamist O B-ORG
Salafi O I-ORG
group O O
fighting O O
in O O
the O O
Syrian O B-MISC
Civil O I-MISC
War O I-MISC
and O O
the O O
War B-MISC B-MISC
in I-MISC I-MISC
Afghanistan I-MISC I-MISC
, O O
composed O O
of O O
primarily O O
Uzbeks B-MISC B-ORG
, O O
and O O
expressing O O
loyalty O O
to O O
the O O
Taliban O B-ORG
movement O O
. O O

He O O
participated O O
in O O
the O O
military O O
dictatorship O O
known O O
as O O
the O O
National O B-MISC
Reorganisation O I-MISC
Process O I-MISC
( O O
1976–1983 O O
) O O
and O O
, O O
along O O
with O O
Leopoldo O B-PER
Fortunato O I-PER
Galtieri O I-PER
and O O
Jorge B-PER B-PER
Isaac I-PER I-PER
Anaya B-LOC I-PER
, O O
was O O
a O O
member O O
of O O
the O O
Third O B-ORG
Military O I-ORG
Junta O I-ORG
that O O
ruled O O
Argentina B-LOC B-LOC
between O O
1981 O O
and O O
1982 O O
. O O

Edith B-MISC B-PER
Tudor O I-PER
- O I-PER
Hart O I-PER
( O O
née O O
Edith B-MISC B-PER
Suschitzky O I-PER
; O O
1908–1973 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
Austrian O B-LOC
- O O
British O B-LOC
photographer O O
, O O
communist O O
- O O
sympathiser O O
and O O
spy O O
for O O
the O O
Soviet B-LOC B-LOC
Union I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Doublehead B-PER B-PER
( O O
1744–1807 O O
) O O
or O O
Incalatanga O B-PER
( O O
" O O
Tal O B-PER
- O I-PER
tsu'tsa O I-PER
" O O
in O O
Cherokee B-MISC B-PER
) O O
, O O
was O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
most O O
feared O O
warriors O O
of O O
the O O
Cherokee B-MISC B-PER
during O O
the O O
Cherokee–American O O
wars O O
. O O

The B-MISC B-MISC
Abandonment I-MISC I-MISC
of O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Jews B-MISC I-MISC
: O I-MISC
America O I-MISC
and O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Holocaust O I-MISC
1941–1945 O I-MISC
, O O
published O O
in O O
1984 O O
, O O
is O O
an O O
influential O O
book O O
by O O
David B-PER B-PER
S. O I-PER
Wyman O I-PER
, O O
former O O
Josiah O B-PER
DuBois O I-PER
professor O O
of O O
history O O
at O O
the O O
University B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Massachusetts I-ORG I-ORG
Amherst I-ORG I-ORG
. O O

The O O
First B-LOC B-ORG
Baptist I-LOC I-ORG
Church I-LOC I-ORG
of I-LOC I-ORG
Tarrytown I-LOC I-ORG
is O O
located O O
on O O
South O B-LOC
Broadway O I-LOC
( O O
U.S. B-LOC B-LOC
Route I-LOC I-LOC
9 I-LOC I-LOC
) O O
in O O
Tarrytown O B-LOC
, O O
New O B-LOC
York O I-LOC
, O O
United O B-LOC
States O I-LOC
. O O

The O O
firm O O
was O O
chartered O O
as O O
a O O
New B-LOC B-LOC
York I-LOC I-LOC
corporation O O
in O O
1922 O O
by O O
Betty O B-PER
" O I-PER
Bessie O I-PER
" O I-PER
Stastny O I-PER
" O O
( O O
née O O
" O O
Fisher O O
) O O
( O O
1882–1974 O O
) O O
and O O
her O O
husband O O
, O O
Anthony O B-PER
John O I-PER
Stastny O I-PER
( O O
1885–1923 O O
) O O
, O O
and O O
M. O B-PER
Kerr O I-PER
– O O
although O O
, O O
there O O
was O O
music O O
published O O
from O O
as O O
early O O
as O O
1908 O O
bearing O O
the O O
name O O
A. O B-ORG
J. O I-ORG
Stasny O I-ORG
Music O I-ORG
Co. O I-ORG
Cleveland O B-LOC
, O O
Ohio O B-LOC
. O O

Antonio B-PER B-PER
Adamini I-PER I-PER
( O O
December O O
25 O O
, O O
1792 O O
in O O
Bigogno O B-LOC
, O O
Ticino O B-LOC
 O O
- O O
 O O
June O O
16 O O
, O O
1846 O O
, O O
St. B-MISC B-LOC
Petersburg I-MISC I-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
Swiss O B-LOC
- O O
born O O
Russian O B-LOC
architect O O
and O O
engineer O O
. O O

Alexander O O
" O O
Alex O O
" O O
Papaconstantinou O B-PER
( O O
Greek O B-LOC
: O O
Αλέξανδρος O B-PER
" O I-PER
Άλεξ O I-PER
" O I-PER
Παπακωνσταντίνου O I-PER
; O O
born O O
29 O O
December O O
1979 O O
in O O
Brännkyrka O B-LOC
, O O
Sweden B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
, O O
is O O
a O O
Swedish O B-LOC
songwriter O O
and O O
music O O
producer O O
of O O
Greek O B-LOC
origin O O
. O O

Originally O O
, O O
in O O
the O O
vicinity O O
of O O
the O O
Castle O B-LOC
, O O
Strand O B-LOC
Street O I-LOC
ran O O
along O O
the O O
Table O B-LOC
Bay O I-LOC
shore O I-LOC
 O O
- O O
 O O
" O O
strand O O
" O O
being O O
the O O
Dutch O B-MISC
and O O
Afrikaans B-MISC B-MISC
word O O
for O O
" O O
beach O O
" O O
 O O
- O O
 O O
but O O
land O O
reclamation O O
to O O
create O O
the O O
Foreshore O O
and O O
the O O
modern O O
Port O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Cape B-LOC I-LOC
Town I-LOC I-LOC
has O O
moved O O
the O O
shoreline O O
about O O
a O O
kilometre O O
to O O
the O O
northeast O O
. O O

Ernest B-MISC B-PER
Durig O I-PER
( O O
1894 O O
in O O
Zurich O B-LOC
, O O
Switzerland O B-LOC
– O O
1962 O O
in O O
Washington O B-LOC
, O I-LOC
D.C. O I-LOC
, O O
United O B-LOC
States O I-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
sculptor O O
and O O
art O O
forger O O
, O O
known O O
for O O
his O O
faking O O
of O O
drawings O O
by O O
Auguste B-PER B-PER
Rodin I-PER I-PER
. O O

Sima B-PER B-PER
Shi I-PER I-PER
( O O
208 O O
– O O
March O O
255 O O
) O O
, O O
courtesy O O
name O O
Ziyuan O B-PER
, O O
was O O
a O O
military O O
general O O
and O O
regent O O
of O O
Cao B-LOC B-PER
Wei I-LOC I-PER
during O O
the O O
Three B-MISC B-MISC
Kingdoms I-MISC I-MISC
period O I-MISC
of O O
China O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Next O B-MISC
- O I-MISC
Generation O I-MISC
Secure B-ORG I-MISC
Computing I-ORG I-MISC
Base O I-MISC
( O O
NGSCB O B-MISC
; O O
codenamed O O
Palladium O B-MISC
and O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
Trusted O B-MISC
Windows O I-MISC
) O O
is O O
a O O
cancelled O O
software O O
architecture O O
designed O O
by O O
Microsoft B-ORG B-ORG
which O O
aimed O O
to O O
provide O O
users O O
of O O
the O O
Windows O B-MISC
operating O O
system O O
with O O
better O O
privacy O O
, O O
security O O
, O O
and O O
system O O
integrity O O
. O O

Laura O B-PER
Margaret O I-PER
Attrux O I-PER
, O O
born O O
June O O
28 O O
, O O
1909 O O
, O O
in O O
Duck B-LOC B-LOC
Lake I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
Saskatchewan I-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Canada O B-LOC
, O O
was O O
a O O
nurse O O
who O O
received O O
an O O
Honorary O B-MISC
Doctor O I-MISC
of O I-MISC
Laws O I-MISC
Degree O I-MISC
from O O
the O O
University B-ORG B-ORG
of I-ORG I-ORG
Alberta I-ORG I-ORG
on O O
June O O
19 O O
, O O
1970 O O
. O O

Pontiac B-ORG B-ORG
Assembly O I-ORG
was O O
one O O
of O O
four O O
General B-ORG B-ORG
Motors I-ORG I-ORG
assembly O O
plants O O
in O O
Pontiac B-LOC B-ORG
, I-LOC O
Michigan I-LOC B-LOC
located O O
along O O
Baldwin O B-LOC
Avenue O I-LOC
. O O

Based O O
on O O
the O O
true O O
story O O
of O O
a O O
1987 O O
cross O O
country O O
team O O
from O O
a O O
mainly O O
Latino O B-LOC
high O O
school O O
in O O
McFarland B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
California I-LOC B-LOC
, O O
the O O
film O O
stars O O
Kevin B-PER B-PER
Costner I-PER I-PER
as O O
Jim O B-PER
White B-MISC I-PER
, O O
the O O
school O O
's O O
coach O O
, O O
who O O
leads O O
the O O
team O O
to O O
win O O
a O O
state O O
championship O O
. O O

He O O
fell O O
at O O
the O O
Battle B-MISC B-MISC
of I-MISC I-MISC
Rovine I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
17 O O
May O O
1395 O O
) O O
, O O
serving O O
the O O
Ottomans O B-ORG
against O O
Wallachia O B-LOC
, O O
fighting O O
alongside O O
Serbian O B-LOC
magnates O O
Stefan O B-PER
Lazarević O I-PER
and O O
Marko O B-PER
Mrnjavčević O I-PER
. O O

He O O
was O O
a O O
son O O
of O O
Stoddard O B-PER
Martin O I-PER
( O O
1781 O O
- O O
1868 O O
) O O
of O O
North O B-LOC
Ferrisburgh O I-LOC
, O O
Vermont O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
in O O
a O O
tradition O O
made O O
famous O O
by O O
Horace O B-PER
Greeley O I-PER
's O O
quote O O
'Go O O
West O O
, O O
young O O
man O O
" O O
took O O
a O O
trail O O
which O O
led O O
him O O
eventually O O
to O O
Madison O B-LOC
, O O
Wisconsin B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
where O O
he O O
built O O
a O O
domicile O O
which O O
was O O
one O O
of O O
the O O
first O O
in O O
the O O
future O O
capital O O
of O O
the O O
state O O
. O O

Souha O B-PER
Fawaz O I-PER
Bechara O I-PER
also O O
spelled O O
Souha B-PER B-PER
Bechara I-PER I-PER
or O O
Soha O B-PER
Bechara O I-PER
( O O
Arabic O B-MISC
: O O
سهى O B-PER
فواز O I-PER
بشارة O I-PER
) O O
( O O
born O O
June O O
15 O O
, O O
1967 O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
Lebanese O B-LOC
national O O
. O O

Designed O O
by O O
architect O O
Robert B-PER B-PER
Mills I-PER I-PER
, O O
it O O
is O O
one O O
of O O
America O B-LOC
's O O
earliest O O
and O O
most O O
distinctive O O
Greek O B-MISC
Revival O I-MISC
churches O O
and O O
is O O
listed O O
on O O
the O O
National O B-MISC
Register O I-MISC
of O I-MISC
Historic O I-MISC
Places O I-MISC
, O O
is O O
a O O
National O B-MISC
Historic O I-MISC
Landmark O I-MISC
and O O
is O O
located O O
in O O
the O O
Court O B-LOC
End O I-LOC
historic O O
district O O
. O O

He O O
was O O
admired O O
by O O
composers O O
as O O
diverse O O
as O O
Debussy O B-PER
, O O
Ravel O B-PER
, O O
Richard B-PER B-PER
Strauss I-PER I-PER
, O O
Satie O B-PER
, O O
Schmitt O O
, O O
Stravinsky O B-PER
, O O
and O O
the O O
group O O
of O O
composers O O
known O O
as O O
Les O B-ORG
six O I-ORG
. O O

The O O
Karangahake O B-LOC
Gorge O I-LOC
lies O O
between O O
the O O
Coromandel O B-LOC
and O O
Kaimai O B-LOC
ranges O O
, O O
at O O
the O O
southern O O
end O O
of O O
the O O
Coromandel O B-LOC
Peninsula O I-LOC
in O O
New O B-LOC
Zealand O I-LOC
's O O
North B-LOC B-LOC
Island I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Skjerka O B-LOC
, O O
Monn O B-LOC
and O O
Logna O B-LOC
all O O
flow O O
into O O
the O O
lake O O
Øre O B-LOC
in O O
Åseral O B-LOC
which O O
is O O
considered O O
the O O
beginning O O
of O O
the O O
main O O
Mandalselva B-LOC B-LOC
river O O
. O O

Since O O
2002 O O
Kwak O O
has O O
been O O
the O O
Chairman O O
and O O
President O O
of O O
News O B-ORG
World O I-ORG
Communications O I-ORG
, O O
which O O
is O O
affiliated O O
with O O
the O O
church O O
and O O
owns O O
United B-ORG B-ORG
Press I-ORG I-ORG
International I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
and O O
numerous O O
other O O
publications O O
, O O
including O O
the O O
" O O
Middle O B-ORG
East O I-ORG
Times O I-ORG
" O O
, O O
and O O
" O O
Tiempos O B-ORG
del O I-ORG
Mundo O I-ORG
" O O
, O O
a O O
Spanish O B-MISC
- O O
language O O
newspaper O O
published O O
in O O
16 O O
countries O O
throughout O O
the O O
Americas O B-LOC
. O O

Singles O O
from O O
the O O
album O O
include O O
" O O
Leave O B-MISC
Him O I-MISC
Out O I-MISC
of O I-MISC
This O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
Tips O I-MISC
of O I-MISC
My O I-MISC
Fingers O I-MISC
" O O
( O O
a O O
cover O O
of O O
Bill B-PER B-PER
Anderson I-PER I-PER
's O O
1960 O O
hit O O
) O O
, O O
" O O
A O B-MISC
Woman O I-MISC
Loves O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
" O O
Crash O B-MISC
Course O I-MISC
in O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Blues O I-MISC
" O O
and O O
" O O
Like O B-MISC
a O I-MISC
River O I-MISC
to O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Sea O I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Finlands O B-MISC
sak O I-MISC
är O I-MISC
vår O I-MISC
( O O
English O B-MISC
: O O
" O O
The O B-MISC
Finnish O I-MISC
cause O I-MISC
is O I-MISC
ours O I-MISC
" O O
) O O
is O O
the O O
title O O
of O O
a O O
Swedish O B-LOC
book O O
written O O
by O O
journalists O O
Olof B-PER B-PER
Lagercrantz I-PER I-PER
and O O
Karl O B-PER
- O I-PER
Gustaf O I-PER
Hillebrand O I-PER
. O O

Nije B-MISC B-MISC
ljubav I-MISC I-MISC
stvar I-MISC I-MISC
( O O
Serbian O B-LOC
Cyrillic O O
: O O
, O O
lit O O
: O O
" O O
Love O B-MISC
is O I-MISC
not O I-MISC
an O I-MISC
Object O I-MISC
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
song O O
by O O
Serbian O B-LOC
singer O O
Željko O B-PER
Joksimović O I-PER
and O O
yet O O
another O O
one O O
of O O
his O O
well O O
- O O
known O O
Balkan O B-LOC
ballads O O
. O O

British O B-LOC
" O O
Vogue O B-MISC
" O O
is O O
the O O
most O O
profitable O O
British O B-LOC
magazine O O
as O O
well O O
as O O
the O O
most O O
profitable O O
edition O O
of O O
" O O
Vogue O B-MISC
" O O
besides O O
the O O
US O B-LOC
and O O
China B-LOC B-LOC
editions O O
. O O

He O O
was O O
trained O O
as O O
an O O
actor O O
at O O
the O O
Stardust O B-ORG
Academy O I-ORG
by O O
Nari B-PER B-PER
Hira I-PER I-PER
of O O
Magna O B-ORG
Publications O I-ORG
, O O
where O O
he O O
was O O
trained O O
by O O
Namit O B-PER
Kishore O I-PER
Kapoor O I-PER
, O O
dance O O
by O O
Shakur O B-PER
and O O
voice O O
training O O
by O O
Ustad O B-PER
Akhtar O I-PER
Ali O I-PER
Khan O I-PER
. O O

Mawei O B-LOC
( O O
; O O
Foochow O B-MISC
Romanized O I-MISC
: O O
Mā O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
muōi O I-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
district O O
of O O
Fuzhou B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Fujian O B-LOC
province O O
, O O
People O B-LOC
's O I-LOC
Republic O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
China O I-LOC
. O O

The O B-ORG
Victorian O I-ORG
Gay O I-ORG
and O I-ORG
Lesbian O I-ORG
Rights O I-ORG
Lobby O I-ORG
( O O
VGLRL O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
the O O
peak O O
lobby O O
group O O
in O O
Victoria O B-LOC
, O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
for O O
the O O
attainment O O
of O O
equality O O
, O O
human O O
rights O O
and O O
social O O
justice O O
for O O
the O O
entire O O
Gay O B-MISC
, O I-MISC
Lesbian O I-MISC
, O I-MISC
Bisexual O I-MISC
, O I-MISC
Transgender O I-MISC
and O I-MISC
Intersex O I-MISC
( O O
GLBTI O B-MISC
) O O
community O O
. O O

On O O
the O O
Venetian O B-LOC
side O O
, O O
the O O
war O O
was O O
fought O O
to O O
avenge O O
the O O
loss O O
of O O
Crete B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
the O O
Cretan O B-MISC
War O I-MISC
( O O
1645–1669 O O
) O O
, O O
while O O
the O O
Ottomans O B-LOC
were O O
entangled O O
in O O
their O O
northern O O
frontier O O
against O O
the O O
Habsburgs O B-LOC
and O O
were O O
unable O O
to O O
concentrate O O
their O O
forces O O
against O O
the O O
Republic O B-LOC
. O O

The O O
Cascadia B-ORG B-ORG
official I-ORG I-ORG
soccer I-ORG I-ORG
team I-ORG I-ORG
is O O
the O O
official O O
association O O
football O O
team O O
representing O O
the O O
Cascadia O B-LOC
region O O
of O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
and O O
Canada O B-LOC
and O O
is O O
controlled O O
by O O
the O O
Cascadia O B-ORG
Association O I-ORG
Football O I-ORG
Federation O I-ORG
( O O
CAFF O B-ORG
) O O
. O O

Queenscliff O B-LOC
is O O
the O O
terminal O O
railway O O
station O O
of O O
the O O
Queenscliff O B-LOC
branch O O
line O O
that O O
originally O O
branched O O
off O O
the O O
main O O
Warrnambool O B-LOC
line O I-LOC
near O O
South O B-LOC
Geelong O I-LOC
in O O
Victoria O B-LOC
, O O
Australia B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Datawind O B-ORG
manufactures O O
low O O
cost O O
tablets O O
and O O
sells O O
these O O
primarily O O
in O O
India B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Nigeria O B-LOC
, O O
the O O
United O B-LOC
Kingdom O I-LOC
, O O
Canada O B-LOC
, O O
and O O
the O O
United O B-LOC
States O I-LOC
of O I-LOC
America O I-LOC
. O O

A O O
chādor O B-MISC
( O O
Persian O O
: O O
چادر‎ O O
‎ O O
) O O
, O O
also O O
variously O O
spelled O O
in O O
English O B-MISC
as O O
chadah O B-MISC
, O O
chad O O
( O O
d O O
) O O
ar O O
, O O
chader O B-MISC
, O O
chud O O
( O O
d O O
) O O
ah O O
, O O
chadur O B-MISC
and O O
naturalized O O
as O O
/tʃʌdə O O
( O O
ɹ O O
) O O
/ O O
is O O
an O O
outer O O
garment O O
or O O
open O O
cloak O O
worn O O
by O O
some O O
women O O
in O O
Iran B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
some O O
other O O
countries O O
in O O
public O O
spaces O O
or O O
outdoors O O
. O O

She O O
was O O
from O O
Qu O B-LOC
County O I-LOC
( O O
朐縣 O B-LOC
) O O
, O O
Donghai O B-LOC
Commandery O I-LOC
( O O
東海郡 O B-LOC
) O O
, O O
which O O
is O O
present O O
- O O
day O O
Lianyungang B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
Jiangsu O B-LOC
. O O

John O B-PER
Udell O I-PER
( O O
22 O O
June O O
1795 O O
– O O
30 O O
June O O
1874 O O
) O O
was O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
farmer O O
and O O
Baptist O B-ORG
lay O O
preacher O O
who O O
is O O
primarily O O
known O O
for O O
two O O
detailed O O
diaries O O
he O O
kept O O
of O O
his O O
travels O O
to O O
California O B-LOC
across O O
the O O
Great B-LOC B-LOC
Plains I-LOC I-LOC
of O O
the O B-LOC
United O I-LOC
States O I-LOC
. O O

Tajik O B-MISC
or O O
Tajiki O B-MISC
( O O
Tajik O B-MISC
: O O
забо́ни O B-MISC
тоҷикӣ́ O I-MISC
, O O
" O O
zaboni O B-MISC
tojikī O I-MISC
, O O
" O O
] O O
) O O
, O O
also O O
called O O
Tajiki O B-MISC
Persian O I-MISC
( O O
Tajik O B-MISC
: O O
форси́и O B-MISC
тоҷикӣ́ O I-MISC
, O O
" O O
forsii O B-MISC
tojikī O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
] O O
) O O
, O O
is O O
the O O
variety O O
of O O
Persian O B-MISC
spoken O O
in O O
Tajikistan B-LOC B-LOC
and O O
Uzbekistan B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

The O O
DARPA B-ORG B-MISC
Agent O I-MISC
Markup O I-MISC
Language O I-MISC
( O O
DAML O B-MISC
) O O
was O O
the O O
name O O
of O O
a O O
US O B-LOC
funding O O
program O O
at O O
the O O
US O B-ORG
Defense O I-ORG
Advanced O I-ORG
Research O I-ORG
Projects O I-ORG
Agency O I-ORG
( O O
DARPA B-ORG B-MISC
) O O
started O O
in O O
1999 O O
by O O
then O O
- O O
Program O O
Manager O O
James B-PER B-PER
Hendler I-PER I-PER
, O O
and O O
later O O
run O O
by O O
Murray O B-PER
Burke O I-PER
, O O
Mark B-PER B-PER
Greaves I-PER I-PER
and O O
Michael B-MISC B-PER
Pagels O I-PER
. O O

Branko O B-PER
" O I-PER
Isusek O I-PER
" O I-PER
Pleše O I-PER
( O O
12 O O
January O O
1915 O O
in O O
Delnice O B-LOC
– O O
28 O O
March O O
1980 O O
in O O
Zagreb B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
Croatian O B-LOC
footballer O O
who O O
played O O
international O O
football O O
for O O
the O O
Croatian O B-LOC
and O O
both O O
the O O
royal O O
and O O
communist O O
Yugoslavian O B-LOC
national O O
teams O O
. O O

Anīrān O O
( O O
Modern O B-MISC
Persian O I-MISC
) O O
or O O
Anērān O B-MISC
( O O
Middle B-MISC B-MISC
Persian I-MISC I-MISC
) O O
is O O
an O O
ethno O O
- O O
linguistic O O
term O O
that O O
signifies O O
" O O
non O O
- O O
Iranian O B-LOC
" O O
or O O
" O O
non O O
- O O
Iran O B-LOC
" O O
( O O
non O O
- O O
Aryan O B-MISC
) O O
. O O

Herzogenbusch O B-LOC
was O O
, O O
with O O
Natzweiler O B-LOC
- O I-LOC
Struthof O I-LOC
in O O
occupied O O
France O B-LOC
, O O
the O O
only O O
concentration O O
camp O O
run O O
directly O O
by O O
the O O
SS O B-ORG
in O O
western O O
Europe O B-LOC
outside O O
of O O
Germany B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

It O O
was O O
written O O
by O O
Anita O B-PER
McCloud O I-PER
and O O
Edmund O B-PER
Clement O I-PER
and O O
produced O O
by O O
the O O
latter O O
along O O
with O O
Jimmy O B-PER
Jam O I-PER
and O O
Terry B-PER B-PER
Lewis I-PER I-PER
for O O
Usher O B-PER
's O O
third O O
studio O O
album O O
" O O
8701 O B-MISC
" O O
( O O
2001 O O
) O O
. O O

The O O
Ringbahn O B-LOC
( O O
German O B-MISC
for O O
Circular O B-LOC
Railway O I-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
37.5 O O
km O O
( O O
23.3 O O
mi O O
) O O
long O O
railway O O
line O O
of O O
the O O
Berlin B-ORG B-MISC
S I-ORG I-MISC
- I-ORG I-MISC
Bahn I-ORG I-MISC
network O O
in O O
Germany B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
around O O
the O O
city O O
centre O O
. O O

A O O
former O O
track O O
cyclist O O
, O O
O'Grady B-MISC B-PER
and O O
Graeme B-PER B-PER
Brown I-PER I-PER
won O O
a O O
gold O O
medal O O
in O O
the O O
Men O B-MISC
's O I-MISC
Madison O I-MISC
at O O
the O O
2004 B-MISC O
Summer I-MISC B-MISC
Olympics I-MISC I-MISC
. O O

" O O
Nuthin O O
" O O
But O O
a O O
" O O
G O O
" O O
Thang O O
" O O
is O O
a O O
duet O O
by O O
American O B-LOC
rapper O O
Dr. B-PER B-PER
Dre I-PER I-PER
and O O
rapper O O
Snoop O B-PER
Doggy O I-PER
Dogg O I-PER
from O O
Dre O B-PER
's O O
debut O O
solo O O
album O O
, O O
" O O
The B-MISC B-ORG
Chronic I-MISC I-ORG
" O O
( O O
1992 O O
) O O
. O O

Konstantin B-MISC B-PER
Dejanović O I-PER
( O O
; O O
1365 O O
- O O
95 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Serbian O B-LOC
magnate O O
that O O
ruled O O
a O O
large O O
province O O
in O O
eastern O O
Macedonia O B-LOC
under O O
Ottoman O B-LOC
suzerainty O O
, O O
during O O
the O O
fall O O
of O O
the O O
Serbian B-LOC B-LOC
Empire I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Khan B-PER B-PER
Abdul I-PER I-PER
Wali I-PER I-PER
Khan I-PER I-PER
( O O
Pashto O O
: O O
خان O O
عبدالولي O O
خان‎ O O
, O O
Urdu B-MISC O
: O O
‎ O O
, O O
born O O
: O O
11 O O
January O O
1917 O O
– O O
26 O O
January O O
2006 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
British O B-LOC
Indian O I-LOC
and O O
later O O
Pakistani O B-LOC
secular O O
democratic O O
socialist O O
and O O
Pashtun O B-ORG
leader O O
, O O
and O O
served O O
as O O
president O O
of O O
National O B-ORG
Awami O I-ORG
Party O I-ORG
. O O

The O O
American B-ORG B-ORG
Broadcasting I-ORG I-ORG
Company I-ORG I-ORG
( O O
ABC O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
broadcast O O
television O O
television O O
network O O
owned O O
by O O
the O O
Disney O B-ORG
Media O I-ORG
Networks O I-ORG
subsidiary O O
of O O
The B-ORG O
Walt I-ORG B-ORG
Disney I-ORG I-ORG
Company I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
which O O
originated O O
in O O
1927 O O
as O O
the O O
NBC B-ORG B-ORG
Blue B-MISC I-ORG
radio O O
network O O
, O O
and O O
five O O
years O O
after O O
its O O
1942 O O
divorce O O
from O O
NBC B-ORG B-ORG
and O O
purchase O O
by O O
Edward B-MISC B-PER
J. O I-PER
Noble O I-PER
( O O
adopting O O
its O O
current O O
name O O
the O O
following O O
year O O
) O O
, O O
expanded O O
into O O
television O O
in O O
April O O
1948. O O
s O O
of O O
March O O
2015 O O
, O O
the O O
network O O
currently O O
has O O
eight O O
owned O O
- O O
and O O
- O O
operated O O
stations O O
, O O
and O O
current O O
affiliation O O
agreements O O
with O O
238 O O
other O O
television O O
stations O O
. O O

This O O
species O O
was O O
found O O
in O O
the O O
Villavieja O B-LOC
Formation O I-LOC
in O O
the O O
area O O
of O O
La O B-LOC
Venta B-LOC I-LOC
in O O
Colombia B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
a O O
famous O O
fossil O O
deposit O O
in O O
the O O
Middle O B-MISC
Miocene O I-MISC
( O O
Laventan O B-MISC
; O O
13.8 O O
- O O
11.8 O O
million O O
years O O
ago O O
) O O
, O O
based O O
on O O
fragments O O
that O O
include O O
a O O
front O O
portion O O
of O O
the O O
lower O O
jaw O O
, O O
with O O
an O O
incipient O O
molar O O
tooth O O
and O O
a O O
piece O O
of O O
carnassial O O
from O O
the O O
front O O
of O O
the O O
maxilla O O
. O O

Trágala O B-MISC
( O O
Spanish O B-LOC
: O O
" O O
swallow O O
it O O
" O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
song O O
the O O
Spanish O B-LOC
liberals O O
used O O
to O O
humiliate O O
the O O
absolutists O O
after O O
the O O
military O O
" O O
pronunciamiento O O
" O O
of O O
Rafael B-PER B-PER
del I-PER I-PER
Riego I-PER I-PER
in O O
Cabezas O B-LOC
de O I-LOC
San O I-LOC
Juan B-MISC I-LOC
, O O
at O O
the O O
beginning O O
of O O
the O O
period O O
known O O
as O O
Trienio O O
Liberal O O
( O O
1820 O O
- O O
1823 O O
) O O
. O O

NXT O B-MISC
TakeOver O I-MISC
took O O
place O O
on O O
December O O
11 O O
, O O
2014 O O
at O O
NXT O B-ORG
's O O
" O O
home O O
" O O
arena O O
, O O
Full B-ORG B-ORG
Sail I-ORG I-ORG
University I-ORG I-ORG
in O O
Winter B-LOC B-LOC
Park I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
Florida I-LOC B-LOC
and O O
featured O O
six O O
matches O O
as O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
main O O
broadcast O O
and O O
one O O
match O O
prior O O
to O O
the O O
televised O O
portion O O
of O O
the O O
show O O
. O O

Prokkonen O B-PER
was O O
also O O
the O O
Minister O O
of O O
Karelian O B-MISC
Affairs O I-MISC
for O O
the O O
Finnish B-LOC B-ORG
Democratic I-LOC I-ORG
Republic I-LOC I-ORG
during O O
the O O
Winter B-MISC B-MISC
War I-MISC I-MISC
in O O
1940 O O
( O O
under O O
the O O
name O O
Paavo O B-PER
Prokkonen O I-PER
) O O

Charles B-PER B-PER
Olemus I-PER O
( O O
born O O
February O O
16 O O
, O O
1947 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
Haitian O B-LOC
track O O
and O O
field O O
athlete O O
who O O
competed O O
at O O
the O O
1976 O B-MISC
Olympic B-MISC I-MISC
Games I-MISC I-MISC
in O O
Montreal B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

Nagata O B-PER
was O O
convicted O O
of O O
murdering O O
, O O
or O O
participating O O
in O O
the O O
murder O O
of O O
, O O
fellow O O
members O O
of O O
the O O
United B-MISC B-ORG
Red I-MISC I-ORG
Army I-MISC I-ORG
( O O
URA O B-ORG
) O O
during O O
a O O
group O O
purge O O
in O O
Gunma O B-LOC
prefecture O O
, O O
Japan B-LOC B-LOC
in O O
February O O
1972 O O
. O O

Fàn O B-PER
Chun O I-PER
Yip O I-PER
( O O
born O O
1 O O
May O O
1976 O O
in O O
Hong B-LOC B-LOC
Kong I-LOC I-LOC
) O O
, O O
with O O
the O O
nickname O O
" O O
Piggy O O
" O O
( O O
豬仔 O O
; O O
) O O
, O O
is O O
a O O
retired O O
goalkeeper O O
and O O
goalkeeping O O
coach O O
for O O
Hong B-LOC B-ORG
Kong I-LOC I-ORG
Pegasus O I-ORG
FC O I-ORG
, O O
was O O
in O O
the O O
squad O O
of O O
the O O
Hong B-ORG B-LOC
Kong I-ORG I-LOC
national I-ORG O
football I-ORG O
team I-ORG O
as O O
a O O
captain O O
, O O
and O O
now O O
has O O
been O O
promoted O O
to O O
become O O
a O O
goalkeeping O O
coach O O
of O O
the O O
national O O
team O O
. O O

El B-ORG B-ORG
Gran I-ORG I-ORG
Combo I-ORG I-ORG
de I-ORG I-ORG
Puerto I-ORG I-ORG
Rico I-ORG I-ORG
, O O
commonly O O
known O O
as O O
El O B-ORG
Gran O I-ORG
Combo O I-ORG
, O O
is O O
a O O
Puerto O B-LOC
Rican O I-LOC
salsa O O
orchestra O O
based O O
in O O
San B-LOC B-LOC
Juan I-LOC I-LOC
, I-LOC O
Puerto I-LOC B-LOC
Rico I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Members O O
include O O
Yuri O B-PER
Nakamura O I-PER
, O O
Hitoshi B-PER B-PER
Okamoto I-PER I-PER
, O O
Nana O B-PER
Azuki O I-PER
, O O
and O O
Hirohito B-PER B-PER
Furui O I-PER
, O O
with O O
Nakamura O B-PER
leading O O
on O O
vocals O O
. O O

Sony B-ORG B-ORG
Interactive B-ORG I-ORG
Entertainment B-ORG I-ORG
( O O
abbreviated O O
as O O
SIE O B-ORG
and O O
formerly O O
known O O
as O O
Sony B-ORG B-ORG
Computer O I-ORG
Entertainment B-ORG I-ORG
( O O
SCE O B-ORG
) O O
and O O
Sony B-ORG B-ORG
Network O O
Entertainment B-ORG O
) O O
is O O
a O O
multinational O O
video O O
game O O
company O O
and O O
is O O
a O O
wholly O O
owned O O
subsidiary O O
and O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
Consumer O O
Products O O
and O O
Services O O
Group O O
of O O
Sony B-ORG B-ORG
. O O

Paul B-PER B-PER
Raphaelson I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
1968 O O
, O O
New B-MISC B-LOC
York I-MISC I-LOC
, I-MISC O
New I-MISC B-LOC
York I-MISC I-LOC
, O O
USA O B-LOC
) O O
, O O
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
artist O O
best O O
known O O
for O O
urban O O
landscape O O
photography O O
. O O

" O O
The O B-MISC
Responsibility B-MISC I-MISC
of O I-MISC
Intellectuals O I-MISC
" O O
is O O
an O O
essay O O
by O O
the O O
American O B-LOC
academic O O
Noam B-PER B-PER
Chomsky I-PER I-PER
which O O
was O O
published O O
as O O
a O O
special O O
supplement O O
by O O
" O O
The B-MISC O
New I-MISC B-ORG
York I-MISC I-ORG
Review I-MISC I-ORG
of I-MISC I-ORG
Books I-MISC I-ORG
" O O
on O O
the O O
23 O O
February O O
1967 O O
. O O

Pacino B-PER B-PER
Horne I-PER I-PER
( O O
born O O
November O O
23 O O
, O O
1983 O O
in O O
Ypsilanti B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
Michigan I-LOC B-LOC
) O O
is O O
a O O
professional O O
Canadian B-MISC B-LOC
football I-MISC O
defensive O O
back O O
who O O
is O O
currently O O
a O O
free O O
agent O O
. O O

Boston B-LOC B-ORG
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
rock O O
band O O
from O O
Boston B-LOC B-ORG
, O O
Massachusetts B-LOC B-LOC
, O O
that O O
achieved O O
their O O
most O O
notable O O
successes O O
during O O
the O O
1970s O O
and O O
1980s O O
. O O

It O O
is O O
a O O
richly O O
embellished O O
Italianate O B-MISC
style O O
building O O
built O O
originally O O
for O O
Jacob O B-PER
J. O I-PER
Bankard O I-PER
, O O
one O O
of O O
many O O
enterprising O O
and O O
prominent O O
butchers O O
who O O
flocked O O
to O O
" O O
Butcher O O
’ O O
s O O
Hill O O
" O O
, O O
and O O
later O O
George O B-PER
Gunther O I-PER
, O O
who O O
established O O
the O O
Gunther B-LOC B-ORG
Brewing I-LOC I-ORG
Company I-LOC I-ORG
in O O
Baltimore B-LOC B-LOC
. O O

EasyJet B-ORG B-ORG
( O O
styled O O
as O O
easyJet O B-ORG
; O O
) O O
is O O
a O O
British O B-LOC
airline O O
, O O
operating O O
under O O
the O O
low O O
- O O
cost O O
carrier O O
model O O
, O O
based O O
at O O
London B-LOC B-LOC
Luton B-LOC I-LOC
Airport I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

Jeffrey O O
Lane O O
" O O
Jeff O O
" O O
Hephner O B-PER
( O O
born O O
June O O
22 O O
, O O
1975 O O
) O O
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
actor O O
, O O
known O O
for O O
his O O
recurring O O
role O O
as O O
Matt B-PER B-PER
Ramsey I-PER I-PER
in O O
the O O
third O O
season O O
of O O
the O O
Fox B-MISC B-ORG
drama O O
" O O
The B-MISC O
O.C I-MISC O
. I-MISC O
" O O

Brigadier O O
Reginald B-PER B-PER
Miles I-PER I-PER
, O O
CBE O O
, O O
DSO O O
& O O
Bar O O
, O O
MC O O
( O O
10 O O
December O O
1892 O O
– O O
20 O O
October O O
1943 O O
) O O
was O O
a O O
professional O O
soldier O O
who O O
served O O
in O O
the O O
New B-LOC B-ORG
Zealand I-LOC I-ORG
Military O I-ORG
Forces O I-ORG
during O O
the O O
First O B-MISC
and O O
Second B-MISC B-MISC
World I-MISC I-MISC
Wars O I-MISC
. O O

Written O O
on O O
his O O
birthday O O
( O O
January O O
5 O O
, O O
2007 O O
) O O
, O O
the O O
song O O
was O O
initially O O
set O O
as O O
the O O
first O O
single O O
from O O
the O O
album O O
, O O
but O O
this O O
was O O
soon O O
changed O O
at O O
the O O
request O O
of O O
Manson O B-PER
's O O
record O O
label O O
, O O
Interscope O B-ORG
, O O
and O O
" O O
Heart B-MISC B-MISC
- I-MISC I-MISC
Shaped I-MISC I-MISC
Glasses I-MISC I-MISC
( O I-MISC
When O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Heart O I-MISC
Guides O I-MISC
the O I-MISC
Hand B-MISC I-MISC
) O I-MISC
" O O
was O O
released O O
instead O O
as O O
the O O
album O O
's O O
first O O
single O O
( O O
similar O O
to O O
the O O
case O O
of O O
" O O
Get B-MISC B-MISC
Your I-MISC I-MISC
Gunn I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
from O O
the O O
band O O
's O O
debut O O
) O O
. O O

Jarmo O B-PER
Viinanen O I-PER
( O O
born O O
February O O
23 O O
, O O
1959 O O
, O O
Imatra O B-LOC
) O O
was O O
a O O
Finnish O B-LOC
ambassador O O
to O O
Sweden B-LOC B-LOC
until O O
2016 O O
, O O
and O O
was O O
President O O
of O O
the O O
UNICEF B-MISC B-ORG
Executive O I-ORG
Board O I-ORG
in O O
2013 O O
. O O

A O O
long O O
- O O
time O O
staple O O
of O O
Italian O B-LOC
genre O O
cinema O O
, O O
Pigozzi O B-PER
was O O
known O O
for O O
such O O
films O O
as O O
" O O
Human O B-MISC
Cobras O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
" O O
Yor B-MISC B-MISC
, I-MISC O
the I-MISC B-MISC
Hunter I-MISC I-MISC
from I-MISC I-MISC
the I-MISC I-MISC
Future I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
" O O
Ivanhoe B-MISC B-MISC
, O O
the O B-MISC
Norman O I-MISC
Swordsman O I-MISC
" O O
, O O
" O O
Blood B-MISC B-MISC
and I-MISC I-MISC
Black I-MISC I-MISC
Lace I-MISC I-MISC
" O O
, O O
" O O
Libido O B-MISC
" O O
and O O
perhaps O O
his O O
goriest O O
role O O
in O O
" O O
Baron B-PER B-MISC
Blood I-PER I-MISC
" O O
. O O

Otto B-MISC B-PER
is O O
a O O
daughter O O
of O O
actors O O
Barry O B-PER
and O O
Lindsay O B-PER
Otto B-MISC I-PER
, O O
and O O
half O O
- O O
sister O O
of O O
actress O O
Gracie B-PER B-PER
Otto I-PER I-PER
. O O

The O O
Kaldanes O B-MISC
are O O
a O O
fictitious O O
sapient O O
species O O
existing O O
in O O
the O O
region O O
of O O
Bantoom O B-LOC
on O O
the O O
planet O O
Barsoom O B-LOC
in O O
the O O
John B-PER B-MISC
Carter I-PER I-MISC
series O O
of O O
books O O
by O O
Edgar B-PER B-PER
Rice I-PER I-PER
Burroughs I-PER I-PER
. O O

In O O
1999 O O
the O O
organisation O O
in O O
the O O
UK O B-LOC
adopted O O
the O O
name O O
Japan B-LOC B-ORG
Christian O I-ORG
Link O I-ORG
for O O
their O O
operations O O
in O O
the O O
UK O B-LOC
, O O
while O O
work O O
in O O
Japan B-LOC B-LOC
continue O O
under O O
the O O
name O O
of O O
JEB O B-ORG
. O O

Nouri O B-PER
Kamil O I-PER
Mohammed O I-PER
Hasan O I-PER
al O I-PER
- O I-PER
Maliki O I-PER
( O O
Arabic O O
: O O
نوري O O
كامل O O
محمد O O
حسن O O
المالكي‎ O O
‎ O O
; O O
born O O
20 O O
June O O
1950 O O
) O O
, O O
also O O
known O O
as O O
Jawad O B-PER
al O I-PER
- O I-PER
Maliki O I-PER
( O O
جواد O O
المالكي O O
) O O
or O O
Abu O B-PER
Esraa O I-PER
( O O
أبو O O
إسراء O O
) O O
, O O
is O O
an O O
Iraqi O B-LOC
politician O O
who O O
was O O
Prime B-PER O
Minister I-PER O
of O O
Iraq B-LOC B-LOC
from O O
2006 O O
to O O
2014 O O
. O O

Often O O
mistakenly O O
called O O
" O O
Rosarito B-LOC B-LOC
Beach I-LOC I-LOC
" O O
because O O
of O O
the O O
well O O
- O O
known O O
Rosarito B-LOC B-LOC
Beach I-LOC I-LOC
Hotel O I-LOC
, O O
the O O
town O O
of O O
Rosarito O B-LOC
is O O
one O O
part O O
of O O
the O O
municipality O O
named O O
Playas O B-LOC
de O I-LOC
Rosarito O I-LOC
( O O
" O O
Beaches O B-LOC
of O I-LOC
Rosarito O I-LOC
" O O
) O O
. O O

Malaysians B-MISC B-ORG
in I-MISC I-ORG
the I-MISC I-ORG
United I-MISC I-ORG
Kingdom I-MISC I-ORG
are O O
British O B-LOC
citizens O O
who O O
are O O
of O O
Malaysian O B-LOC
descent O O
or O O
Malaysian O B-LOC
citizens O O
residing O O
in O O
the O O
United B-LOC B-LOC
Kingdom I-LOC I-LOC
. O O

He O O
reestablished O O
the O O
Song B-LOC B-MISC
dynasty I-LOC I-MISC
( O O
as O O
the O O
Southern O B-MISC
Song B-LOC I-MISC
dynasty I-LOC I-MISC
) O O
in O O
Lin'an O B-LOC
( O O
present O O
- O O
day O O
Hangzhou B-LOC B-LOC
) O O
and O O
was O O
proclaimed O O
emperor O O
. O O

The O O
Impeachment O B-MISC
March O I-MISC
, O O
sometimes O O
referred O O
to O O
as O O
the O O
" O O
Impeach O B-MISC
Trump O I-MISC
" O O
protest O O
, O O
was O O
a O O
series O O
of O O
rallies O O
against O O
the O O
President O O
of O O
the O B-LOC
United B-LOC I-LOC
States I-LOC I-LOC
, O O
Donald B-PER B-PER
Trump I-PER I-PER
, O O
held O O
nationwide O O
on O O
July O O
2–4 O O
, O O
2017 O O
, O O
advocating O O
that O O
Congress O B-ORG
begin O O
the O O
impeachment O O
process O O
against O O
him O O
. O O

Africa B-LOC B-ORG
Finance O I-ORG
Corporation B-ORG I-ORG
( O O
AFC O B-ORG
) O O
is O O
a O O
pan O O
- O O
African O B-LOC
multilateral O O
development O O
finance O O
institution O O
established O O
in O O
2007 O O
to O O
bridge O O
Africa B-LOC B-LOC
’ O O
s O O
infrastructure O O
investment O O
gap O O
through O O
the O O
provision O O
of O O
debt O O
and O O
equity O O
finance O O
, O O
project O O
development O O
, O O
technical O O
and O O
financial O O
advisory O O
services O O
. O O

Arsen O B-PER
Sheklian O I-PER
, O O
better O O
known O O
by O O
his O O
stage O O
name O O
Arsen B-PER B-PER
Roulette I-PER I-PER
, O O
( O O
born O O
July O O
23 O O
, O O
1976 O O
) O O
is O O
an O O
American O B-LOC
singer O O
, O O
lyricist O O
, O O
guitar O O
player O O
and O O
upright O O
bass O O
player O O
from O O
Fresno B-LOC B-LOC
, I-LOC O
California I-LOC B-LOC
. O O
